<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>ESO Announcements</title>
        <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/</link>
        <description>Combined ESO blog and forum post announcements feed</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>Magic</generator>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Crown Store Showcase—August 2024]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66453</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66453</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Check out the new mounts, houses, and other exciting collectibles coming to the Crown Store this August!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/ddcaf7f77872a9ecc2b541e6fba0f114.jpg" /><p><i>Check out the new mounts, houses, and other exciting collectibles coming to the Crown Store this August!</i></p> 
<p>The summer is heating up, and so are the offerings from the Crown Store! Find fiery finery and hot new items to make the most of the month. Be sure to head over to the <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/crownstore">Crown Store page</a> to check out the currently available items. One or more of these goodies catch your eye? Then drop by the <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/buycrowns">Buy Crowns page</a> and secure however many crowns you need! Certain items and offers will be available for a limited time only, so be sure to read their details below and don't miss out.</p> 
<h2>ESO Plus Deals</h2> 
<p>All ESO Plus™ members have access to a monthly selection of exclusive deals and items. You can find more information about them in <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/54825">this article</a>.</p> 
<p><b>Exclusive Free Items</b></p> 
<p><b>Painting: The Stitches</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/662c356ad984b2791d1fc4a9296c6302.jpg" />
<p><i>Located within the Scar in Northern Elsweyr, the Stitches draws the eye of many an artist seeking the challenge of illustrating a more vertically oriented settlement.</i></p> 
<p>The Painting: The Stitches will be available in the Crown Store FREE, exclusively to ESO Plus Members on all platforms for a limited time, from August 29, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to October 3, 2024 at 10AM EDT.</p> 
<p><b>Statuette: Auriel of Garlas Agea</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/f166622e3e8a9b8e1cddf867489f8f1b.jpg" />
<p><i>A miniature statue of Auriel, King of the Aldmer. Based on the storied effigy of the same name in the ruins of Garlas Agea along the Gold Coast.</i></p> 
<p>The Statuette: Auriel of Garlas Agea will be available in the Crown Store FREE, exclusively to ESO Plus Members on all platforms for a limited time, from July 29, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to August 29, 2024 at 10AM EDT.</p> 
<h2>Crown Gem and Seals of Endeavor Items</h2> 
<p><b>Celestial Lynx</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/5d8841305145dd18ccfc4ec06f579d5f.jpg" />
<p><i>Swift as a stream and silent as a shadow, this creature appears in many folktales across Tamriel. In some, the lynx stalks its quarry across the night sky. In others it's an agile companion, perfect for worthy hunters prowling the darkest nights.</i></p> 
<p>The Celestial Lynx mount will be available for Crown Gems and Seals of Endeavor on all platforms for a limited time, from August 8, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to August 22, 2024 at 10AM EDT.</p> 
<p><b>Blazeborn Wolf</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/7352142c786846a7bd461e5dfef98390.jpg" />
<p><i>None can say the Blazeborn Wolf lacks a bold appearance, formed from flames as it is. Even bolder, though, is its temperament, making it a perfect companion for racing through icy wastes to confront foes you deem worthy of your courage!</i></p> 
<p>The Blazeborn Wolf mount will be available for Crown Gems and Seals of Endeavor on all platforms for a limited time, from August 22, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to September 5, 2024 at 10AM EDT.</p> 
<h2>Crafting</h2> 
<p><b>Crown Crafting Motif: Elder Argonian</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/e53124a1b1fa36649f3ce1c9fae70069.jpg" />
<p><i>Concordia Mercius of Cyrodilic Collections writes, "The similarity of designs and motifs found during our expeditions across Black Marsh suggest that the Argonians once may have had a more unified civilization, or perhaps simply traded more widely." Use to learn the Elder Argonian crafting style.</i></p> 
<p>The Crown Crafting Motif: Elder Argonian will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from August 1, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to August 5, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item. Elder Argonian Motif chapters, and very rarely the complete book, have a chance to drop from Tribal Armor Crates, awarded by completing daily quests in Murkmire.</p> 
<p><b>Crown Crafting Motif: Silver Rose</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/62b080003bb7f64d6b2fd7c6d4ef91da.jpg" />
<p><i>Chief Archivist Bartholomew states, “Like our namesake, the liveries of the venerable Knights of the Silver Rose have grown haler and more beautiful with each generation, tended by collective wisdom and guidance of our order.” Use to learn the Silver Rose crafting style.</i></p> 
<p>The Crown Crafting Motif: Silver Rose will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from August 12, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to August 15, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item. Silver Rose Motif chapters, and very rarely the complete book, have a chance to drop from Prior Thierric Sarazen in the Red Petal Bastion dungeon. Harder difficulties will increase the chances of the item dropping.</p> 
<p><b>Crown Crafting Motif: Black Fin Legion</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/be718047aed7672e3a1f4c9bf3b65a6d.jpg" />
<p><i>Keshu the Black Fin notes, “From head to toe, the Black Fin legionnaire must dress for conditions that destroy the arms and armor of other lands. But if the swamp is an enemy to the unprepared, it can also be a potent ally for the warrior who learns its ways.” Use to learn the Black Fin Legion crafting style.</i></p> 
<p>The Crown Crafting Motif: Black Fin Legion will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from August 15, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to August 22, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item. Black Fin Legion Motif chapters, and very rarely the complete book, have a chance to drop from Leyawiin Reward Coffers, awarded by completing delve daily quests for Deetum-Jas in Leyawiin.</p> 
<p><b>Crown Crafting Motif: Stags of Z'en</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/7ef5ced60cd4eec720ec51fb4956f7f2.jpg" />
<p><i>Gwaerelos, Greenblessed Master of Arms, states: "We Stags exact punishment for transgression and wickedness, seeking payment in kind. We claim that payment in blood. Z'en, god of toil and vengeance, demands nothing less.” Use to learn the Stags of Z'en crafting style.</i></p> 
<p>The Crown Crafting Motif: Stags of Z'en will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from August 19, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to August 22, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item. Stags of Z'en Motif chapters, and very rarely the complete book, have a chance to drop from Maarselok in the Lair of Maarselok dungeon. Harder difficulties will increase the chances of the item dropping.</p> 
<p><b>Crown Crafting Motif: Waking Flame</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/a691c2413ab7711f804d823e778877eb.jpg" />
<p><i>Dress and armor yourself in the fashion to best please Lord Dagon and commit atrocities on the tiresome "innocents" roaming Tamriel! Use to learn the Waking Flame crafting style.</i></p> 
<p>The Crown Crafting Motif: Waking Flame will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from August 22, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to August 26, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item. Waking Flame Motif chapters, and very rarely the complete book, have a chance to drop from Baron Zaudrus in The Cauldron dungeon. Harder difficulties will increase the chances of the item dropping.</p> 
<p><b>Crown Crafting Motif: Pyre Watch</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/bc89e34e394609fb5967e4e5db2d1a66.jpg" />
<p><i>Tazheq at-Rajd writes, "A horror rests within this Unhallowed Grave. Know well our order's arms and armor that give us the strength to defend the living. Because, the Gray Host shall not wake. Death must be the end." Use to learn the Pyre Watch crafting style.</i></p> 
<p>The Crown Crafting Motif: Pyre Watch will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from August 29, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to September 2, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item. Pyre Watch Motif chapters, and very rarely the complete book, have a chance to drop from Kjalnar Tombskald in the Unhallowed Grave dungeon. Harder difficulties will increase the chances of the item dropping.</p> 
<p><b>Outfit Style</b></p> 
<p><b>Prior Thierric Arms Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/3396cf135f4c072ba39b96cd67f08697.jpg" />
<p><i>Venturing into Red Petal Bastion, the stronghold of a knightly order that has fallen from grace, puts you on a path to confront the deadly Prior Thierric Sarazen. Alter your weapon's appearance to match the Undaunted Prior Thierric awards by using this complete set of Outfit styles.</i></p> 
<p>The Prior Thierric Arms Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from August 1, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to August 5, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item. The matching mask page will have a small chance to drop from Prior Thierric Sarazen from veteran Red Petal Bastion. The matching shoulder page can be purchased from Urgarlag Chief-bane for 50 Undaunted keys, or has a chance of dropping from Urgarlag's Mystery Coffer for 1 key. Having the achievement “Prior Offenses” increases the drop chances of both items.</p> 
<p><b>Valkyn Skoria Arms Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/991cf83060ce569fd07bbe55767ddea2.jpg" />
<p><i>The minion of Mehrunes Dagon, Valkyn Skoria, awaits any who seek to close an Oblivion Gate in the City of Ash. Alter your weapon's appearance to match the Undaunted Valkyn Skoria awards by using this complete set of Outfit styles.</i></p> 
<p>The Valkyn Skoria Arms Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from August 5, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to August 12, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item. The matching mask page will have a small chance to drop from Valkyn Skoria from veteran City of Ash II. The matching shoulder page can be purchased from Glirion the Redbeard for 50 Undaunted keys, or has a chance of dropping from Glirion's Mystery Coffer for 1 key. Having the achievement “A World On Fire” increases the drop chances of both items.</p> 
<p><b>Stonekeeper Arms Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/f91c34b3848c3ba1dbc9185f0c0bdbf8.jpg" />
<p><i>The Dwarven Colossus called Stonekeeper awaits any seeking to explore the newly unearthed Frostvault. Alter your weapon's appearance to match the Undaunted Stonekeeper awards by using this complete set of Outfit styles.</i></p> 
<p>The Stonekeeper Arms Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from August 8, 2024 at 1PM EDT, to August 12, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item. The matching mask page will have a small chance to drop from the Stonekeeper from veteran Frostvault. The matching shoulder page can be purchased from Urgarlag Chief-bane for 50 Undaunted keys, or has a chance of dropping from Urgarlag's Mystery Coffer for 1 key. Having the achievement “Vault Cracker” increases the drop chances of both items.</p> 
<p><b>Kargaeda Arms Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/17cc1f78290c3cd05c230b609a754461.jpg" />
<p><i>Confront the powerful gryphon Kargaeda in what Urgarlag Chief-bane calls the "glorious mess" that the Ascendant Order and yaghra have made of Coral Aerie. Alter your weapon's appearance to match the Undaunted Kargaeda awards by using this complete set of Outfit styles.</i></p> 
<p>The Kargaeda Arms Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from August 12, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to August 15, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item. The matching mask page will have a small chance to drop from Varallion from veteran Coral Aerie. The matching shoulder page can be purchased from Urgarlag Chief-bane for 50 Undaunted keys, or has a chance of dropping from Urgarlag's Mystery Coffer for 1 key. Having the achievement “Superior Pedigree” increases the drop chances of both items.</p> 
<p><b>Elder Scrolls Artifact: Sword of Jyggalag</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/ef13f789cfe3d9892c667ac80136c989.jpg" />
<p><i>Alter your two-handed sword's Outfit style with a replica of the Sword of Jyggalag Elder Scrolls Artifact, the claymore created by the absent Prince of Order.</i></p> 
<p>The Elder Scrolls Artifact: Sword of Jyggalag will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from August 15, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to August 19, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item. </p> 
<p><b>Infernal Guardian Arms Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/8b3172c25499b1cd1ef3663c3b525832.jpg" />
<p><i>The blazing lurcher called the Infernal Guardian may prove a worthy challenge to any seeking to confront enemies within the City of Ash. Alter your weapon's appearance to match the Undaunted Infernal Guardian awards by using this set of Outfit styles.</i></p> 
<p>The Infernal Guardian Arms Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from August 19, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to August 26, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item. The matching mask page will have a small chance to drop from Razor Master Erthas from veteran City of Ash I. The matching shoulder page can be purchased from Glirion the Redbeard for 50 Undaunted keys, or has a chance of dropping from Glirion's Mystery Coffer for 1 key. Having the achievement “Fire Brigade” increases the drop chances of both items.</p> 
<p><b>Encratis's Behemoth Arms Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/c0d1c882723418d6a7d566a5d641aedd.jpg" />
<p><i>Pyroturge Encratis of the True-Sworn and his fire behemoth creations enjoy a good conflagration, making them worthy opponents to any who dare traverse Black Drake Villa. Alter your weapon's appearance to match the Undaunted Encratis's Behemoth awards by using this complete set of Outfit styles.</i></p> 
<p>The Encratis's Behemoth Arms Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from August 29, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to September 2, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item. The matching mask page will have a small chance to drop from Pyroturge Encratis from veteran Black Drake Villa. The matching shoulder page can be purchased from Urgarlag Chief-bane for 50 Undaunted keys, or has a chance of dropping from Urgarlag's Mystery Coffer for 1 key. Having the achievement “Snuffed Out” increases the drop chances of both items.</p> 
<h2>Adornment</h2> 
<p><b>The Standing Wave</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/9f64d3cb79f5fa76027f197561c37b02.jpg" />
<p><i>Do you stand tall and proud, adventurer? Then so should your hair! Add to your already impressive height with The Standing Wave, the hairdo that's sweeping the Fighters Guild.</i></p> 
<p>The Standing Wave adornment will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from August 29, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to September 2, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<h2>Wardrobe</h2> 
<p><b>Pellitine Tea-Fete Gown</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/16dc59a80a850a1908d06d9de95dd56c.jpg" />
<p><i>Originally worn during the ancient Pa'alatiin clan's tradition of taking tea, this classic garment's popularity has resurged in recent months, making it the perfect dress for any Khajiiti gathering.</i></p> 
<p>The Pellitine Tea-Fete Gown will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from August 1, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to August 5, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<p><b>Vinedusk Vigilant</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/e4204e19962b0cc4e378b26489e8bdd7.jpg" />
<p><i>Among the Vinedusk Rangers lurks an even more dangerous force: assassin-scouts who move quietly through forests, dealing with any who pose a threat. Sometimes called "tree ghosts," they wear custom-made gear that works with their preferred combat styles.</i></p> 
<p>The Vinedusk Vigilant will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from August 19, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to August 22, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<p><b>Liespinner's Vestments</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/dc8b1d1ed2c83b1d14804917ede6acf0.jpg" />
<p><i>Acolytes of Mephala spread falsehoods and disinformation to keep their secrets hidden. When they meet, they don these vestments to conceal their identities. Beware her whispers beneath the veil.</i></p> 
<p>The Liespinner's Vestments will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from August 19, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to August 22, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<p><b>Dragon Priest</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/9bbd8f8f48775dbae40eb26f9e2be412.jpg" />
<p><i>Once, it is said, a cult of Dragon-worshipers ruled all of northern Tamriel. Their leaders were Dragon Priests, cruel clerics of great power who hid their faces under magical masks. Now you can wear the semblance of these legendary magi.</i></p> 
<p>The Dragon Priest will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from August 22, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to August 26, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<h2>Skins</h2> 
<p><b>Mind-Shriven</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/78a5df06b3064ae523c58d4662f12e8f.jpg" />
<p><i>This costume gives the wearer the appearance of those tragic mortals whose will and mentality have been stolen by Molag Bal.</i></p> 
<p>The Mind-Shriven skin will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from August 12, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to August 15, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<h2>Crate</h2> 
<p><b>Nightfall Crate </b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/7ba4782f2150079d54abd24dd58646aa.jpg" />
<p><i>A mystery collection of Nightfall related items! </i></p> 
<p>Nightfall Crates will return to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from August 8, 2024 at 1PM EDT, to August 22, 2024 at 10AM EDT. </p> 
<p><b>Wraithtide Crate </b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/fe900d208a869d7a6f73c8f629c02a0d.jpg" />
<p><i>A mystery collection of Wraithtide related items! </i></p> 
<p>Wraithtide Crates will return to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from August 22, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to September 5, 2024 at 10AM EDT.</p> 
<h2>Events </h2> 
<p><b>Currency</b></p> 
<p><b>Event Tickets</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/0eca6e67f5bc52c1eb8932d18cb2e7ce.jpg" />
<p><i>A ticket used to purchase rare goods from The Impresario, Event Merchant. Curious as to what goods? Well, chat with her to see what she has to offer!</i></p> 
<p>Single Event Tickets will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time during the Whitestrike's Mayhem event, from July 25, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to August 6, 2024 at 10AM EDT. Event Tickets are also giftable to other players from within the Crown Store. </p> 
<h2>Furniture </h2> 
<p><b>Music Box, Ascension to the Ruby Throne</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/adb9213d228d6c35995e6a1e81a563e6.jpg" />
<p><i>When activated, plays the majestic music box composition "Ascension to the Ruby Throne."</i></p> 
<p>The new Music Box, Ascension to the Ruby Throne will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from August 1, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to August 8, 2024 at 10AM EDT.</p> 
<p><b>Music Box, Feast of All Flames</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/72309a88619fa9b3b9b67d17b6be1b57.jpg" />
<p><i>When activated, plays a music box arrangement of the playfully tumultuous "Feast of All Flames" composition.</i></p> 
<p>The Music Box, Feast of All Flames will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from August 5, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to August 12, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<p><b>Daedric Statue, Sanguine</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/cb1a9d3dbbbb1ba9227c1c943ccbb49f.jpg" />
<p><i>Add to the exuberant atmosphere of any gathering with this rose-bestrewn statue of Sanguine, the Daedric Prince of Revelry. Let drifts of petals caress bare skin. Draw eyes with a flash of crimson. Then showcase the statue's illusions all at once.</i></p> 
<p>The new Daedric Statue, Sanguine will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from August 8, 2024 at 1PM EDT, to August 15, 2024 at 10AM EDT.</p> 
<p><b>Statue, Vampiric Sovereign</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/d0b205487b589d0ad7ff11d0f543b3a2.jpg" />
<p><i>The vile enchantments placed upon this statue make it a grim reminder of a vampire's power. Whether cloaked in bats, imbued with dark energies, or wreathed in flame, weak-hearted mortals will never forget the sight of it.</i></p> 
<p>The Statue, Vampiric Sovereign will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from August 12, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to August 15, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<p><b>Statue, Prince of Ambition</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/b3b5299af89d669e3d26b7decfce4ecf.jpg" />
<p><i>Sweltering chaos accompanies this colossal statue of Mehrunes Dagon, the Prince of Destruction. Whether you prefer his smoldering heat, fiery gaze, blazing axe, or the full force of his inferno, this statue will bring sublime terror to any home.</i></p> 
<p>The Statue, Prince of Ambition will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from August 15, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to August 22, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<p><b>Furnishing Pack: Daedric Ambitions</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/5095f85e4dd08ee1a8ed76294058599a.jpg" />
<p><i>Build your own imposing edifices with these structural pieces and accessories. Will your enemies—and maybe even friends—quail at the results of your labors? Yes, yes, they will.</i></p> 
<p>The Furnishing Pack: Daedric Ambitions will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from August 15, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to August 22, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<h2>Houses</h2> 
<p><b>Potentate's Retreat</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/6916881ad81d58d3e7d41b971f4aea79.jpg" />
<p><i>Originally built by the Potentate Versidue-Shaie as a retreat from Senchal, this manor contains roomy spaces in which to entertain guests. A terraced area features a flooded aeonstone crater as well as luminescent flora transplanted from Moonlit Cove.</i></p> 
<p>Potentate's Retreat returns to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from August 1, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to August 15, 2024 at 10AM EDT. Furnished and unfurnished versions will be available.</p> 
<p><b>Zhan Khaj Crest</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/4ddbfe900fa21f23634c24e9e98a05fa.jpg" />
<p><i>Breezes carry verdant scents from the nearby jungle to caress the sand gardens in this former Desert Wind adeptorium. Though no longer a site of Khajiit practicing a dual-sword technique, this riverside location serves well as a meditative getaway.</i></p> 
<p>The new Zhan Khaj Crest will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from August 8, 2024 at 1PM EDT, to August 22, 2024 at 10AM EDT. Furnished and unfurnished versions will be available.</p> 
<p><b>Agony's Ascent</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/b4fd9757f03cdb88b108099788719557.jpg" />
<p><i>Cautioning whispers about these dominating spires convince the wary to avoid the place for fear of torture … or worse. Those with courage, though, might find the stalwart tower and commanding views make for an imposing Oblivion keep.</i></p> 
<p>Agony's Ascent returns to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from August 15, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to August 29, 2024 at 10AM EDT. Furnished and unfurnished versions will be available.</p> 
<p><b>Tel Galen</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/2c6bba03da581bc705f242fb7cb63c84.jpg" />
<p><i>Fulfill your fantasies of a fungal flat with this fabulous Telvanni wizard's tower, on a private island on Azura's Coast! Comes complete with grand foyer, workshop, suite, and tower chamber ideal for magical research.</i></p> 
<p>Tel Galen returns to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from August 29, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to September 12, 2024 at 10AM EDT. Furnished and unfurnished versions will be available.</p> 
<h2>Houseguests</h2> 
<p><b>Druid Ryvana</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/a879d1fc4a85b8b3f0e09695dd6433b2.jpg" />
<p><i>Mysterious and kind, Druid Ryvana welcomes the chance to teach others about the wisdom of the Stonelore Druids. What teachings has she for you? After adding Ryvana to your home, you can set her on a path, plus you and your visitors can speak with her.</i></p> 
<p>Druid Ryvana will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from August 1, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to August 5, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<p><b>Imperial Legionary Larina</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/74d1837462dc0e047cd8b05c46dcfeef.jpg" />
<p><i>A series of defeats in the Three Banners War led veteran Larina to take some leave to recuperate before her next battle in Cyrodiil. Will you give her a place to rest? After adding Larina to your home, you can set her on a path.</i></p> 
<p>The new Imperial Legionary Larina will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from August 8, 2024 at 1PM EDT, to August 15, 2024 at 10AM EDT.</p> 
<h2>Mounts</h2> 
<p><b>Manelord Nightmare Senche</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/f0ea0f9eefdcefcbecd79be74d9cc7af.jpg" />
<p><i>King of the Nightmare Pride, this night-black senche-tiger has burning paws and flames hissing from its face; rumor says Mehrunes Dagon is responsible.</i></p> 
<p>The Manelord Nightmare Senche mount will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from August 5, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to August 12, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<p><b>Seaghost Pillion Moose</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/25810e3808bc3c441ea1f50f745c56f7.jpg" />
<p><i>"I've always preferred moose to elk or horses. In battle they're more reliable, they're cussed strong, and for overland travel they can't be beat. Plus, their noses are just so soft!"—Yvon Serielle, Daggerfall</i></p> 
<p>The new Seaghost Pillion Moose mount will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from August 8, 2024 at 1PM EDT, to August 15, 2024 at 10AM EDT.</p> 
<p><b>Grudge-Rock Welwa</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/5b81d2cf23f46d0f1d748c235d3430e4.jpg" />
<p><i>These petulant welwas hail from Wrothgar and more than live up to their name. Hardened by their difficult landscape, the creatures delight in punishing their riders for the smallest slight, whether it's a late feeding or a slightly too-tight saddle.</i></p> 
<p>The new Grudge-Rock Welwa mount will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from August 12, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to August 15, 2024 at 10AM EDT.</p> 
<p><b>Dremnaken Wrathsteed</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/fb07b93f5991699e9db6d17bbd7707cd.jpg" />
<p><i>"Dremnaken are fearsome creatures with crushing footpads and jagged teeth that promise only pain. Anyone who can strap armor onto one's back and ride it into battle should be doubly feared. That's only logical."—Nororlie, Alinor Daedrology Society</i></p> 
<p>The Dremnaken Wrathsteed mount will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from August 15, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to August 22, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<p><b>Nightfall Sabre Cat</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/4b1d98787d933ce2facf4cb2d6f314c6.jpg" />
<p><i>The Reachmen of the upper Karth valley, who train them as mounts, swear that the Nightfall variant is sacred to the Daedric Prince Nocturnal.</i></p> 
<p>The Nightfall Sabre Cat mount will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from August 19, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to August 22, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<p><b>Midnight Cantor Senche-raht</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/53e15f480a0f347b81b3f63e0e7fe1a4.jpg" />
<p><i>After spending years expelling dro-m'Athra from Nirn, M'aar decided to follow a new path. Now they hope to explore as much of the Mundus as possible before venturing to the Gates of the Crossing.</i></p> 
<p>The Midnight Cantor Senche-raht mount will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from August 22, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to August 26, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<p><b>Rubyflare Torchnix</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/c63282a3306b5d566ea20e495cde0199.jpg" />
<p><i>"Legends claim the Erabenimsun tamed these luminous creatures after Ashu-Ammu rode the first nix-ox into battle. While it's strange to choose a steed whose glow gives away your position, some warriors delight in added danger before battle."—Murdyn Athren</i></p> 
<p>The Rubyflare Torchnix mount will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from August 29, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to September 2, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<h2>Personality</h2> 
<p><b>Swashbuckler</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/8dbd021d384eae911c4d85a6fd7d2b3d.jpg" />
<p><i>You've braved dangerous waters and seedy back-alleys. Now, on land or sea, your telltale swagger marks you as someone who's comfortable in all manner of deadly environments!</i></p> 
<p>The Swashbuckler personality will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from August 22, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to August 26, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<h2>Emote</h2> 
<p><b>Bright Moons Greeting</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/14c1746bb30877f4e4f22a9ba59ece6c.jpg" />
<p><i>Sweep your hands into a gesture revering the moons, Jone and Jode, with this Khajiiti greeting.</i></p> 
<p>The Bright Moons Greeting emote will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from August 26, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to August 29, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<h2>Pets</h2> 
<p><b>Mind-Shriven Cat</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/1ac9646781c675be1302d9fb5bd2a431.jpg" />
<p><i>"The Mind-Shriven usually have no concept of the self, but this feline appears to be as content with its nature as always. It seems that Molag Bal himself cannot enslave a cat."—Warlock Aldaale</i></p> 
<p>The Mind-Shriven Cat pet will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from August 12, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to August 15, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<p><b>Nightmare Firestalker Cub</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/b3aa13eb3eb75325f5b7baf3d89a623d.jpg" />
<p><i>Some may find the fiery cuteness of this horned cub unbearable, but you can handle it! Just watch out for those adorable little paws—they're hot as coals.</i></p> 
<p>The Nightmare Firestalker Cub pet will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from August 19, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to August 26, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<p><b>Nightmare Senche Cub</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/a7eb35e8e8888250dea7da950912ba28.jpg" />
<p><i>Despite the fact that this night-black senche-tiger cub has burning paws and flaming eyes, it's so adorable it might be a nightmare you never want to awaken from!</i></p> 
<p>The Nightmare Senche Cub pet will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from August 26, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to September 2, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p>From houseguests and gowns to Telvanni towers and swashbuckling swagger, there's a bit of everything in this month's showcase. Have an idea as to which goodies you'll want to add to your collection? Be sure to stock up on crowns by heading over to the <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/crowns">Buy Crowns page</a> beforehand. What new or returning item(s) are you most excited to pick up this month? Let us know via <a name="_Hlk159602221"></a><a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>. </p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Crown Store</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/ddcaf7f77872a9ecc2b541e6fba0f114.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Anniversary Spotlight—Claim Red-Hot Rewards Within the Portals of Oblivion]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66437</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66437</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A fiery host of rewards (voted for by you, the community) await those willing to clash with the minions of Mehrunes Dagon during the Portals of Oblivion Anniversary Spotlight.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/0966c53412f65c163d7a893c5dc0eef6.jpg" /><p><i>A fiery host of rewards (voted for by you, the community) await those willing to clash with the minions of Mehrunes Dagon during the Portals of Oblivion Anniversary Spotlight.</i></p> 
<h2>August's Red-Hot Rewards</h2> 
<p>Our 10-Year Anniversary spotlights continue with the Portals of Oblivion, challenging you to invade Mehrunes Dagon's realm of destruction. Starting August 5 at 10AM EDT and running until September 3 at 10AM EDT, if you have unlocked either the <b>Blackwood Portal Punisher</b> or <b>Deadlands Portal Punisher</b> achievement, you can claim the Flame Atronach Pony Guar pet for <b>free</b> from the in-game Crown Store. </p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/0838b38218bd134cf139a12dc99a4037.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>The Flame Atronach Pony Guar pet</i></p> 
<p>To unlock either one of these achievements, you must enter 10 <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/60051">Oblivion Portals</a> in the zone and destroy the antecedent catalyst devices within. Once you have earned either the Blackwood or Deadlands Portal Punisher achievement, you can claim the free pet from the Crown Store.</p> 
<p>Even better, unlock the <b>Oblivion Obliterator achievement</b> by defeating all the bosses found within Oblivion Portals and you can also claim the new Firebelly Shalk pet from the Crown Store as a bonus reward.</p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/0f317dc677b420a280f45160eddf7610.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>The new Firebelly Shalk pet</i></p> 
<p>Be warned, the minions of Mehrunes Dagon are some of the most dangerous in Oblivion, and you may wish to recruit your strongest allies for this venture—good luck!</p> 
<h2>Devilish Daily Rewards</h2> 
<p>In addition to the pets you can earn via the portal achievements, the Flame Atronach Senche-Jaguar pet has also been added to Augusts Daily Login Rewards. Simply log in twice during the month of August to claim it!</p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/9b42308d823da417d490c558796270af.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>The Flame Atronach Senche-Jaguar pet</i></p> 
<h2>Endeavor to Defeat Dagon</h2> 
<p>Finally, keep an eye out for special Endeavors during the month of August. This includes a new Weekly Endeavor that challenges you to complete 10 Oblivion Portals and daily portal-themed Endeavors that reward a larger-than-usual number of Seals. </p> 
<h2>The Forces of Oblivion Await</h2> 
<p>Join us in continuing the massive 10-Year Anniversary Celebration by venturing into the realm of Mehrunes Dagon and saving the Imperial province of Blackwood. Are you prepared to face the Daedra of the Deadlands this August? Let us know via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>—have fun!</p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>10th Anniversary</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/0966c53412f65c163d7a893c5dc0eef6.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Daily Login Rewards—August 2024]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66439</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66439</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Check out some of the items and collectibles you can claim simply by logging in to The Elder Scrolls Online during August 2024!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/23ffa717e750af65592d64122ca58250.jpg" /><p><i>Check out some of the items and collectibles you can claim simply by logging in to The Elder Scrolls Online during August 2024!</i></p> 
<p>A new month is upon us, and that means new rewards for you to claim throughout August! Curious about how Daily Login Rewards work? Check out <a href="https://help.elderscrollsonline.com/#en/answer/41950">this help article</a> to discover all you need to know and take a peek at some of the highlights you can enjoy throughout August 2024 below!</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Flame Atronach Senche-Jaguar—Day 2</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/058b29a6195b74a12007a147704e4675.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Be careful when cuddling this fiery fellow!</i></p> 
<p>When asked about flame atronachs, many may think of destruction and ruin, while some may even bring up Mehrunes Dagon's realm of the Deadlands. But never fear—this fiery beast can become a fierce partner in your adventures. You can claim the Flame Atronach Senche-Jaguar by logging in twice this month, which features <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66437">other surprises</a> from Dagon's Oblivion realm.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Face Marking: Rose of Tamriel—Day 7</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/6aabccfdeec3be6fb37316d57a434b75.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Let your beauty bloom</i></p> 
<p>You'll love how you look with this gorgeous face marking. Unlock the Rose of Tamriel face marking after seven days of logins this month.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Luminous Ink—Days 10-13</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/f94e25f6524a6566850f985dff57ca5b.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Voluminous amounts of Luminous Ink</i></p> 
<p>Luminous Ink is a key resource for the <i>Gold Road </i>Chapter's Scribing system. Whether you want it for your own Scribing efforts or to trade to other players, you receive three Luminous Ink each day when you log in on days 10-13, potentially earning 12 Luminous Ink in total.</p> 
<p><b><br></b></p><p><b>Body Marking: Rose of Tamriel—Day 14</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/daa62402930321b8a9739b6075227137.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Turn heads with this body tattoo</i></p> 
<p>Be the center of attention with these stunning body markings. Are they devotions to Dibella, a statement of self-love and fulfillment, or just too striking not to wear? You tell us—and be sure to claim them on your fourteenth login this month!</p><p><br></p> 
<p>These and more rewards await while logging in this month. To see the full list, venture into the game on August 1 (and claim the first one while you're there). Are you eager to claim August 2024's in-game Daily Login Rewards? Don't forget, August continues the 10-Year Anniversary Celebration fun with <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66437">an all-new spotlight, too</a>. Let us know what you think via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>. </p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Daily Rewards</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/23ffa717e750af65592d64122ca58250.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[QuakeCon Livestream Trial Competition]]></title>
            <link>https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/662970/quakecon-livestream-trial-competition</link>
            <guid>https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/662970/quakecon-livestream-trial-competition</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 19:18:08 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://us.v-cdn.net/5020507/uploads/editor/mz/wkpkq7xex2sb.jpg"><br><span style="text-decoration: line-through;">We're looking for score-pushing Trials teams for this year's QuakeCon livestream! Sign up for a chance to compete from the comfort of your home and win some awesome prizes, including a custom banner, year of ESO+, 14k Crowns, and more! Sign up 🔗: <a href="https://woobox.com/puswca?linkId=100000275687342">https://beth.games/4dcw7p3</a></span><br>
Update: All slots have filled up and we have closed the form. Thanks for your interest!<br>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>Forum</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Defeat Your Rivals & Earn Bonus Rewards During the Whitestrake's Mayhem Event!]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66367</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66367</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Go toe-to-toe with your fellow players across Cyrodiil, the Imperial City, and Battlegrounds all while collecting exciting in-game rewards during the Whitestrake's Mayhem PvP event!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/b26b7108bae413a9c1cebbd2d7fa75b1.jpg" /><p><i>Go toe-to-toe with your fellow players across Cyrodiil, the Imperial City, and Battlegrounds all while collecting exciting in-game rewards during the Whitestrake's Mayhem PvP event!</i></p> 
<h2>Mayhem Is On the Rise</h2> 
<p>The Whitestrake's Mayhem event makes its grand return to Tamriel next Thursday, July 25 at 10AM EDT, and runs until August 6 at 10AM EDT. Throughout the event, you will benefit from a 100% bonus to Alliance Point, XP, and Tel Var Stone gain. In addition, you can earn unique goodies by participating in <i>ESO</i>'s PvP game modes.</p> 
<p>Ready to clash against other adventurers on the battlefield? Simply follow the steps below:</p> 
<ol><li>Head over to the in-game Crown Store and receive the “Details on the Whitestrake's Mayhem" quest</li><li>Travel to your Alliance War faction's main gate in Cyrodiil using the Alliance War menu or a Battlegrounds camp outside major cities</li><ol><li>You do not need to travel to Cyrodiil to start the event</li></ol><li>Locate the NPC named “Predicant Maera" and continue the quest</li><ol><li>Note that if you've previously completed the quest, you won't need to do it again</li></ol><li>Complete the quest to receive a complimentary Pelinal's Boon Box</li></ol>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/dcf9721d1b9361d959ce7db76d5c1dcc.jpg" />
<p>One key difference from previous years' events is that you no longer need to obtain or use the Scroll of Pelinal's Ferocity to benefit from the 100% buff to Alliance Point, XP, and Tel Var Stone gains. These bonuses are now shared passively to adventurers skirmishing throughout Cyrodiil, the Imperial City, and Battlegrounds. As a result, there is no longer a method to pick up the Scroll of Pelinal's Ferocity anywhere in-game, and those who already own the item will now notice it no longer offers any functionality.</p> 
<h2>Battle for Bonus Rewards</h2> 
<p>While participating in the Whitestrake's Mayhem in-game event, you can amass a collection of bonus in-game goodies for your heroic efforts. </p> 
<p><b>NEW—Ayleid Lich Outfit Style Armor</b></p> 
<p>Dominate both the living and the dead while donning the Ayleid Lich Armor, dropped in Pelinal's Boon Boxes.</p> 
<p><b>Pelinal's Boon Boxes</b></p> 
<p>You can earn Pelinal's Boon Boxes as rewards from the following activities throughout the event:</p> 
<ul><li>Battlegrounds quests from Battlemaster Rivyn</li><li>Scouting, Battle, Warfront, and Conquest Missions</li><li>Elder Scroll capture and recapture quests</li><li>Town quests in Vlastarus, Bruma, Cropsford, Cheydinhal, and Chorrol</li><li>Imperial City daily quests</li></ul> 
<p>Whenever you open a Pelinal's Boon Box, you have the chance to receive the following items:</p> 
<ul><li>Parcel of Tel Var Stones</li><li>Cyrodiil repair kit</li><li>Soul Gems</li><li><b>ONE</b> of the following:</li><ul><li>Alchemy Ingredients </li><li>Style item for your Alliance's armor style </li><li>Style item for Akaviri armor style </li><li>Daedric siege weapon </li><li>Whitestrake's Mayhem book furnishing</li><li>Forward Camp for your Alliance</li><li>Chapter of your Alliance's armor motif</li><ul><li>There is a small chance that the full book may drop instead of a single chapter</li></ul><li>Prismatic Runestone </li><li>Chapter for the Akaviri armor motif</li><ul><li>There is a small chance that the full book may drop instead of a single chapter</li></ul><li>Small chance to receive one or two fragments of the Alliance Breton Terrier pet</li></ul><li>Small chance to receive a Transmute Geode</li><li>Very small chance to receive an unbound, tradeable Ayleid Lich Armor Style Page</li><ul><li>A Dovah's Du'ul Style Page may drop instead if you've already earned the Ayleid Lich Armor Style Page</li></ul></ul>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/08b6d9726209e1d787a6a20bff1014ec.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>The Ayleid Lich Armor Style</i></p> 
<p><b>Bonus Resources &amp; The Golden</b></p> 
<p>Are you a crafter? Keep a keen eye out as you travel from battle to battle as harvesting nodes in Cryodiil will yield additional resources throughout the event. </p> 
<p>Additionally, the merchant Adhazabi “The Golden” Aba-daro will offer various CP160 jewelry from Cyrodiil item sets. Legendary necklaces will be available during the first weekend of Whitestrake's Mayhem and legendary rings from the same sets will be offered during the second. </p> 
<p>Throughout the celebration, The Golden will not offer Monster Masks and all purchases in her shop will require Alliance Points. Contrary to her title, she will <b>not</b> accept gold.</p> 
<h2>The Impresario &amp; Event Tickets</h2> 
<p>During Whitestrake's Mayhem, up to three Event Tickets can be earned each day by completing the following activities:</p> 
<ul><li>Two Event Tickets from the first Cyrodiil or Battlegrounds daily quest </li><ul><li>This includes Bounty Board quests, a Town Daily, the Conquest Board quests, or the daily Battlegrounds quest</li></ul><li>One Event Ticket from an Imperial City District daily quest</li></ul> 
<p>You can obtain a total of <b>39</b> Event Tickets by the event's end. Remember: you can only hold up to 12 Event Tickets at one time. Be sure to stop by the Impresario's market now and again to clear the way to collect more Tickets!</p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/d9ed9e8b42f7fc418866d6874d82db40.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Acquire the Anchorborn Welwa's first fragment</i></p> 
<p>Here's what the Impresario is offering during this event:</p> 
<ul><li>All three Molag Bal Illusion Imp pet fragments</li><ul><li>Anchor Chain Fragment</li><li>Dark Anchor Pinion</li><li>Effigy of the Dominator</li></ul><li>The first Anchorborn Welwa mount fragment </li><ul><li>Bizarre Daedric Meat</li></ul><li>Bag of Veteran's Glory (You can only hold one bag at a time. Be sure to collect your rewards from within before purchasing another!)</li><ul><li>Group Repair Kit</li><li>Legion Zero Style Pages</li><li>Standard-Bearer Emotes</li><li>Second Legion Style Pages</li><li>Standard-Bearer Staves and Shields </li><li>Legion Zero Vigiles Pages</li><li>Ebonsteel Knight Armor Pages</li><li>Black Drake Clanwrap Style Pages</li><li>Black Drake Warpaint Face and Body Markings</li><li>Battle-Scared Body and Face Markings</li><li>House Dufort Banneret Style Pages</li><li>Tools of Domination Weapon Style Pages</li><li>Gloamsedge Outfit Style Pages</li><ul><li>Bound Ayleid Lich Armor Style Pages </li><li>Group Repair Kits </li><li>Companion Guild Commendations </li></ul></ul></ul> 
<p>Additionally, the Impresario's Assistant will offer the following items which you can acquire with your tickets:</p> 
<ul><li>All three Unstable Morpholith pet Fragments</li><li>All three Soulfire Dragon Illusion pet Fragments </li><li>All three Deadlands Firewalker personality Fragments </li><li>All three Aurelic Quasigriff mount Fragments </li></ul>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/06/dc0df2fd14d1a13961e0c2f767083484.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Give these Indriks a new home</i></p> 
<p>And lastly, Nenulaure at the Indrik Vendor's shop will include updated offerings that players can purchase with Event Tickets:</p> 
<ul><li>Onyx Indrik Berries</li><li>Onyx Indrik pet</li><li>Mossheart Indrik Berries </li><li>Mossheart Indrik pet</li></ul> 
<h2>Victory and Glory Awaits!</h2> 
<p>It's time to test your mettle against fellow champions while earning tantalizing rewards as proof of your glory! Are you excited to charge onto the battlefield and clash against mighty warriors during this anarchic event period? Let us know via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>. </p> 
<p><i>The Whitestrake's Mayhem in-game event begins Thursday, July 25 at 10AM EDT, and runs until Tuesday, August 6 at 10AM EDT.</i></p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Events</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/b26b7108bae413a9c1cebbd2d7fa75b1.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Missing Jubilee Steed Issue - Console Servers (June 18)]]></title>
            <link>https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/660775/missing-jubilee-steed-issue-console-servers-june-18</link>
            <guid>https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/660775/missing-jubilee-steed-issue-console-servers-june-18</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 12:56:10 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[We are currently investigating an issue that emerged after the Gold Road and Update 42 maintenance on Xbox and PlayStation servers where some players are missing the Jubilee Steed after previously earning it during this year's Anniversary Jubilee event in April. Players who are affected by this will also see their "Jubilee Confetti Conveyor" achievement progress reset to zero. This is occurring on the Xbox and PlayStation servers.<br><br>
While investigations are ongoing, we will ensure that any players affected by this issue get the Jubilee Steed back. We do not need affected players to submit a Support Ticket at this time. We will follow up here and in <a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/660761/jubilee-mount-missing-ps5">this discussion thread</a> as we have more information to share.<br><br>
Thank you!,Hi everyone! We have identified the issue on Xbox and PlayStation servers and are working on a fix. We plan to push this fix during the next console incremental patch, tentatively scheduled for Wednesday, July 10. Here's what you need to know, once the fix is live:
<ul><li>If you had the Jubilee Steed and completed the "Jubilee Confetti Conveyor" achievement before, you will have the mount back and your achievement will once again be complete.</li>
<li>If you had <i>partial</i> progress towards the "Jubilee Confetti Conveyor" achievement completion, we will bump you back to where you were before the Update 42 launch on consoles.</li>
<li>If you use Jubilee Confetti Packs before the fix goes live, you will lose that progress toward the "Jubilee Confetti Conveyor" achievement when it does. We encourage you not to use any additional Jubilee Confetti Packs until after the fix is live on July 10.</li>
</ul>
Players affected by this issue do not need to submit a Support Ticket. Thank you all for your patience.,Hi All. We're updating to note that this issue has been resolved with today's patch. You should be able to use your Jubilee Steed Mount once again. Thanks again for your patience while resolving this issue.]]></content:encoded>
            <category>Forum</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Update 43 Is Now Available on the PC/Mac Public Test Server]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66365</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66365</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Test out new quality-of-life features, including an all-new system to tour player homes across Tamriel, in the Update 43 base-game patch on the PC/Mac Public Test Server!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/d0e7f87c2db24925ffee9612c3be11d3.jpg" /><p><i>Test out new quality-of-life features, including an all-new system to tour player homes across Tamriel, in the Update 43 base-game patch on the PC/Mac Public Test Server!</i></p> 
<p>Update 43 is ready for your testing and feedback! The Public Test Server (PTS) has now been updated to include Update 43, giving you access to Home Tours, additions to Infinite Archive, and more. To access the PTS, go to the Settings menu within the PC/Mac <i>ESO</i> launcher by toggling the “Show Public Test Environment” option. You can then download and access the game client. Don't forget to leave feedback and report any bugs you come across by typing “/feedback” or “/bug” in chat.</p> 
<p>If you want to learn about the features coming in Update 43 or anything else to do with the patch, be sure to check out our recent <a href="https://www.twitch.tv/videos/2188253758">preview livestream</a> and <a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/662078/">PTS Patch Notes</a> on the <i>ESO</i> forums.</p> 
<p>Are you excited to see all the improvements in Update 43? Let us know via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>. </p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Community</category>
            <category>Update 43</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/d0e7f87c2db24925ffee9612c3be11d3.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Update 43 Preview—Tour ESO's Upcoming Base-Game Features & Improvements]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66331</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66331</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn about Home Tours, updates to the Infinite Archive, and more with our sneak peek at Update 43!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/a485860acb4ef7db7339db29ead9f8ec.jpg" /><p><i>Learn about Home Tours, updates to the Infinite Archive, and more with our sneak peek at Update 43!</i></p> 
<p>The Update 43 base-game patch is set to bring a ton of great features and improvements to all <i>ESO</i> players,<b> completely free of charge</b>, on August 19 for PC/Mac and September 4 for Xbox and PlayStation consoles. </p> 
<p>Eager to check it out? You can test out the new update for yourself on the PC/Mac Public Test Server early next week—keep an eye out for the announcement blog! If you missed the <a href="https://www.twitch.tv/videos/2188253758">preview livestream</a>, or just want more details, check out what's coming below. </p> 
<h2>Home Tours</h2> 
<p>One of the year's most anticipated new features for Tamriel's housing enthusiasts is Home Tours, a new entry in the Activity Finder that shares and showcases listed player homes. </p> 
<p>With Home Tours, you can search for homes owned and decorated by another player you know by searching for their UserID. You can also filter through other criteria like owner-applied labels for theme, such as “Libraries” or “Strongholds.” Of course, the creativity of many players defies such simple categorization, so if you're interested in seeing all sorts of homes or in viewing the most popular creations, you can browse the top player homes in the Recommended tab of Home Tours. Whatever way you search, friends and guildmates will be specially tagged in the feed for easy recognition. </p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/1fb5d9343a4564711c639ddeada956f3.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Tour Tamriel together!</i></p> 
<p>When you find a home that really impresses you, you can recommend it to others, as well as favorite it for yourself to visit later. You can even favorite homes you visit through other means, regardless of whether they are listed for Home Tours. There's a weekly limit on how many homes you can recommend, but no limit on how many you can visit and enjoy. Your own home may be featured as a recommended home in the Activity Finder if it becomes popular enough! </p> 
<h2>Infinite Archive Update</h2> 
<p>Update 43 also adds more depth to the Infinite Archive in the form of new maps, enemies, Verses and Visions, and updated loot, including new class item sets! This includes new hazard stages where the Archive itself presents a danger and a wider pool of foes to battle in maligraphic form. </p> 
<p>Helping you tackle these new challenges are eight additional Verses and 10 additional Visions. For example, you can use the new Phalanx verse to call on ghostly soldiers to form a wall of defenders, collect the new Necrotic Vision set to unlock an Undead Avatar transformation that allows you to empower yourself with each defeated enemy, and more. You can also earn potent new consumable items that unlock a guaranteed transformation verse like the Undead Avatar, but getting them will not be easy!</p> 
<p>Once you return to the Index with your hard-won Archival Fortunes, you can spend them on new rewards, whether as part of Filer Ool's rotating stock or purchased from new arrival Filer Brax, who stocks all gear from the class item sets. Filer Brax's inventory isn't limited to the existing seven sets from the Archive's launch, but also includes new sets like the gruesome Corpseburster set for Necromancers that detonates corpses your skills consume. <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/64891">As before</a>, each of these sets is themed around a specific class skill line.</p> 
<h2>Quality of Life Improvements</h2> 
<p>The above new features and additions aren't the only focus of Update 43. Several smaller improvements included in Update 43 are aimed at making your time in Tamriel easier and more enjoyable. </p> 
<p>For example, item curation, the system that prevents duplicate item drops within a set while you are still filling it out in Collections, expands to cover new sources. These include weekly Trial rewards, offerings from Imperial City vendors, and the Dungeon-specific reward chests for monster sets available for Undaunted Keys from Glirion the Redbeard, Maj-al Ragath, and Urgarlag Chief-bane at the Undaunted Enclaves. </p> 
<p>The update also includes improvements to mount previews in the Crown Store, allowing you to preview and replay animations such as summoning or rearing up without needing to purchase a mount. Finally, many further smaller changes and bug fixes are included in Update 43. For example, Guild Trader and Guild Bank interfaces remember the last player Guild you interacted with in a play session.</p> 
<p>Update 43 brings a host of new features, improvements, and fixes to Tamriel's adventurers, and you can test them out for yourself on PTS next week. Keep an eye out for those patch notes, too! Are you excited for the changes coming in the next base-game patch? Let us know via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>. </p> 
<p><i>The Update 43 base-game patch arrives on August 19 for PC/Mac and September 4 for Xbox and PlayStation consoles. </i></p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Community</category>
            <category>Update 43</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/a485860acb4ef7db7339db29ead9f8ec.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Crown Store Showcase—July 2024]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66325</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66325</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Discover the flashy new goodies you can pick up from the Crown Store this July as you continue your adventures throughout West Weald and beyond.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/787b7aa7194cdb76a23c768cf1aa0a60.jpg" /><p><i>Discover the flashy new goodies you can pick up from the Crown Store this July as you continue your adventures throughout West Weald and beyond.</i></p> 
<p>Take a peek at all the upcoming items arriving to the in-game Crown Store during July 2024! Be sure to also head over to the <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/crownstore">Crown Store page</a> to check out the currently available items, too. One or more of these goodies catch your eye? Then drop by the <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/buycrowns">Buy Crowns page</a> and secure however many crowns you need! Certain items and offers will be available for a limited time only, so be sure to read their details below and don't miss out.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>ESO Plus Deals</h2> 
<p>All ESO Plus™ members have access to a monthly selection of exclusive deals and items. You can find more information about them in <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/54825">this article</a>.</p> 
<p><b>Exclusive Free Items</b></p> 
<p><b>Statuette: Auriel of Garlas Agea</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/58405cc5e04d4746eceb6be58469a527.jpg" />
<p><i>A miniature statue of Auriel, King of the Aldmer. Based on the storied effigy of the same name in the ruins of Garlas Agea along the Gold Coast.</i></p> 
<p>The Statuette: Auriel of Garlas Agea will be available in the Crown Store FREE, exclusively to ESO Plus Members on all platforms for a limited time, from July 29, 2024 at 10 AM EDT, to August 29, 2024 at 10 AM EDT.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Crown Gem and Seals of Endeavor Items</h2> 
<p><b>Vampiric Soulrazer Knight</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/518409144f597fb140debea2dcda5f67.jpg" />
<p><i>The Soulrazer Knights of High Isle were intimidating enough on their own—before a vampire twisted that power to suit their needs. Now, you too can burn with a glorious, bloody purpose.</i></p> 
<p>The Vampiric Soulrazer Knight polymorph will be available for Crown Gems and Seals of Endeavor on all platforms for a limited time, from July 11 to July 25, 2024 at 10AM EDT.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Legion Zero Charger</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/23cd1dca99c3c39fea333b36eadb33fa.jpg" />
<p><i>Battlemages within the perfidious Legion Zero conjure these powerful warhorses out of thin air using forbidden Daedric magic. The sight of this otherworldly charger inspires both fear and awe on the battlelines.</i></p> 
<p>The Legion Zero Charger mount will be available for Crown Gems and Seals of Endeavor on all platforms for a limited time, from July 25 to August 1, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Crafting</h2> 
<p><b>Crown Crafting Motif: Ra Gada Style</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/636aa986fcde981b645468f9965bb6b4.jpg" />
<p><i>The Ra Gada or “Warrior Wave" of settlers from Yokuda actually took place in the First Era's ninth century. The second, or “Tavan" wave, revered holy Tava, Lady of the Air. Thus the Tavans' arms and armor are replete with bird imagery, which makes for a very distinctive crafting style. Use to learn the Ra Gada crafting style. Also teaches the equivalent Ra Gada Outfit Styles.</i></p> 
<p>The Crown Crafting Motif: Ra Gada Style will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from July 25, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to August 1, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item. Motif chapters, and very rarely the complete book, have a chance to drop from Focus Points (Group Events), and very rarely found by looting treasure chests or defeating Delve and World Bosses in Craglorn.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Outfit Style</b></p> 
<p><b>Balorgh Arms Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/b8e062d07f699fc8a434bfb834c01435.jpg" />
<p><i> The mighty Balorgh fell due to your skill. Commemorate this victory—alter your weapon's appearance to match the Undaunted Balorgh awards by using this complete set of Outfit styles.</i></p> 
<p>The Balorgh Arms Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from July 1, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to July 8, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item. The matching mask page will have a small chance to drop from Balorgh from veteran March of Sacrifices. The matching shoulder page can be purchased from Urgarlag Chief-bane for 50 undaunted keys, or has a chance of dropping from Urgarlag's Mystery Coffer for 1 key. Having the achievement “Hircine's Champion” increases the drop chances of both items.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>The Blind Arms Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/2f74b4ccec46b741e0cf688d526a1481.jpg" />
<p><i>Fa-Nuit-Hen seeks champions to defeat the Blind Path cultists that have invaded Bedlam Veil. Perhaps you seek more visible signs of your victories than glory? Alter your weapon's appearance to match The Blind Weapons by using this complete set of The Blind Outfit styles.</i></p> 
<p>The new Blind Arms Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from July 3, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to July 25, at 10AM EDT. The matching mask page will have a small chance to drop from The Blind from veteran Bedlam Veil. The matching shoulder page can be purchased from Urgarlag Chief-bane for 50 undaunted keys, or has a chance of dropping from Urgarlag's Mystery Coffer for 1 key. Having the achievement “Lithe and Clever” increases the drop chances of both items.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Elder Scrolls Artifact: Skull of Corruption</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/2145c0fe2ef58549b749dfbd131478c9.jpg" />
<p><i>Alter your staff's Outfit style with a replica of the Skull of Corruption Elder Scrolls Artifact, the signature weapon of the Daedric Prince Vaermina.</i></p> 
<p>The Elder Scrolls Artifact: Skull of Corruption will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from July 11, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to July 18, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Ebonsteel Knight Arms Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/8ab9fae2381269e7b502048f5b68cac7.jpg" />
<p><i>Gather your gear and ready yourselves for mayhem! Alter your weapon's appearance by using this complete set of Ebonsteel Knight Outfit styles.</i></p> 
<p>The new Ebonsteel Knight Arms Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from July 11, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to July 25, 2024 at 10AM EDT. Matching armor pages will have a small chance to drop from the Bag of Veteran's Glory during Whitestrake's Mayhem. Bound versions of the armor pages can be purchased from the Impresario for 5 Event Tickets each during the event.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Vykosa Arms Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/6f45ac80ababb426b069fe4c992f5ba9.jpg" />
<p><i> Legends claim that Vykosa, Khajiit huntress and Werewolf lord, was among the first turned by Hircine. Does that make you eager to face her in combat? Regardless, you can alter your weapon's appearance to match the Undaunted Vykosa awards by using this complete set of Outfit styles.</i></p> 
<p>The Vykosa Arms Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from July 15, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to July 22, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item. The matching mask page will have a small chance to drop from Vykosa the Ascendant from veteran Moon Hunter Keep. The matching shoulder page can be purchased from Urgarlag Chief-bane for 50 undaunted keys, or has a chance of dropping from Urgarlag's Mystery Coffer for 1 key. Having the achievement “The Alpha Predator” increases the drop chances of both items.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Stormfist Arms Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/c69772342bae9995db7fb6f5603c6bb7.jpg" />
<p><i> Of course you vanquished the storm atronach known as Stormfist. Now celebrate your victory by altering your weapon's appearance to match the Undaunted Stormfist awards with this complete set of Outfit styles.</i></p> 
<p>The Stormfist Arms Pack will return to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from July 22, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to July 25, 2024 at 10AM EDT. The matching mask page will have a small chance to drop from Stormreeve Neidir from veteran Tempest Island. The matching shoulder page can be purchased from Glirion the Redbeard for 50 undaunted keys, or has a chance of dropping from Glirion's Mystery Coffer for 1 key. Having the achievement “Burial at Sea” increases the drop chances of both items.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Khenarthi's Pride Armor Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/458fc8391eda1073a476ad81b7579c30.jpg" />
<p><i>Blessed are those who don the trappings of the Wind God! Alter your armor's appearance by using this complete set of Khenarthi's Pride Outfit styles.</i></p> 
<p>The Khenarthi's Pride Armor Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from July 25, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to August 1, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Ayleid Lich Arms Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/a4f7834e17821e1176620e2cf80de028.jpg" />
<p><i>Vastarie writes that “... like Mannimarco, liches of Ayleid provenance crave power as a starving creature hopes for its next meal.” Alter your weapon's appearance to match the Ayleid Lich Weapons by using this complete set of Ayleid Lich Outfit styles.</i></p> 
<p>The new Ayleid Lich Arms Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from July 25, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to August 6, 2024 at 10AM EDT. Matching armor pages will have a small chance to drop from Pelinal's Boon Box. Bound versions of the armor pages can be purchased from the Impresario for 5 Event Tickets each during the event.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Adornment</h2> 
<p><b>Adorable Assassin</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/e498b302980fefa516abdf0a06f919da.jpg" />
<p><i>Knock 'em dead with this casual hairstyle popularized by the Dark Elf assassins of Morrowind.</i></p> 
<p>The Adorable Assassin adornment will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from July 18, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to July 25, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Anequine Oasis Eyes</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/e39adb496d7d1e0281155231b810956f.jpg" />
<p><i>"Though many dispute whether Khenarthi, S'rendarr, or another spirit grants these jade-green eyes to blessed individuals, all agree on one thing: Those who discover and share the location of an oasis to those in need earn them."—Sulema, Initiate Scholar</i></p> 
<p>The Anequine Oasis Eyes adornment will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from July 18, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to July 25, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Whitestrake's Mayhem Crowns</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/4e176f708348208700eedba17a843b64.jpg" />
<p><i>This bundle includes all three Imperial crowns celebrating the Whitestrake's Mayhem event: the Circlet, the Coronet, and the Diadem.</i></p> 
<p>The Whitestrake's Mayhem Crowns adornment will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from July 25, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to August 1, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Wardrobe</h2> 
<p><b>Moth Priest</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/7d7fba29fd9fc536bb423bfc8d412999.jpg" />
<p><i>"The priests of the Ancestor Moth are devoted to veneration of those who came before us, for the wisdom of the ancestors can sing the future into the present. As such, we alone have the privilege of interpreting the Elder Scrolls."—Sister Terran Arminus</i></p> 
<p>The Moth Priest costume will return to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from July 1, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to July 8, 2024 at 10AM EDT.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Naryu's Morag Tong Costume Bundle</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/bc560c280f253bf2991f819ed5d89814.jpg" />
<p><i>Naryu Virian the Morag Tong assassin is nothing if not practical. Her functional, low-profile leather armor provides vital protection without compromising her agile acrobatics, and her pair of Morag Tong-style goggles keeps blood out of her eyes.</i></p> 
<p>The Naryu's Morag Tong Costume Bundle will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from July 18, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to July 25, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Star-Made Wolfshead </b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/4a6f3a99ea812a535535066312f344bc.jpg" />
<p><i>Even if your background isn't Imperial, if you admire history's greatest warriors, you'll want to honor Pelinal Whitestrake with this costume from Whitestrake's Mayhem, the celebration that commemorates his deeds. </i></p> 
<p>The Star-Made Wolfshead will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from July 25, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to August 1, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Jakarn's Ensemble</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/0ccb76f0335104df1373adc1f99df235.jpg" />
<p><i>Jakarn is rugged, practical, and dashing. Dressing like him ensures that you never look like you're trying too hard. His well-tailored clothes always fetch the eyes of tavern beauties and never chafe when riding a stallion into the sunset.</i></p> 
<p>The Jakarn's Ensemble will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from July 29, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to August 5, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Skins</h2> 
<p><b>Shivering Isles Anointment</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/6c70a1e6064dd81a4d9525afd44f32bd.jpg" />
<p><i>Butterflies. Glowing pink eyes. The Shivering Isles calls to you. Will you fight the call or bend the knee to the Mad God?</i></p> 
<p>The Shivering Isles Anointment skin will return to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from July 1, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to July 8, at 10AM EDT.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Ebony Epidermis</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/98203ead49bb4bec7a9db569ab8fabb0.jpg" />
<p><i>Never trust an alchemist with a Daedric scroll—you might end up with skin that's the color and hardness of Ebony! Unless you think that's a good idea, of course.</i></p> 
<p>The Ebony Epidermis skin will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from July 22, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to July 29, at 10AM EDT.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<h2>Crate</h2> 
<p><b>Dark Chivalry Crate </b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/5e7ebfecdd1dacf7c7eda327c820cfc5.jpg" />
<p><i>A mystery collection of Dark Chivalry related items! </i></p> 
<p>Dark Chivalry Crates will return to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from July 11, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to July 25, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount when purchasing the ×15 Crate bundle of this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Events </h2> 
<p><b>Currency</b></p> 
<p><b>Event Tickets</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2022/01/d80129d699abe5116dbb4fb22c2d4b5b.jpg" />
<p><i> A ticket used to purchase rare goods from The Impresario, Event Merchant. Curious as to what goods? Well, chat with her to see what she has to offer!</i></p> 
<p>Single Event Tickets will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time during the Whitestrike's Mayhem event, from July 25, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to August 6, 2024 at 10AM EDT. Event Tickets are also giftable to other players from within the Crown Store.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<h2>Furniture </h2> 
<p><b>Furnishing Pack: Coldharbour Arcanaeum</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/10ab677077e466834478662b6bbc367a.jpg" />
<p><i>A selection of furnishings for the true connoisseur of Molag Bal's darkest secrets. Includes a tear in the fabric of reality itself, perfect for impressing guests (voluntary or otherwise).</i></p> 
<p>The Furnishing Pack: Coldharbour Arcanaeum will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from July 3, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to July 18, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Furnishing Pack: Azura</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/1b4cb9316b387b1a560c20712b086114.jpg" />
<p><i>Furnishings associated with the Daedric Prince Azura.</i></p> 
<p>The Furnishing Pack: Azura will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from July 18, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to July 25, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Target Serpent's Image, Trial</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/0ecb4feb78dd75c3f53bb6abbd91957b.jpg" />
<p><i>This is a large house item. This may be attacked and, when destroyed, will regenerate. This creature is equivalent to a veteran trial boss. Its abilities include granting a resource-restoring synergy opportunity, performance buffs, and self debuffs.</i></p> 
<p>The new Target Serpent's Image, Trial will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from July 18, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to August 1, 2024 at 10AM EDT.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Houses</h2> 
<p><b>Ossa Accentium</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/f94438860a726693bdf6dfede6e0e9af.jpg" />
<p><i>Once the home of an eccentric merchant-collector, this sumptuous manor possesses a view framed by one of Fargrave's otherworldly skeletons plus offers easy access to all the amenities and exotic goods this city provides.</i></p> 
<p>Ossa Accentium returns to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from July 3, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to July 18, 2024 at 10AM EDT. Furnished and unfurnished versions will be available.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Linchal Grand Manor</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/022f0485bd9ef25a08712bee586aad98.jpg" />
<p><i>This imposing estate in the Nibenese style was originally built as the summer manor of an Imperial City nobleman, now sadly deceased. Gardens with statues and a reflecting pool surround the stately walled mansion. Sumptuous!</i></p> 
<p>The Linchal Grand Manor returns to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from July 18, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to August 1, 2024 at 10AM EDT. Furnished and unfurnished versions will be available.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Houseguests</h2> 
<p><b>Relic-Apprentice Marafar</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/595f07b0d5c0f076e23a24573f747ee3.jpg" />
<p><i>With her initial Daedric studies finished, Marafar hopes to uncover more secrets as she assists Artaeum's Relicmaster. Will you host her efforts? After adding Marafar to your home, you can set her on a path, plus you and your visitors can speak with her.</i></p> 
<p>Relic-Apprentice Marafar will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from July 18, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to July 25, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Assistants</h2> 
<p><b>Eri, Barking Banker</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/b6300c383afc6e1197df7790b7b49b39.jpg" />
<p><i>Eri has been expertly trained by Nord beast tamers to act as a very good (such a good!) personal banker for you and your groupmates. He doesn't venture to Cyrodiil or the Battlegrounds. Too much violence, not enough pets.</i></p> 
<p>The new Eri, Barking Banker assistant will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from July 3, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to July 11, 2024 at 10AM EDT.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Mounts</h2> 
<p><b>Legion Zero Destrier</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/3ae39609941e9b53459e8811960d6296.jpg" />
<p><i>By forcing their steeds to consume the Blood of Coldharbour, the traitorous soldiers of Legion Zero created a war horse unlike any other. Adorned with fearsome barding and their sullen red colors, this is truly a mount to be feared.</i></p> 
<p>The Legion Zero Destrier mount will return to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from July 1, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to July 3, 2024 at 10AM EDT.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Nix-Ox Fabricant Steed</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/c82de9bc9b94ba62558b43ad3e8f35d7.jpg" />
<p><i>Programmed for obedience and fabricated for endurance, these synthetic Nix-Ox Steeds are the perfect mounts for ranging out from the Brass Fortress across the dangerous Radius.</i></p> 
<p>The Nix-Ox Fabricant Steed mount will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from July 3, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to July 8 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Ebon Steel Dwarven Spider</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/9d9dd809edcd9bde83653d8371f37224.jpg" />
<p><i>Though Dwarven Metal was usually employed in building Spider constructs, for reasons unknown some rare variants were built with a darker Ebon Steel alloy. When found in working order, these automata are prized by collectors.</i></p> 
<p>The Ebon Steel Dwarven Spider mount will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from July 3, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to July 8, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Lustrous Nix-Ox Fabricant Steed</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/4576e5a45ba733e36f781337f258e0ba.jpg" />
<p><i>Before Saints Llothis and Olms had to be confined in the Asylum Sanctorium, they used to ride through the Brass Fortress on holy days on these bizarre Fabricant mounts. But the parades are long gone, and the synthetic steeds have been repurposed.</i></p> 
<p>The Lustrous Nix-Ox Fabricant Steed mount will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from July 15, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to July 22, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Grand Nibenese Stallion</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/18505135e37f8e23295a4648840431a5.jpg" />
<p><i>Though some claim these horses are bred purely for show, the Grand Nibenese Stallion serves as more than just a good luck charm in Leyawiin. They possess a keen intelligence and even temperament—maintaining their composure, even on crowded streets.</i></p> 
<p>The Grand Nibenese Stallion mount will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from July 15, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to July 22, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Hivethief Vvardvark</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/300fb4ce6a816b3a65de80400132d3d7.jpg" />
<p><i>"Look at that tongue! You can thank Spellwright Domavas for these bug-eating beauties, expanding on Magister Varkenel's work. I hear he first tried to give them feathers, failed, then came up with this gorgeous steed."—Cidius Sosia, Necrom Stablemaster</i></p> 
<p>The Hivethief Vvardvark mount will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from July 18, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to July 22, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Hist Guar</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/3205f770f4a5c8866f18a598f3bc102f.jpg" />
<p><i>In Black Marsh this mount is called Scales-Seem-Daubed-with-Hist-Sap, but the rest of Tamriel just calls it the Hist Guar. It is the only subspecies of guar known to enjoy music.</i></p> 
<p>The Hist Guar mount will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from July 22, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to July 29, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Queen's Claw Senche-raht</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/dffb702f15f72f7bf522cfcad0e77290.jpg" />
<p><i>A scholar studying Mnemoli the Blue Star as well as a Whispering Claw warrior, this Senche-raht serves Queen Khamira with both brain and brawn. He volunteered to travel with you, lending you speed and steady companionship.</i></p> 
<p>The Queen's Claw Senche-raht mount will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from July 29, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to August 1, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Customized Actions</h2> 
<p><b>Ashen Runegathering</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/db0dcc194dd9b08f65e477578c5bf35f.jpg" />
<p><i>With a flourish of your sharp Ashlander blade, you collect a runestone in the manner taught to you by the people of the wastes.</i></p> 
<p>The Ashen Runegathering customized action will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from July 8, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to July 15, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Memento</h2> 
<p><b>Blossom Bloom</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/2d8566179dd1fc771a3f2b3f20f5fd8c.jpg" />
<p><i>This eternally blooming flower once graced the boudoir of a Dibellan high priest. Gifted to you for services rendered, you may now command it yourself.</i></p> 
<p>The Blossom Bloom memento will return to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from July 1, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to July 8, 2024 at 10AM EDT.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<h2>Pets</h2> 
<p><b>Firepot Spider</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/73e666cd0ba086bbe72f2d902bbdbc71.jpg" />
<p><i>In the Clockwork City, mechanical Firepot Spiders can be programmed to follow chefs around like little walking barbecues. Someone has devised a secret method for exporting them from Sotha Sil's hidden world—but how? Better get one while you still can.</i></p> 
<p>The Firepot Spider pet will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from July 3, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to July 8, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Small Bone Dragon Construct</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/3eefd253a2155fb4e7af3345787a5671.jpg" />
<p><i>This construct resembles a great and fearsome Bone Dragon, but it's actually a product of the Necromancer's art, assembled from modern bird and reptile bones and then reanimated.</i></p> 
<p>The Small Bone Dragon Construct pet will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from July 8, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to July 15, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Brimstone Nixad</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/7be905f9757887f7a251957266eb5e7c.jpg" />
<p><i>The legend among the underworld explorers of the Undaunted is that these little incendiary sprites are responsible for lighting all the candles, torches, and lanterns found burning underground, flying ahead of adventurers to ignite them in the dark.</i></p> 
<p>The Brimstone Nixad pet will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from July 25, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to August 1, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Hearthfire Hatchling</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/6824a976abf211d15584d2d997963abf.jpg" />
<p><i>Hearthfire Hatchlings, which are found only in an orphaned state, appear to be the offspring of a normal kagouti and one of the Hearthfire variety. Driven away by ordinary kagouti, these hatchlings are in grave need of adoption.</i></p> 
<p>The Hearthfire Hatchling pet will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from July 29, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to August 5, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Helkarn Wolf Pup</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/ec69646297e59583aa98903f464993f4.jpg" />
<p><i>The pups of the Helkarn Wolves from Elsweyr are almost as sociable with people as dog puppies, so they get a lot of attention when young. This probably contributes to their docility as mounts when full grown.</i></p> 
<p>The Helkarn Wolf Pup pet will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from July 29, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to August 5, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p>Whether you're looking for furry (and occasionally scaly) friends for your home, sinister and shimmering skins to show off, or exotic weapons and armor to best your rivals with on the battlefield, there's no shortage of fantastic deals in the Crown Store this July! Have an idea of which goodies you'll want to add to your collection? Be sure to stock up on crowns by heading over to the <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/crowns">Buy Crowns page</a> beforehand. </p> 
<p>What new or returning item(s) are you most excited to pick up this month? Let us know via <a name="_Hlk159602221"></a><a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>. </p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Crown Store</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/787b7aa7194cdb76a23c768cf1aa0a60.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ESO Live: July 3 @ 1PM EDT—Update 43 Developer Preview]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66329</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66329</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Get a peek at what's ahead with a special reveal livestream for the upcoming Update 43 base-game patch.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/43526465f5479eea75125c4e6e82fa00.jpg" /><p><i>Get a peek at what's ahead with a special reveal livestream for the upcoming Update 43 base-game patch.</i></p> 
<p>Tune in to <a href="https://www.twitch.tv/bethesda">Twitch.tv/Bethesda</a> this Wednesday, July 3 at 1PM EDT, as Associate Director of Community Management Jessica Folsom, Senior Community Manager Gina Bruno, Senior System Designer Cullen Lee, Senior UI Engineer James Sammartino, and Lead Encounter Designer Mike Finnigan provide a first-look preview of the upcoming Update 43 base-game patch. </p> 
<p>This is your chance to get the inside scoop on an upcoming feature tied to the player housing system as the team shows off the new features, improvements, and more coming with the free update. </p> 
<p>Twitch Drops will be enabled (<a href="https://help.elderscrollsonline.com/#en/answer/41809">link your <i>ESO</i> and Twitch accounts here</a>) during the livestream, so don't miss out! Are you looking forward to finding out about the new features and improvements coming in Update 43? Be sure to join us Wednesday, July 3, at 1PM EDT to learn more!</p> 
<p><i>ESO Live is your official Elder Scrolls Online stream, hosted on </i><a href="https://www.twitch.tv/bethesda"><i>Twitch.tv/Bethesda</i></a><i> by ESO's Associate Director of Community Management Jessica Folsom and Senior Community Manager Gina Bruno.</i></p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>ESO Live</category>
            <category>Community</category>
            <category>Update 43</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/43526465f5479eea75125c4e6e82fa00.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ESO's July 2024 Survival Guide]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66327</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66327</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The Gold Road Chapter is live, but there's still an incredible amount of fun on the horizon for ESO's adventurers. Check out (almost) everything coming to the game this July 2024!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/06/31ab26889565c05da5022cf3cadc271e.jpg" /><p><i>The Gold Road Chapter is live, but there's still an incredible amount of fun on the horizon for ESO's adventurers. Check out (almost) everything coming to the game this July 2024! </i></p> 
<p>As your adventures in West Weald (and beyond) continue, July introduces a host of exciting new events, promotions, and rewards. Get the inside scoop on a very busy month for <i>ESO</i>'s adventurers with another chronological breakdown!</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Daily Login Rewards (7/1 – 7/30)</b></p> 
<p>As is tradition, a host of wonderful <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66323">Daily Login rewards</a> are lined up for you throughout the month of July. This includes the fan-favorite <i>Clockwork City</i> DLC on Day 2, so don't miss it!</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Anniversary Spotlight—Morrowind &amp; Clockwork City (7/2-8/15)</b></p> 
<p>Venture into the home of the Dark Elves and <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66277">complete the Vvardenfell main storyline</a> to unlock a unique customizable action. A special themed Endeavors is also on offer—Vivec needs you!</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>ESO Live Update 43 Preview Livestream (7/3)</b></p> 
<p>The <i>ESO </i>Community Team gives you a first look at the upcoming Update 43 base-game patch via Twitch.tv/Bethesda! Check <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/" target="_blank">elderscrollsonline.com</a> next week for details.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Update 43 on Public Test Server (7/8)</b></p> 
<p>If you're on PC/Mac, you can check out (and help us test) the upcoming Update 43 base-game patch!</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Chaos Ball Weekend (7/11-7/16)</b></p> 
<p>Get the (chaos)ball and fight to hold it! Tamriel's PvP Battlegrounds competitors can enjoy solo and group queues for this specific match until July 16. Don't forget, there's also a 25% boost to Alliance Point gains.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>100% XP Boost Mini-Event (7/18-7/23)</b></p> 
<p>Leveling up a new character? Enjoy a substantial boost to XP gains from July 18 until July 23—no questions asked!</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Whitestrake's Mayhem In-Game Event (7/25-8/6)</b></p> 
<p>To arms! <i>ESO</i>'s PvP warriors take to Cyrodiil, the Imperial City, and Battlegrounds where they can enjoy bonus rewards, including Event Tickets, buffs to Alliance Points gains, and more. Look for our official announcement blog to find out more later in July.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Alienware 10-Year Anniversary July Giveaway (July)</b></p> 
<p>As part of the ongoing 10-Year Anniversary Celebration, you can log into the Alienware Vault during the month of July for a chance to receive a free code for the <i>Gold Road</i> Chapter. Keep an eye on <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/" target="_blank">elderscrollsonline.com</a> and <a href="https://na.alienwarearena.com/" target="_blank">Alienware Arena</a> for more details soon! </p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/06/7d1045324533a431a569b95e2432fef0.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>10-Year Anniversary July Roadmap</i></p> 
<p>As promised, July is another huge month for <i>ESO</i> and its many adventurers, so be sure to look out for more information on the above items closer to their live dates. Note that some details and dates may change between now and when the above promotions begin. </p> 
<p>Are you eager to continue the <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/anniversary">10-Year Anniversary Celebration</a> with us? Let us know via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>. </p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Community</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/06/31ab26889565c05da5022cf3cadc271e.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Daily Login Rewards—July 2024]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66323</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66323</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Get in gear this July with these rewards you can earn simply by logging in, including a free DLC!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/06/3328861697c77fac69cedfd4c1b2a64a274613.jpg" /><p><i>Get in gear this July with these rewards you can earn simply by logging in, including a free DLC!</i></p> 
<p>We're not here to wind you up or grind your gears—there's a free DLC available this month, just one of the great offerings you can acquire by logging in! Curious to learn more about Daily Login Rewards? Check out <a href="https://help.elderscrollsonline.com/#en/answer/41950">this help article</a> to discover all you need to know.</p> 
<p>Now, let's take a peek at some of the highlights you can receive throughout July 2024:</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Clockwork City DLC—Day 2</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/06/034ddd4aac8839219e1bedf75725641f.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Claim a free DLC and set the gears of a new story in motion!</i></p> 
<p>Log in for just two days this upcoming month to gain the <i>Clockwork City</i> DLC for free! That means a new zone with a unique storyline, encounters, item sets, and more. Enter the realm of Sotha Sil and meet the Clockwork God himself.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Wild Hunt Crown Crates—Day 3-7</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/06/a54491b018c5a2afb478500d39b27673.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Go wild with free crown crates!</i></p> 
<p>Collect a Wild Hunt Crown Crate every day from your third to your seventh login during the month of July for a total of five crates. You can preview the kinds of items available in Wild Hunt Crown Crates <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/25953">in this blog</a>.</p> 
<p><b><br></b></p><p><b>Seals of Endeavor×500—Day 9</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/10/cbf054f9fa4122ee9be26996607da8d2.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Take your pick of crown crate goods</i></p> 
<p>Get the Crown Crate item you've been saving up for with this hefty boost in your Seal savings. Claim 500 Seals of Endeavor on Day 9 to cash in. You can learn more about Seals of Endeavor <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-gb/news/post/59925">in this blog</a>.</p> 
<p><b><br></b></p><p><b>Miscarcand Monocle—Day 14</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/06/5907f6e4d64bfe64f2af83de4351b629.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>No one has been this fancy since the Ayleid Empire fell!</i></p> 
<p style="text-align: center" style="text-align: left;;">Everybody loves monocles, right? They're just so delightfully stylish. And what could represent greater style—nay, <i>grandeur</i>—than an ancient monocle of the finest Ayleid glass? Nothing, that's what. So, claim yours by logging in for fourteen days this July.<br></p> 
<p><b><br></b></p><p><b>50,000 Gold—Day 21</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/4fd2fa272aef9a9fb443be645a775da3.png" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Log in for a golden opportunity</i></p> 
<p>They say money can't buy happiness, but maybe the other great login rewards can help with that. In the meantime, you can enjoy a boon of 50,000 gold for logging in at least 21 days this month. Buy yourself something nice!</p><p><br></p> 
<p>From arcane mysteries to stylish frippery, there's a lot going on with these rewards. Which one are you most excited about? You can let us know via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>. </p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Daily Rewards</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/06/3328861697c77fac69cedfd4c1b2a64a274613.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Anniversary Spotlight—Venture into Vvardenfell & Seht's Realm]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66277</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66277</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Claim a free Customized Action by completing the Morrowind storyline, plus receive the Clockwork City DLC for free with Daily Login Rewards this July!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/06/534692666de35e670766a83ab507eaba.jpg" /><p><i>Claim a free Customized Action by completing the Morrowind storyline, plus receive the Clockwork City DLC for free with Daily Login Rewards this July! </i></p> 
<h2>Recall in Autumnal Style </h2> 
<p>The <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/anniversary">10-Year Anniversary Celebration</a> continues with a new spotlight, and this time, we're taking you and your allies to the Dark Elf island home of Vvardenfell and Sotha Sil's world in miniature. From July 2 until August 15, you can unlock the ability to claim the Gold Road Recall Customized Action for FREE from the in-game Crown Store when you complete the Champion of Vivec Achievement. </p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/06/d6f12ee627485a66a3d582c800d6b801.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Gold Road Recall</i></p> 
<p>Customized Actions allow you to change the animation and effects for specific in-game actions, such as harvesting and, in this case, recalling. To earn the Champion of Vivec Achievement, complete the Vvardenfell zone storyline and restore the demi-god's lost power. </p> 
<h2>Claim Clockwork City </h2> 
<p>In addition to the Customized Action, you can also unlock the <i>Clockwork City</i> DLC free with July's Daily Login Rewards. Simply log in during the month of July and claim the DLC on Day 2—easy! </p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/06/e4d35c3251d14d200c11b6664fea1778.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Venture into Clockwork City</i></p> 
<p>In the <i>Clockwork City</i> DLC, you can explore one of Seht's most incredible (and dangerous) creations: an entire world in miniature. This unique zone has its own storyline, challenges, and characters to discover, plus it's a long-time favorite of the <i>ESO</i> community. If you've not yet had the chance to explore the Clockwork City (or are yet to own the DLC outright), this is your opportunity to do so! </p> 
<h2>Endeavor into Morrowind</h2> 
<p>During the Anniversary Spotlight period, you can also enjoy themed Endeavors, allowing you to earn Seals by completing activities such as destroying clockwork foes, slaying public dungeon bosses in Vvardenfell, clearing the Halls of Fabrication, and more. Keep an eye out for them!</p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/06/382f7d092fd48683cfa3b946ba668f0a.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Complete Endeavors in Vvardenfell</i></p> 
<h2>Celebrate the Home of the Dark Elves</h2> 
<p>As <i>ESO</i>'s massive <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/anniversary">10-Year Anniversary Celebration</a> continues, we're thrilled to give you even more reasons to venture into the home of the Dark Elves and Sotha Sil's Clockwork City. Will you be exploring the island of Vvardenfell or Seht's world in miniature this July? Let us know via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>—have fun!</p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Community</category>
            <category>10th Anniversary</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/06/534692666de35e670766a83ab507eaba.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Workaround for Rarely Occurring Crown Crate Screen Crash - Consoles]]></title>
            <link>https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/660994/workaround-for-rarely-occurring-crown-crate-screen-crash-consoles</link>
            <guid>https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/660994/workaround-for-rarely-occurring-crown-crate-screen-crash-consoles</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 13:20:02 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[Hi all, we're following up on some reports regarding Xbox and PlayStation players encountering a rarely occurring crash when interacting with the Crown Crate screen. We are working on investigating a solution to this issue. However, we do currently have workarounds for both Xbox and PlayStation players. For those who encounter this issue, clearing your save data is the current workaround. We have next steps on how to clear your save data for Xbox and PlayStation listed below.<br><br><b>How to clear your saved data on Xbox.</b> For more detailed instructions, follow the link <a href="https://help.elderscrollsonline.com/#en/answer/29779">here</a>.
<ul><li>Restart the Game</li>
<li>Power Cycle Your Xbox</li>
<li>Clear Save Data</li>
<li>Uninstall and Reinstall the Game</li>
</ul><br><b>How to clear your saved data on PlayStation.</b> For more detailed instructions, follow the link <a href="https://help.elderscrollsonline.com/#en/answer/29777">here</a>.
<ul><li>Power Cycle Your PlayStation</li>
<li>Clear Save Data</li>
<li>After you clear your save data, do not enable the "1080p Enhanced" setting. We have found this can result in the crash reoccurring.</li>
<li>Uninstall and Reinstall the Game</li>
</ul><br>
If you continue to run into issues after following these steps, please place a ticket for us to assist you. Thanks for your patience as we work through this issue.]]></content:encoded>
            <category>Forum</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Quickly Level or Respec Your Character Free with Xbox Game Pass Rewards!]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66275</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66275</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Lay claim to in-game goodies via Xbox Game Pass Ultimate.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/06/4ef0b9758eb70067463a4193cb728909.jpg" /><p><i>Lay claim to in-game goodies via Xbox Game Pass Ultimate.</i></p> 
<p>Xbox players rejoice! You can now claim the rewards contained within the 10-Year Anniversary Pack #2 via your <a href="https://www.xbox.com/en-US/xbox-game-pass">Xbox Game Pass Ultimate</a> subscription and gain access to the following in-game items:</p> 
<ul><li>3× Gold Coast Experience Scrolls</li><ul><li>Upon usage, each of these scrolls will allot you 50% experience points from all sources for 1 hour</li><ul><li>The timer will pause while you are offline and will resume once you return.</li></ul></ul><li>1× Skill Respecification Scroll</li></ul> 
<p>Whether you need to level fast or reset your skill points, this collection of scrolls is a welcome boon for your characters.</p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/06/54e494ffed3cdce0d7439f8c9eeb80e4.png" />
<p><!--EndFragment -->From now until August 18, 2024 at 12:00PM EDT, you can obtain the 10-Year Anniversary Pack #2 by following these steps:</p> 
<ol><li>Navigate to your Xbox Home dashboard and select Game Pass</li><li>Navigate to <b>Perks</b></li><li>Find and select the <i>ESO</i> perks (10-Year Anniversary Pack #2)</li><li>Select the <b>Claim</b> button to receive a code</li><li>Select <b>Redeem</b> code and input it into the code field</li><ul><li>It will auto-populate the code field—do not alter it</li></ul><li>Select <b>Check Code</b> and then <b>Next</b></li><li>Finally, select <b>Confirm</b> to receive your in-game items!</li></ol> 
<p>Following the completion of this process, you'll receive your rewards! Don't forget, you <b>must </b>have Xbox Game Pass Ultimate to earn these goodies.</p> 
<p>Keep in mind, the 10-Year Anniversary Pack #2 will be redeemable for a limited time only. Want to learn more? Click <a href="https://www.xbox.com/en-US/xbox-game-pass">here</a> to discover what exciting offers await you with Xbox Game Pass Ultimate! Are you going to make good use of the extra XP, or perhaps you're eager to change up your character's skill points? Let us know via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, or <a href="https://www.facebook.com/ElderScrollsOnline">Facebook</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Community</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/06/4ef0b9758eb70067463a4193cb728909.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Claim This Fiery Free Mount with Your ESO Plus Membership]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66253</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66253</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Enjoying the benefits of ESO Plus™ membership? Here's one more! Claim your free in-game mount today.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esossl-a.akamaihd.net/uploads/Community/Article/blogimage/Mounts_PyrodraconicCamelLizard_header.jpg" /><p><i>Enjoying the benefits of ESO Plus™ membership? Here's one more! Claim your free in-game mount today. </i></p> 
<p>Starting today and continuing until July 19 at 10AM EDT, <b>ALL current ESO Plus members</b> can claim the free Pyrodraconic Camel-Lizard from the Mounts category of the in-game Crown Store. This scaled, fire-breathing beast is an ideal mount for your travels across the wasteland of the Wildburn or other dangerous realms. </p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/06/e7f46db8accb41ece7939308de5a20ce.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Pyrodraconic Camel-Lizard mount</i></p> 
<p>Its origins might be obscure (and perhaps a little frightening), but we're reasonably sure it's tame enough to ride.</p> 
<p>Of course, this free mount is only one of many special boons that ESO Plus members enjoy. These benefits include: </p> 
<ul><li>Access to DLC game packs</li><li>Access to the Craft Bag</li><li>A monthly crown stipend</li><li>Bonuses to gold and experience gains</li><li>And more!</li></ul> 
<p>Visit our <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/esoplus">ESO Plus page</a> to see everything that comes with membership and to sign up yourself. </p> 
<p>Don't forget, this mount is available only to ESO Plus members from now until July 19, so don't hesitate to claim yours today. Once claimed, you can find it listed under the Mounts – Camelids category of your Collections UI. </p> 
<p>Are you excited to claim your own Pyrodraconic Camel-Lizard mount and spit fire at the minions of Ithelia? Let us know via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (Formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/ElderScrollsOnline">Facebook</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>ESO Plus</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esossl-a.akamaihd.net/uploads/Community/Article/blogimage/Mounts_PyrodraconicCamelLizard_header.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Feedback On Console Environmental Sustainability Features]]></title>
            <link>https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/660783/feedback-on-console-environmental-sustainability-features</link>
            <guid>https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/660783/feedback-on-console-environmental-sustainability-features</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 15:09:23 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[Hi all. We're gathering some feedback regarding the Environmental Sustainability Features added in U42. Specifically, we would like feedback on the following patch note:
<ul><li>Reduced GPU use in Contextual Menus (Xbox Series X|S and PS5): When viewing most menus, (eg. managing inventory, achievements, quest journal, etc) framerate is now capped to 30fps. Some menus are exempt on a case-by-case basis (eg. conversations, various mini-games). Testing in Performance Mode while in these menus shows a 50% reduction in GPU consumption, resulting in overall power consumption going from approximately 63% of the maximum possible on a console down to 37%.</li>
</ul>
We're seeing your feedback about menus capped to 30fps is causing issues for some of you. Please let us know how it is impacting your play experience. We are sharing this with our teams to better inform them of your feedback and how we can improve the experience overall. Additionally, if you are experiencing other framerate issues with either your menus or player character, please note those here as well. Thanks, all.]]></content:encoded>
            <category>Forum</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Elder Scrolls Online: Gold Road & Update 42 Now Live on All Platforms]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66077</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66077</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Uncover the mystery of the Forgotten Prince with The Elder Scrolls Online: Gold Road and Update 42 base-game patch, now live on all platforms!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/ab7441b3abfa4ddc788528fb315ab9e1.jpg" /><p><i>Uncover the mystery of the Forgotten Prince with The Elder Scrolls Online: Gold Road and Update 42 base-game patch, now live on all platforms!</i><br></p> <p><i>The Elder Scrolls Online: Gold Road</i> is now live on PC/Mac, Steam, Epic Game Store, Xbox One, Xbox Series X|S, PlayStation 4, and PlayStation 5. This new Chapter for <i>The Elder Scrolls Online</i> introduces a new zone to explore, West Weald, along with a new system to master called Scribing. It also concludes the story of Ithelia, the Forgotten Prince, which began with 2023's Shadows Over Morrowind saga. </p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/459638ba6ddd36869757f1ff8004d442.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>The Forgotten Prince returns</i></p> 
<p>In addition to the Chapter, this release also includes the U42 base-game patch, introducing a host of bug fixes, balance changes, and other improvements free for all <i>ESO </i>players. You can view the full patch notes for <i>Gold Road</i> and Update 42 <a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/categories/patch-notes">on our official forums</a>. </p> 
<h2>Gold Road Chapter</h2> 
<p>In <i>The Elder Scrolls Online: Gold Road</i> you can venture into the heart of Colovian Imperial culture as you unravel the mystery of the return of a never-before-seen Daedric Prince—Ithelia. While <i>Gold Road</i> continues (and concludes) the Shadow Over Morrowind narrative that began in 2023, you can experience and enjoy the latest Chapter's storyline without having to play any of the game's previous content. </p> 
<p><b>West Weald Zone</b></p> 
<p>Located along Cyrodiil's southwest border and neighboring Valenwood and the Gold Coast, this new Chapter allows you to <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66003">explore West Weald</a>, a wealthy Imperial province thrown into chaos. Home to the proud and cosmopolitan Colovians, West Weald has found itself besieged by mysterious unknown Daedra. Even worse, a large part of the region has seemingly overnight become overgrown by the vast jungles of Valenwood, resulting in the migration of local Wood Elves. </p>
<a href="https://youtube.com/v/znogunEB5V0?autoplay=1&rel=0"><img src="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/znogunEB5V0/maxresdefault.jpg" /></a>
<p>Within this new zone, you can explore the city of Skingrad in addition to both the Gold Road region and emergent Dawnwood, where you'll discover a multitude of new side quests, world bosses, delves, public dungeons, and more. Discover more about the zone in <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66003">this preview blog</a>. </p> 
<p><b>Scribing System</b></p> 
<p>An all-new system introduced with <i>Gold Road</i>, Scribing grants you the ability to craft and <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66057">customize your own handmade abilities</a>. With Scribing, you can select a base Grimoire and tailor it with scripts to create an ability that perfectly fits your playstyle and build. </p>
<a href="https://youtube.com/v/_yWOpQ6_T0M?autoplay=1&rel=0"><img src="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/_yWOpQ6_T0M/maxresdefault.jpg" /></a>
<p>With this new system, you'll discover a robust questline that has you restore an ancient Scholarium while diving deep into the mysteries of magicka in Tamriel. Whether you're looking for greater power, versatility, or roleplaying opportunities, Scribing introduces a powerful new way to tailor your builds and play your way. </p> 
<p><b>Group Activities</b></p> 
<p>In addition to the zone's multiple world bosses, delves, and public dungeons, <i>Gold Road</i> also introduces two new group activities to challenge you and your allies: the Lucent Citadel and Mirrormoor Incursions. </p> 
<p>In the Lucent Citadel Trial, you and your large group (12 players total) must venture into a long-forgotten Daedric vault within the realm of Fargrave, contend with its unique boss encounters, and seek out the mysterious Arcane Knot. </p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/82f94f90370d384feb55d981391e73aa.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Team up to defend West Weald</i></p> 
<p>Mirrormoor Incursions are a new type of world event plaguing West Weald and threatening to overwhelm the region with the minions of Ithelia. You can discover more about both activities in <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66085">this preview blog</a>. </p> 
<p><b>New Rewards</b></p> 
<p>In addition to a new zone to explore, stories to experience, and challenges to overcome, the <i>Gold Road</i> Chapter is full of new Achievements, items, and collectibles for you to loot and earn. </p> 
<p>Specifically, West Weald features 10 powerful item sets to loot and craft in addition to three unique Mythic items to uncover using the Antiquities system. Completing Achievements can also earn you a wide range of collectibles, such as style pages for King Nantharion's Royal Armor or even the Wildburn Lynx mount. </p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/ad5fa21a49f122ad3b119ca16cf333b5.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>New collectibles, styles, and more</i></p> 
<p>Rewards also include fragments for the all-new Tales of Tribute patron and deck, Saint Alessia, in addition to a new type of collectible, called Skill Styles. Skill Styles are cosmetic collectibles that allow you to change the visuals for your existing abilities. With <i>Gold Road</i> and Update 42, there are 22 Skill Styles for you to unlock and apply from various sources, including quest rewards, public dungeons, and other activities. </p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/1d948b29fef327a9c9c14a8ce284f2c1.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Great challenges lead to great rewards!</i></p> 
<p>Finally, <i>Gold Road</i> and Update 42 also introduces the <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66017">Adventurer Across a Decade</a> Achievement, celebrating <i>ESO</i>'s 10-Year Anniversary by granting you the Fractured Glory skin for having completed the game's story content (including <i>Gold Road</i>) throughout its long history. </p> 
<h2>Purchase Details &amp; Requirements</h2> 
<p><i>The Elder Scrolls Online: Gold Road</i> is available <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/joinus">to buy now</a>, with four editions:</p> 
<ul><li><i>The Elder Scrolls Online Deluxe Collection: Gold Road</i> </li><li><i>The Elder Scrolls Online Collection: Gold Road</i> </li><li><i>The Elder Scrolls Online Deluxe Upgrade: Gold Road</i> </li><li><i>The Elder Scrolls Online: Upgrade: Gold Road</i> </li></ul> 
<p>If you are a brand-new or lapsed player, both <i>Collection </i>editions include the base game, the <i>Gold Road</i> Chapter, and ALL previous Chapters. If you already own <i>ESO</i> and its previous Chapters, both <i>Upgrade </i>editions grant access to the <i>Gold Road</i> Chapter. Note that to run <i>Gold Road</i> on PC/Mac, your machine needs to meet the game's requirements here: <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/newplayerguide/minspec">PC</a>, <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/newplayerguide/minspec">Mac</a>.</p> 
<p>In addition to the game, both versions of <i>Gold Road</i> are also available in <i>Deluxe</i> editions, which feature a unique mount, pet, memento, outfit style, and emotes.</p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/01/be77a18cfe66c3cfa77b66b9c1e021ca.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Gold Road Deluxe Edition items</i></p> 
<p>To find out more about <i>Gold Road</i> and its editions, <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65365">check out this blog</a>.</p> 
<h2>Getting Started in Gold Road</h2> 
<p>Ready to venture into West Weald? You can travel to the new zone and begin your adventure in the following ways: </p> 
<p><b>Via Wayshrine</b></p> 
<p>You can teleport directly to the zone by accessing your map, selecting Gold Road, and then selecting the automatically unlocked Skingrad Vineyards Wayshrine.</p> 
<p><b>Via the Gold Road Main Quest</b></p> 
<p>You can have the game lead you to West Weald by picking up the Chapter's first main story quest, “Paths of Chaos.” You can find it by navigating to your Collections and then viewing Stories, selecting Chapter, and then Gold Road. </p> 
<p><b>Via the Tutorial</b></p> 
<p>You can also travel to West Weald by creating a new character and completing the tutorial. At the end of the tutorial experience, you can select the zone as your destination and begin.</p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/178df5daaf8d02cd7580ae91c5a6519b.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center"><i>Adventure awaits in Gold Road</i></p> <p>Note that there are no level or story requirements for the <i>Gold Road </i>Chapter, allowing you to jump right in with any of your characters—existing or brand new! </p> <h2>Update 42 </h2> <p>Launching in tandem with Gold Road is Update 42, a free base-game patch for all <i>ESO</i> players. Update 42 introduces a series of balance changes, fixes, and additions with no purchase required (beyond access to the game itself). </p> <p><b>Improvements to In-game Mail</b></p> <p>With Update 42, we've made a series of improvements to in-game mail, focusing on its interface and notifications. This includes the addition of categories (player mail, system mail, and system alerts), improved sorting, attachment preview, and inventory space display. </p> <p>This update also adds a “Delete After Claim” option (helping you keep inboxes under control), a “Take All” function, and notifications for mail with attachments. In addition, messages received from your Hirelings will now be automatically recorded in the Lore Library under “Hireling Correspondence.”</p> <p>Finally, as part of the team's efforts to improve server performance and stability, Update 42's mail changes also include reduced expiration times based on the mail types. </p> <p><b>Environment Sustainability Features</b></p> <p>With this update, we're joining Team Xbox in reducing our game's environmental impact with the following new features:</p> <ul><li>Reduced GPU use during periods of inactivity for PC/Mac, Xbox Series X|S, and PlayStation 5. </li><ul><li>Reducing resolution and imposing a framerate cap during inactivity. </li></ul><li>Screen dimming during periods of inactivity on PC/Mac. </li><ul><li>Note that this already occurs on consoles.</li></ul><li>Reduced GPU use in Contextual Menus for Xbox Series X|S and PlayStation 5. </li><ul><li>When viewing most menus on consoles, the framerate is capped.</li></ul></ul> <p>For more on Xbox's sustainability efforts, <a href="https://www.xbox.com/en-US/community/sustainability">visit this page</a>.<br></p> <p>For everything changing and coming with Update 42, be sure to check out the <a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/categories/patch-notes">patch notes on the official forums</a>. </p> <h2>Forgotten No More</h2> <p>The Forgotten Prince walks Tamriel, and chaos follows in her wake. Investigate the emergence of Ithelia and confront her scions, explore the Colovian region of West Weald, and unlock and customize new abilities with the Scribing System in <i>The Elder Scrolls Online: Gold Road</i>. Tell us if you're excited to dive deep into this new Chapter via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline;">Facebook</a>. </p> <p><i>The Elder Scrolls Online: Gold Road is now live on PC/Mac, Xbox One, Xbox Series X|S, PlayStation 4, and PlayStation 5.</i><br></p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Gold Road</category>
            <category>Update 42</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/ab7441b3abfa4ddc788528fb315ab9e1.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Celebrate ESO in Style with the Diamond Anniversary Crown Crate]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66083</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66083</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Find the finery and fashion appropriate to the ongoing celebrations with the items and collectibles found in the new Diamond Anniversary Crown Crates.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/06/183d368d4915fea341a39956ae007749.jpg" /><p><i>Find the finery and fashion appropriate to the ongoing celebrations with the items and collectibles found in the new Diamond Anniversary Crown Crates.</i></p> 
<p>***</p> 
<p><i>Ten years. From Dragons in Elsweyr to Vampires in Skyrim, we've slain some of the mightiest foes. We've laughed alongside Razum-dar, gotten our hands bloody with Naryu, and cried with Khamira. Whether you carry the lion banner, swear fealty to the Tribunal, or leap into battle with "For the Queen!" on your lips, we've shared a decade of Elder Scrolls Online adventures together.</i></p> 
<p><i>Take up arms in celebration of our Diamond anniversary. Carry remembrances of the Five Companions into battle, ride atop a fallen titan as you leap into the fray, and commemorate the last decade of adventures with dazzling new treasures to last ten years more. Come along, friend. You're always welcome in Tamriel.</i> </p> 
<p>***
</p><p> The new Diamond Anniversary Crown Crates arrive in the Crown Store this Thursday, June 20, 2024 at 10AM EDT. When opening these crates, you'll have a chance to acquire fine goods suitable to celebrate any special occasion in the form of new and returning items and collectibles.</p> 
<p>These goods include unique mounts, pets, furnishings, and much more. You can see just some of the items available within Diamond Anniversary Crown Crates below.</p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/06/c66151c85b06753cec012f09cf075c29.jpg" />
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/06/25dcd9b6a5d46d8e181f5d2af04b1816.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Prince Irnskar's Gala Regalia and King Emeric's Diamond Regalia costumes</i></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/06/6f4b3625a2dcc4894068c25327716a7b.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Queen Ayrenn's Diamond Gown costume</i></p>
<img src="https://esossl-a.akamaihd.net/uploads/Community/Article/blogimage/Polymorph_MolagBalIllusion.jpg" />
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/06/8ef5d81052ef4ca65b02c772f8f1333d.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Molag Bal Illusion polymorph and Skin of the Anchorite skin</i></p> 
<p>The luckiest revelers may find especially grand rewards in the form of the Radiant Apex Mounts below. One of these mounts, the Shackled Titan, even has a special summoning animation if called when using the Molag Bal Illusion polymorph!</p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/06/e041472b30b1627565c000dff4d360a1.jpg" />
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/06/e5ef26000d1ad6df773029f5c4a137df.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Worm Cultist Senche-raht and Tharn's Lucent Revelry Senche mounts</i></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/06/15c7bea48ad16f96c051c2bd69d620ab.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Shackled Titan mount</i></p> 
<p>Diamond Anniversary Crown Crates will be available in one-, four-, and 15-crate bundles in addition to a unique 25-crate offering, the Diamond Anniversary Crate Bundle, that is available as a one-time purchase only. In addition to the crates, this special bundle also includes the Coldharbour Recall Customized Action.</p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/06/1f52eff6cba31db5cf9cfcc5d0d35a87.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Celebrate with this bundle of Crown Crates!</i></p> 
<p>This customized action will be unlocked automatically and added to your collectibles when the one-off bundle is first purchased. It is not part of the Diamond Anniversary crates themselves.</p> 
<p>Of course, the above is just some of the finery held in waiting for this momentous release. If you wish to see the full list of items you have a chance to receive when opening a Diamond Anniversary Crown Crate, check out <a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/660702">this thread</a> on our official forums.</p> 
<p>Be warned, when the new crates go live, the <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65723">currently available Order of the Lamp Crates</a> will be removed from the Crown Store in turn, so don't forget to pick them up while they're still available!</p> 
<p>Diamond Anniversary Crown Crates arrive this Thursday, June 20 at 10AM EDT, and you can acquire them from the Crown Crate section of the in-game Crown Store. Will you be celebrating in style? Share your festive plans and looks via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>. </p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Crown Store</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/06/183d368d4915fea341a39956ae007749.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Your Labors Are Rewarded during the Zeal of Zenithar In-Game Event]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66255</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66255</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Honor the God of Commerce to receive hard work's rewards during the Zeal of Zenithar in-game event!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/06/86e7550fdc628bef6633f8e5c6ffa840.jpg" /><p><i>Honor the God of Commerce to receive hard work's rewards during the Zeal of Zenithar in-game event!</i></p> 
<p><b>Update:</b> An earlier version of this article had incorrect information on the stock of Nenulaure, the Indrik Vendor. The information has now been updated below. We apologize for the inconvenience.</p><h2>Work Hard and Prosper</h2> 
<p>The Zeal of Zenithar in-game event returns on June 20 at 10AM EDT, and it runs until July 2 at 10AM EDT. To get started, pick up the introductory quest "The Unrefusable Offer" from Amminus Varo at the Belkarth festival grounds or acquire the free quest starter from the Crown Store. Having trouble locating Belkarth? Don't worry; just head over to the nearest Impresario tent and take the nearby portal. Upon finishing the intro quest, you unlock the daily quest, "Honest Toil."</p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/06/d71e555cee7f13e569acf66be881b4a9.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Seek Amminus Varo to begin your labors</i></p> 
<p>During the event, the first time you complete the daily quest each day, you receive a Zenithar's Sublime Parcel box as a bonus reward. Each subsequent completion of the “Honest Toil” quest during that same day rewards you with a Zenithar's Delightful Parcel box.</p> 
<p>In addition, you can earn Zenithar's Delightful Parcel boxes by participating in the following activities:</p> 
<ul><li>Completing the introductory quest “The Unrefusable Offer”</li><li>Completing any Master Writ, per discipline, per account, each day</li><ul><li>Subsequent Master Writs of the same discipline won't provide further boxes until the daily reset</li></ul><li>First daily Crafting Writ, per account, completed each day</li><li>Each time you defeat a world boss while grouped with a player who is in at least one of your player guilds</li><li>Each time you complete a world event while grouped with a player who is in at least one of your player guilds</li></ul> 
<p>You also have a <b>chance</b> to earn a Zenithar's Delightful Parcel box when conquering each round of a group-based arena challenge or completing a Cycle in the Infinite Archive while teamed up with a player who is a member of at least one of your guilds. Additionally, the final round's reward chest contains a guaranteed parcel, as will Tho'at Replicanum's reward chest.</p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/06/100c72fa3802f776bd5fc86cedbb2b75.jpg" />
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/06/756dd9d5b008f4e02fb579dbd23532d9.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Trade and toil </i></p> 
<p>If (Divines forefend!) you aren't the sort to practice an honest trade, you may discover parcels scattered across Tamriel by pickpocketing citizens and looting strongboxes or thieves troves. Maybe crime does pay, as long as some other rube is doing the hard work first!</p> 
<p>Within either parcel box (Sublime or Delightful), there is a chance to receive the following rewards:</p> 
<ul><li>A tradeable outfit style page for the <b>new </b>Gold Road Dragoon outfit style armor</li><ul><li>If you've already earned a Gold Road Dragoon style page for the day, you have a chance to instead get a style page for a past Zeal of Zenithar event set such as the High Rock Spellsword outfit style armor, Kwama Miner's Kit armor outfit style, or Ashen Militia weapon outfit style.</li></ul><li>Durable crafting materials, provisioning ingredients, alchemy reagents, runestones, or a motif style item</li><li>Crafting boosters</li><ul><li>Chance to drop a gold-tier booster or a research time scroll</li></ul><li>Furnishing or provisioning recipes</li><li>Repair kits, siege repair kits, or a small chance for an Impresario Group Repair Kit</li><li>Treasure Maps, Survey Reports, Imperial City vault keys, Companion gear, or a random currency pouch.</li><ul><li>The random currency pouch can contain either gold or Tel Var stones; there is an extremely small chance that you discover a jackpot that allots 100,000 of the associated currency! </li><ul><li>The earnings from this pouch, jackpot or otherwise, are unaffected by any form of currency boosts</li></ul></ul></ul>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/06/7418b660301b1349c57d59fc47a7b634.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Honor the Divines as a Gold Road Dragoon</i></p> 
<p>Both boxes can contain any of the above, but the Sublime Parcel boxes provide a higher chance to contain the more valuable rewards.</p> 
<h2>Good Deeds Go Round Tamriel</h2> 
<p>These boxes won't be the only bonus rewards you can enjoy during the Zeal of Zenithar event. Throughout the duration, you'll benefit from the following modified global in-game effects:</p> 
<ul><li>Wayshrine travel costs are reduced by 75%</li><li>Repair costs on vendors are reduced by 50%</li><li>Crafting inspiration gain from all sources is increased by 100%</li><li>Vendor prices across Tamriel are reduced by 10%</li><ul><li>These include:</li><ul><li>Vendors that sell items for gold, AP, or Tel Var stones, including the Golden Vendor</li><li>Houses purchasable for gold</li></ul></ul></ul> 
<h2>Event Tickets &amp; Vendors</h2> 
<p>If you participate in the Zeal of Zenithar event, you also receive three Event Tickets the first time you complete the “Honest Toil” quest each day. By the end of the event, you can collect a whopping 39 tickets!</p> 
<p>Thankfully, the Impresario is well-stocked to help you make good use of your gathered wealth. You'll even have your first opportunity to complete the Master of Schemes personality with the release of its third fragment.</p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/06/24f94af4ee71a97012ab795e468c6054.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Ensure your just rewards with masterful scheming</i></p><p>During the event period, the Impresario stocks:</p> <ul><li>All three Molag Bal Illusion Imp pet fragments</li><ul><li>Anchor Chain Fragment</li><li>Dark Anchor Pinion</li><li>Effigy of the Dominator</li></ul><li>All three Master of Schemes personality fragments</li><ul><li>Cold Iron Gauntlet</li><li>Grim Iron Mask</li><li>(NEW) Tyrant's Soul Gem</li></ul><li><b>NEW</b> bound style pages for the Gold Road Dragoon outfit style armor</li><li>Group Repair Kits</li><li>Companion Guild Commendations</li></ul><p>Additionally, during the event, the Impresario's Assistant Philius Dormier offers the following goodies:</p><ul><li>All three Unstable Morpholith pet fragments</li><ul><li>Deadlands Flint</li><li>Rune-Etched Striker</li><li>Smoldering Bloodgrass Tinder</li></ul><li>All three Deadlands Scorcher skin fragments</li><ul><li>Rune-Scribed Daedra Hide</li><li>Rune-Scribed Daedra Sleeve</li><li>Rune-Scribed Daedra Veil</li></ul><li>All three Soulfire Dragon Illusion pet fragments</li><ul><li>Hallowed Hourglass Basin</li><li>Illuminated Dragon Scroll</li><li>Kvatchian Incense</li></ul><li>All three Scales of Akatosh skin fragments</li><ul><li>Aureate Anointing Oils</li><li>Lustrous Ritual Sand</li><li>Sacred Scale</li></ul></ul><p>Last but certainly not least, the Indrik vendor Nenulaure's shop is stocked with the following items:<br></p><ul><li>Nascent Indrik Feathers</li><li>Luminous Indrik Berries</li><li>Icebreath Indrik Berries</li><li>Shimmering Indrik pet</li><li>Rimedusk Indrik pet</li></ul>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/06/d38e826229c85db13f9c863ecf150571.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Nenulaure the Indrik Vendor</i></p> 
<h2>May Zenithar Fill Your Coffer</h2> 
<p>With Zenithar watching over you during this event, you can earn incredible rewards for your hard work. Ready to pitch in and see the fruits of honest labor arrive as in-game rewards? Let us know whether you'll be honoring the Trader God via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>. </p> 
<p><i>The Zeal of Zenithar in-game event begins June 20 at 10:00AM EDT, and it runs until Tuesday, July 2 at 10:00AM EDT.</i></p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Events</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/06/86e7550fdc628bef6633f8e5c6ffa840.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Celebrate ESO's 10th Anniversary with Us in Grazzano Visconti, Italy!]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66243</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66243</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Sign up today and join other members of the #ESOFam in Italy for an unforgettable night of mystery and fun!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/06/4cf1fb044f13751a24eef4aaaccc6d0e.jpg" /><p><i>Sign up today and join other members of the #ESOFam in Italy for an unforgettable night of mystery and fun!</i></p> 
<p>The <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/anniversary">worldwide 10-Year Anniversary Celebration</a> continues with even more awesome in-person community events. This time, we're inviting players to gather for an evening of <i>ESO</i>-themed fun in the picturesque Italian village of Grazzano Visconti.</p> 
<p>On September 14, guests will arrive at the Ristorante il Biscione and take part in a live Tamriel adventure experience. This will include several whodunit mystery games, so keep your wits about you—these puzzles are worthy of Investigator Vale! Once the games have been completed, community members will be invited to partake in a banquet with their fellow sleuths.</p> 
<p>Want to sign up? Select the button below and follow the instructions to register. Guest slots are limited, so snag your ticket ASAP!</p><p><i><br></i></p><p>If you have any questions regarding event details, please reach out to us on our Italian social channels via <a href="https://twitter.com/bethesda_it">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/bethesda_it/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline.it/">Facebook</a>.</p><p><i>ESO's</i> 10-Year Anniversary Celebration continues all across the globe, and the party isn't done yet! Keep an eye out for news on future events you won't want to miss. Are you excited to join us and other passionate community members in Italy to commemorate an entire decade of <i>ESO?</i> Let us know via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Community</category>
            <category>10th Anniversary</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/06/4cf1fb044f13751a24eef4aaaccc6d0e.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Anniversary Celebration—Dazzle Your Friends with a Flashy Emote from Alienware]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66221</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66221</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Claim a free in-game emote via this 10-Year Anniversary promotion!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/06/75f87acfd13a9b3038f589a209fef51b.jpg" /><p><i>Claim a free in-game emote via this 10-Year Anniversary promotion!</i></p> 
<p>The ongoing 10-Year Anniversary Celebration continues, and we are thrilled to announce more player rewards—this time in partnership with Alienware™! You can now claim the Pyromancer's Quandary emote for <i>ESO</i> while supplies last.</p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/06/c1f3631b9b3d003cf7deb703be00de71.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>The Pyromancer's Quandary</i></p> 
<p>All you need to do is sign in or create a free account with <a href="https://www.alienwarearena.com/ucf/show/2171337/boards/contest-and-giveaways-global/Giveaway/the-elder-scrolls-online-pyromancers-quandary-emote-key-giveaway">Alienware Arena</a> and click “GET KEY” on <a href="https://www.alienwarearena.com/ucf/show/2171337/boards/contest-and-giveaways-global/Giveaway/the-elder-scrolls-online-pyromancers-quandary-emote-key-giveaway">this page</a>. You can then redeem it on the official <i>ESO</i> website using these steps:</p> 
<p>1. Copy the Reward Code provided in your email from Alienware.</p> 
<p>2. Confirm that you own a copy of <i>The Elder Scrolls Online</i> before redeeming a Reward Code. </p> 
<p>3. Navigate to this URL and sign into your <i>ESO </i>account: <a href="https://account.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/redeem-code">https://account.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/redeem-code</a> </p> 
<p>4. Enter the code and click Redeem Code to submit.</p> 
<p>To sign up or find more information and support, visit Alienware's <a href="http://www.aw.gg/arena">official website</a>.</p> 
<p>Are you excited to show your friends and guildmates your pyromantic potential? Let us know via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>10th Anniversary</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/06/75f87acfd13a9b3038f589a209fef51b.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Try Out ESO Plus for Free to Enjoy Unlimited Crafting Storage, DLC Access, & More]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66079</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66079</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Welcome the arrival of Gold Road with access to DLCs such as Scribes of Fate, Scions of Ithelia, and more with an ESO Plus™ free trial!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/06/40fbc1ad52fcab9c911388a3e617ed90.jpg" /><p><i>Welcome the arrival of Gold Road with access to DLCs such as Scribes of Fate, Scions of Ithelia, and more with an ESO Plus™ free trial!</i><br></p> 
<h2>Enjoy ESO Plus on Us</h2> 
<p>The ESO Plus Free Trial is live from now until Wednesday, June 19, 2024 at 10:00AM EDT. During the trial period, you can enjoy the following ESO Plus benefits with no credit card required and no strings attached:</p> 
<ul><li>Full access to over 20 DLC game packs—new zones, quests, dungeons, and more</li><ul><li>Includes access to the zones from last year's <i>Necrom</i> release (Note that players on Xbox and PlayStation consoles will need to wait until after <i>Gold Road</i> launches on June 18 to access <i>Necrom</i>)</li><li>Includes 28 group dungeons (including the <i>Scions of Ithelia</i> dungeons from earlier this year), systems such as Antiquities and Tales of Tribute, and more!</li></ul><li>A Craft Bag providing unlimited storage for all your crafting materials </li><li>Double Bank space for all characters on your account </li><li>10% increase to experience, gold, and Archival Fortune acquisition, crafting inspiration, and trait research rates </li><li>Double furnishings and collectibles space in player housing </li><li>Exclusive ability to dye costumes </li><li>Double Transmute Crystal storage</li></ul> 
<p>Eager to check out ESO Plus for free? Here's what you need to do:</p> 
<ol><li>Log in to <i>The Elder Scrolls Online</i></li><li>Navigate to the Crown Store</li><li>Select the ESO Plus tab</li><li>Select “Free Trial!”</li></ol> 
<p>Once you've activated your trial, all the benefits listed above are available to you until June 19. Note that this free trial does <b>not</b> grant access to the Companions from the <i>Blackwood</i>, <i>High Isle</i>, or <i>Necrom</i> Chapters.</p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/06/9db07c7eb9e9a2428a3e49640779ef4d.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Explore the Telvanni Peninsula with ESO Plus!</i></p> 
<p>If you'd like to continue to enjoy the benefits of ESO Plus beyond the trial, including monthly crown stipends and exclusive in-game deals, you can get full membership via our ESO Plus page! Want to learn more? Check out our <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/guides/esoplusguide">ESO Plus guide</a>.</p> 
<h2>ESO Plus Is a Plus to Have</h2> 
<p>Boosts to XP and gold gains, additional bag space, DLC access, and more await those with ESO Plus membership, and you can try out these incredible benefits with no credit card required and no strings attached during the free trial period. </p> 
<p>Are you excited to enjoy the benefits of membership at no cost? Let us know via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>. </p> 
<p><i>The ESO Plus Free Trial is now live and will run until Wednesday, June 19, 2024 at 10:00AM EDT.</i></p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>ESO Plus</category>
            <category>Crown Store</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/06/40fbc1ad52fcab9c911388a3e617ed90.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Crown Store Showcase—June 2024]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66157</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66157</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Find a home on the high seas or claim Undaunted plunder with new Crown Store goods this month!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/962fd2536f72aa7754c0cf804b2ed8c0327363.jpg" /><p><i>Find a home on the high seas or claim Undaunted plunder with new Crown Store goods this month!</i></p> 
<p>Below, you can review all the items available in (and coming to) the in-game Crown Store throughout June 2024. Don't forget to also check out what is currently available on the <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/crownstore">Crown Store page</a>. Fancy any of these goods? Then head over to the <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/buycrowns">Buy Crowns page</a> to secure the crowns you need! Certain items and offers will be available for a limited time only, so be sure to read their details below and don't miss out.</p> 
<h2>ESO Plus Deals</h2> 
<p>All ESO Plus™ members have access to a monthly selection of exclusive deals and items. You can find more information about them in <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/54825">this article</a>.</p> 
<p><b>Exclusive Free Items</b></p> 
<p><b>Statuette: Peryite, Blightlord </b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/18df619754737bd63d7423d96dd38cb2.jpg" />
<p><i>A miniature statue of Peryite, the Daedric Prince of Pestilence.</i></p> 
<p>The Statuette: Peryite, Blightlord will be available in the Crown Store FREE, exclusively to ESO Plus Members on all platforms for a limited time, from June 27, 2024 at 10 AM EDT, to July 29, 2024 at 10 AM EDT.</p> 
<h2>Crafting</h2> 
<p><b>Crown Crafting Motif: Huntsman </b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/3135c66cb2311c4669d91f8496ecf2b5.jpg" />
<p><i>For those who would honor Hircine the Hunter, it is right and proper to adopt the apparel and arms of his Huntsmen, those spear-shakers, fewterers, and whippers-in of the Lord of the Hunting Grounds.—Uraccanach the Witchman</i></p> 
<p>The Crown Crafting Motif: Huntsman will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from June 3, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to June 6, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item. Huntsman Motif chapters, and very rarely the complete book, have a chance to drop from Balorgh in March of Sacrifices.</p> 
<p><b>Crown Crafting Motif: Shardborn</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/5c3802102594f1f2b1a00d6bb6334964.jpg" />
<p><i>Glass-smiths form Shardborn arms and armor using creatia and sand in secretive techniques they hold dear. Use to learn the Shardborn crafting style.</i></p> 
<p>The Crown Crafting Motif: Shardborn will be available in the Crown Store with the launch of <i>Gold Road </i>and Update 42 coming June 3, 2024 for PC/Mac, and on June 18, 2024 for Xbox One, Xbox Series X|S, PlayStation 4, and PlayStation 5. Shardborn Motif chapters, and very rarely the complete book, have a chance to drop from Skingrad Reward Coffers, acquired by completing daily Delve quests from Lieutenant Agrance and daily World Boss quests from Commander Salerius in Skingrad.</p> 
<p><b>Crown Crafting Motif: Wayward Guardian</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/acf0bac005e7a005d50e3c406e6430ee.jpg" />
<p><i>Arana of the Ghostsong Clan notes this about Wayward Guardian gear: "If the deepfolk sought the protection of the Witch, Hunter, and Headsman to create their otherworldly works, let us turn that strength against our equally unnatural foes." Use to learn the Wayward Guardian crafting style.</i></p> 
<p>The Crown Crafting Motif: Wayward Guardian will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from June 6, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to June 10, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item. Wayward Guardian Motif chapters have a chance to drop from a Wayward Guardian's Cache, acquired by completing daily quests from Ardanir in Markarth.</p> 
<p><b>Crown Crafting Motif: Meridian</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/f0ff1fe7aefb6ea0aa7098e315e302f4.jpg" />
<p><i>From ancient times till the present, the Cult of Meridia, no matter how often suppressed, always rebounds and reappears. Mortals who revere her often honor her by adopting an armor style inspired by that of the Aurorans, Meridia's Daedric warriors. Use to learn the Meridian crafting style.</i></p> 
<p>The Crown Crafting Motif: Meridian will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from June 10, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to June 13, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item. Meridian Motif chapters, and very rarely the complete book, have a chance to drop from Symphony of Blades in the Depths of Malatar.</p> 
<p><b>Crown Crafting Motif: Nighthollow</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/5c100012078a73522e996974cc8c3712.jpg" />
<p><i>The panoply of the Nighthollow vampires evokes the sublime terror of their shadowy domain. Mortals who see this fearsome armor rarely keep their blood for long. Use to learn the Nighthollow crafting style.</i></p> 
<p>The Crown Crafting Motif: Nighthollow will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from June 24, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to June 27, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item. Nighthollow Motif chapters, and very rarely the complete book, have a chance to drop from Markarth Reward Coffers, acquired by completing the Harrowstorm daily quest for Nelldena in Markarth.</p> 
<p><b>Outfit Style</b></p> 
<p><b>Symphony of Blades Arms Pack </b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/f46da91768f338906a7b779bb5e75d4b.jpg" />
<p><i>Urgarlag Chief-bane may tell you of the sunken ruins of Malatar, where Meridia's champions—such as the Symphony of Blades—await. Alter your weapon's appearance to match the Undaunted Symphony of Blades awards by using this complete set of Outfit styles.</i></p> 
<p>The Symphony of Blades Arms Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from June 3, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to June 6, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item. The matching mask page will have a small chance to drop from Symphony of Blades from veteran Depths of Malatar. The matching shoulder page can be purchased from Urgarlag Chief-bane for 50 Undaunted keys, or has a chance of dropping from Urgarlag's Mystery Coffer for 1 key. Having the achievement “Throwing Shade” increases the drop chances of both items.</p> 
<p><b>Ilambris Arms Pack </b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/8d2951cd4de9acd16952c4b45f9b8852.jpg" />
<p><i>Undaunted veteran Glirion may warn you of the Ilambris twins, who serve as wardens in the Crypt of Hearts, Alter your weapon's appearance to match the Undaunted Ilambris awards by using this complete set of Outfit styles.</i></p> 
<p>The Ilambris Arms Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from June 10, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to June 13, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item. The matching mask page will have a small chance to drop from the Ilambris twins from veteran Crypt of Hearts I. The matching shoulder page can be purchased from Glirion the Redbeard for 50 Undaunted keys, or has a chance of dropping from Glirion's Mystery Coffer for 1 key. Having the achievement “A Crypt for Two” increases the drop chances of both items.</p> 
<p><b>Pirate Skeleton Arms Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/7d5958e91170bde58894b17c1140e42e.jpg" />
<p><i>Captain Blackheart and his pirate crew may control an idyllic haven in Bangkorai, but Glirion the Redbeard hopes to change that—through you. Alter your weapon's appearance to match the Undaunted Pirate Skeleton awards by using this complete set of Outfit styles.</i></p> 
<p>The Pirate Skeleton Arms Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from June 13, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to June 17, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item. The matching mask page will have a small chance to drop from Captain Blackheart from veteran Blackheart Haven. The matching shoulder page can be purchased from Glirion the Redbeard for 50 Undaunted keys, or has a chance of dropping from Glirion's Mystery Coffer for 1 key. Having the achievement “Thoroughly Plundered” increases the drop chances of both items.</p> 
<p><b>Gold Road Dragoon Arms Pack </b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/c4c396a429f8a5b31b4d703d912630ae.jpg" />
<p><i>Those who patrol and ensure the safety of travelers along the Gold Road use matching weapons that feature the red diamond. Alter your weapon's appearance to match the Gold Road Dragoon Weapons by using this complete set of Gold Road Dragoon Outfit styles.</i></p> 
<p>The new Gold Road Dragoon Arms Pack will be available in the Crown Store during the Zeal of Zenithar event, from June 20, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to July 2, 2024 at 10AM EDT. Matching armor pages will drop from Zenithar's Sublime Parcel, obtainable once per day for the duration of the event. Bound versions of the armor pages can be purchased from the Impresario for 5 Event Tickets each during the event.</p> 
<p><b>Anvil of Zenithar Arms Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/f19e382d667589ec58c1328cb96d66d4.jpg" />
<p><i>The blessings of Zenithar, God of Work and Commerce, light up weapons forged on his sacred anvil. Alter your weapon's appearance by using this complete set of Anvil of Zenithar Outfit styles.</i></p> 
<p>The Anvil of Zenithar Arms Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from June 24, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to June 27, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<h2>Wardrobe</h2> 
<p><b>Rimmen Fountain-Side Loungewear </b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/7dac4e0b5b261e622dc11a509027c500.jpg" />
<p><i>Famed for their clear water, the fountains of Rimmen provide a place for locals to gather and catch up on the news of the day. If you seek a moment of refreshment, wear this elegant yet comfortable garb as you dangle your feet in the cool waters.</i></p> 
<p>The Rimmen Fountain-Side Loungewear costume will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from June 10, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to June 13, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<p><b>Pirate Costume Pack </b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/ccfb9cffc46db9aefd4472dda1f8c755.jpg" />
<p><i>The pirates of the Abecean Sea are among Tamriel's fiercest sea raiders—and they have a style all their own, which you can adopt when you don these jaunty and rakish costumes!</i></p> 
<p>The Pirate Costume Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from June 13, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to June 17, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<p><b>Dremora Deceiver Duster </b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/257a492369cd43a271a4642580ea35fb.jpg" />
<p><i>In the ceaseless wars of Oblivion, there will always be scoundrels. After rooking marks of goods and foes of lives, this rugged, Dremora-style coat lets you slink away, sounding no louder than a whisper.</i></p> 
<p>The Dremora Deceiver Duster will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from June 24, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to June 27, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<h2>Crate</h2> 
<p><b>Dwarven Crate</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/b3901af9f6aeee1238b18428623f6c9c.jpg" />
<p><i>A mystery collection of Dwarven-themed items!</i></p> 
<p>Dwarven Crates return to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from June 6, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to June 20, 2024 at 10AM EDT.</p> 
<h2>DLC</h2> 
<p><b>Necrom Deluxe Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/7f8806ce8ecd8a9fb42c345192e9bef6.jpg" />
<p><i>Includes all the bonus content of the Necrom Deluxe Edition, as well as the Necrom pre-purchase digital items.</i></p> 
<p>The <i>Necrom</i> Deluxe Pack will be available in the Crown Store with the launch of <i>Gold Road </i>and Update 42 coming June 3, 2024 for PC/Mac, and on June 18, 2024 for Xbox One, Xbox Series X|S, PlayStation 4, and PlayStation 5.</p> 
<p> </p> 
<p><b>Necrom</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/d39b1aa78c03198f3c880af648a4425c.jpg" />
<p><i>What truths are best left hidden? Discover Necrom and delve into the forbidden secrets of Apocrypha. From Morrowind's Telvanni Peninsula to Hermaeus Mora's realm, fight to preserve reality.</i></p> 
<p>The<i> Necrom</i> Chapter will be available in the Crown Store with the launch of <i>Gold Road </i>and Update 42 coming June 3, 2024 for PC/Mac, and on June 18, 2024 for Xbox One, Xbox Series X|S, PlayStation 4, and PlayStation 5.</p> 
<p><b>Class: Arcanist</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/29c4ad472ab07eae495f781f8d8eabb6.jpg" />
<p><i>Unlocks the Arcanist class for use in character creation.</i></p> 
<p>The Arcanist class will be available in the Crown Store with the launch of <i>Gold Road </i>and Update 42 coming June 3, 2024 at 2AM EDT for PC/Mac, and on June 18, 2024 at 2AM EDT for Xbox One, Xbox Series X|S, PlayStation 4, and PlayStation 5.</p> 
<h2>Events </h2> 
<p><b>Currency</b></p> 
<p><b>Event Tickets</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2022/01/d80129d699abe5116dbb4fb22c2d4b5b.jpg" />
<p><i>A ticket used to purchase rare goods from The Impresario, Event Merchant. Curious as to what goods? Well, chat with her to see what she has to offer!</i></p> 
<p>Single Event Tickets will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time during the Zeal of Zenithar event, from June 20, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to July 2, 2024 at 10AM EDT. Event Tickets are also giftable to other players from within the Crown Store. </p> 
<h2>Furniture </h2> 
<p><b>Music Box, Subterranean Sonata </b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/1eaaa1e50fb21d85aeb0ee062f7a0a4b.jpg" />
<p><i>When activated, plays a music box arrangement of the otherworldly "Subterranean Sonata" composition.</i></p> 
<p>The Music Box, Subterranean Sonata will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from June 6, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to June 10, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<p><b>Furnishing Pack: Maormer Boarding Party </b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/80c4b944a3325d1014eaafdb1f1b5c69.jpg" />
<p><i>The Sea Elves rule the waves, but you've beaten them just the same. Celebrate your victory in battle by furnishing your home with "liberated" serpentine items, including a raiding party tent and a Maormer ship's prow!</i></p> 
<p>The Furnishing Pack: Maormer Boarding Party will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from June 13, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to June 27, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<p><b>Cadwell's Astounding Portal </b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/e0e2a5599fcb180b6a6d3dd19266b257.jpg" />
<p><i>Ready for a jolly good time with Cadwell? Summon him to your home with this handy portal, and he'll play a tune, juggle fish, indulge in some chit-chat, or more! Alas, Cadwell refuses to do preview performances.</i></p> 
<p>Cadwell's Astounding Portal will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from June 17, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to June 20, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<p><b>Furnishing Pack: Aquatic Splendor </b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/888299ca342eb445c0017d85bdd64ffe.jpg" />
<p><i>Add oceanic depth to your abode with this seaworthy arrangement of home furnishings. An abundance of vibrant coral and kelp, effervescent bubbles and jellyfish, and even a mudcrab sparring partner can turn your home into a deep-sea wonderland.</i></p> 
<p>The Furnishing Pack: Aquatic Splendor will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from June 27, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to July 11, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<h2>Houses</h2> 
<p><b>Merryvine Estate </b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/5b5dc0f34448f91dc068970e14a63f5c.jpg" />
<p><i>Merryvine's wines once rivaled those of the nearby Valente Vineyard, but misfortune sent its former owner fleeing. This sun-kissed estate features fertile grapevines, a house suitable for entertaining, and facilities that would please any vintner.</i></p> 
<p>Merryvine Estate will be available in the Crown Store with the launch of <i>Gold Road </i>and Update 42 coming June 3, 2024 for PC/Mac, and on June 18, 2024 for Xbox One, Xbox Series X|S, PlayStation 4, and PlayStation 5. Furnished and unfurnished versions will be available.</p> 
<p><b>The Fair Winds</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/9d438de952d2bad68d90ae4afd13a29a.jpg" />
<p><i>Enjoy sea-based living on the Fair Winds, a spacious galleon hailing from the Systres Isles. You have a bevy of travel options a mere spin of the ship's wheel away, with ports of call in Vulkhel Guard, Davon's Watch, and Daggerfall. Just watch for ornaugs!</i></p> 
<p>The Fair Winds returns to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from June 13, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to June 27, 2024 at 10AM EDT. Furnished and unfurnished versions will be available.</p> 
<p><b>Seaveil Spire </b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/77bbf65e3862e00d8fb1428d860a6762.jpg" />
<p><i>Early in the First Era, a pious tribe of Nedes followed the Tower's guidance to an undersea anomaly, where they built a submerged sanctuary. Millennia later, the edifice and anomaly remain, providing a secure and wondrous escape from the surface world.</i></p> 
<p>Seaveil Spire returns to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from June 27, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to July 11, 2024 at 10AM EDT. Furnished and unfurnished versions will be available.</p> 
<h2>Houseguests</h2> 
<p><b>Clan Mother Tadali </b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/138836652c3ed9a78b351b15c01d27f3.jpg" />
<p><i>Get ready for a visit from Clan Mother Tadali! She'll share her wisdom with you if you share your sunbeams with her. After adding Tadali to your home, you can set her on a path, plus you and your visitors can speak with her.</i></p> 
<p>Clan Mother Tadali will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from June 13, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to June 17, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<h2>Assistants</h2> 
<p><b>Tzozabrar, Dwarven Deconstructor </b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/f2fbc14f5c9a0d4d20e0d42dd9f4aab9.jpg" />
<p><i>Tzozabrar will intake items you don't need, expelling useful materials no doubt scavenged from a Dwarven construct. Tonal interference makes it unusable in Cyrodiil or Battlegrounds.</i></p> 
<p>The new Tzozabrar, Dwarven Deconstructor assistant will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from June 27, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to July 11, 2024 at 10AM EDT.</p> 
<h2>Mounts</h2> 
<p><b>Meridian Sabre Cat</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/625826055d5689776b043f31a885148b.jpg" />
<p><i>"Some accounts of Meridia's plane of the Colored Rooms describe a menagerie of light-imbued spectral beasts elevated from Nirn and 'purified' by the Lady's holy light."—Sayings of Valasha</i></p> 
<p>The Meridian Sabre Cat mount will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from June 10, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to June 13, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<p><b>Ossified Rime Wolf</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/3c1cb929e8727d1dfd9dbcf524e88f35.jpg" />
<p><i>"Tears of rage and hatred don't go wasted in Skyrim. These rare droplets fall upon the snow, calling a spirit of bone and rime from Aetherius. Within seconds, a frost-spiked wolf forms, snarling and bridled with grim purpose."—Hef, Tale Collector</i></p> 
<p>The Ossified Rime Wolf mount will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from June 13, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to June 17 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<p><b>Stitchedwell Stick Guar </b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/7a43c0497b7510e8f06a6ea721f5011f.jpg" />
<p><i>Soul Shriven knights ride only the most finely stitched steeds. As one old knight proclaimed, "Don't mind the bit of fray at the bottom there. Or the pesky splinters sticking out of the handle. This guar is a jolly smooth ride!"</i></p> 
<p>The Stitchedwell Stick Guar mount will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from June 17, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to June 20, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><b>Baysong Quasigriff</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/cc43407abbdc38a1de4fc07abe481cc1.jpg" />
<p><i>Unlike their mainland cousins, the quasigriffs of the Systres Archipelago have vibrant, sea-tinted feathers. Admittedly, Irastimil Direnni never intended to create such colorful creatures. Noble Bretons adore them and travel about High Isle on their backs.</i></p> 
<p>The Baysong Quasigriff mount will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from June 27, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to July 1, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<h2>Customized Actions</h2> 
<p><b>Dwarven Sphere Chop </b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/52120a1ee22861be73dea6e73db34600.jpg" />
<p><i>Why break a sweat by chopping wood yourself when you can have a Dwarven Sphere do it for you?</i></p> 
<p>The new Dwarven Sphere Chop customized action will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from June 6, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to June 10, 2024 at 10AM EDT. </p> 
<h2>Pets</h2> 
<p><b>Meridian Sabre Cub </b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/0f8e9fadeb76724c34a4b146aa0b66f1.jpg" />
<p><i>"Our Lady of the Infinite Energies, Strict but Fair Arbiter of Inner Luminance, grant unto thy most devoted worshiper a sign of thy radiant favor, mayhap a loveable, glowing Sabre Cat cub."—Sayings of Valasha</i></p> 
<p>The Meridian Sabre Cub pet will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from June 10, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to June 13, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<h2>Upgrades</h2> 
<p><b>West Weald Skyshards</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/d7c9297e78597f96344505352591dc22.jpg" />
<p><i>Instantly unlocks the remaining Skyshards in West Weald.</i></p> 
<p>The West Weald Skyshards will be available in the Crown Store with the launch of <i>Gold Road </i>and Update 42 coming June 3, 2024 for PC/Mac, and on June 18, 2024 for Xbox One, Xbox Series X|S, PlayStation 4, and PlayStation 5.</p><p><br></p> 
<p>It seems the <i>Gold Road </i>Chapter isn't the only exciting thing coming to <i>ESO</i> this month! Whether you plan to thwart Daedric plots alongside the Leramil the Wise, bust heads with the Undaunted, or simply get away from it all with a high seas cruise, there's something for you in the Crown Store this June. </p> 
<p>Don't forget, if you wish to acquire any of the above items, you will need to stock up on crowns via the <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/crowns">Buy Crowns page</a> first. Do you have your eye on any of these new or returning items? Let us know via <a name="_Hlk159602221"></a><a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>. </p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Crown Store</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/962fd2536f72aa7754c0cf804b2ed8c0327363.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Crown Store Gifting Update – October 2023]]></title>
            <link>https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/644559/crown-store-gifting-update-october-2023</link>
            <guid>https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/644559/crown-store-gifting-update-october-2023</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 20:22:11 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[Following up on Studio Director Matt Firor's message last month about the <a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/643289/update-on-current-and-future-status-of-gifting">current and future status of Crown Store Gifting</a>, we are moving forward with re-enabling this functionality for eligible players at the account level. In this post, we will detail what to expect.<br><br>
In September, we temporarily disabled Crown Store gifting due to a rapidly growing issue of "bad actors" using various fraudulent means to amass crowns without paying for them, then using them in turn to sell Crown Store items to players for real-world cash outside of the game client. That said, we recognize that gifting is a meaningful part of our community, and we are in the process of manually re-enabling Crown Store gifting access for select players who meet our specific criteria. This work will be complete tomorrow, October 11, during the maintenance window from 09:00 AM ET to 12:00 PM ET.<br><br>
Gifting eligibility is determined by an evolving list of factors including but not limited to the account being at least 180 days past its first login and previous engagement with in-game features. You may check if you have access to gifting in-game via the Crown Store as well as via <a href="https://account.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/account/billing/billing-history">your billing history page</a> in the ESO account center. If you have access to Crown Store gifting, you will see "Allow Crown Store Gifting" in your billing history. If you try to send a gift via the in-game Crown Store and do not have access, you will see a "Gifting Locked" pop-up message. Please note that we are exploring better ways to display this information in-game in the future, such as updating the Gifting Tutorial.<br><br>
If you do not have access to Crown Store gifting after it is re-enabled on October 11, 2023, and wish for a review of your account, please visit <a href="https://help.elderscrollsonline.com">https://help.elderscrollsonline.com</a> and submit a Customer Support ticket. Please choose the Billing / Purchase / Code category then Platform &gt; I have a question about a sale / offer &gt; I want to send gift items from this account.<br><br>
We appreciate everyone's understanding and patience while we get this solution up and running. Multiple teams have worked long hours to evaluate the best technical solutions that we could stand up in a reasonably short time, while also prioritizing the Crown Store gifting player experience. We are dedicated to continuing to explore ways to make this better and reduce fraudulent activity in ESO. Thanks again for being a part of our community and for your continued support.]]></content:encoded>
            <category>Forum</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[New Patcher Rollout]]></title>
            <link>https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/642066/new-patcher-rollout</link>
            <guid>https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/642066/new-patcher-rollout</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 20:49:19 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[Hello everyone! After plenty of testing <a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en-gb/discussion/632782/new-eso-launcher-testing-and-launch-plan-pc-and-mac">during the last PTS period</a>, we are pleased to announce the rollout of our new patcher on the live servers for PC/Mac. The rollout of the new patcher will happen in four phases, with new countries being added during each phase. As we give countries access to the new patcher, we will make note of it in the list below by noting next to the country name (has the new patcher.) We will also note what phase we are currently in by specifying whether it has not started, in progress, or complete, next to the phase number. The countries getting the patcher are listed in order below.<br><br>
Thanks for your patience as we roll this out to all countries listed below. A special thanks to everyone who helped test out the launcher during the last PTS and provided feedback.<br><br>
Edit for 3/4/2024: All phases have now been complete.<br><br><b>Phase 1 (Complete) </b>
<ol><li>Netherlands (Has the new patcher)</li>
<li>Sweden (Has the new patcher)</li>
<li>Czech Republic/ Finland (Has the new patcher)</li>
<li>Norway/ Denmark (Has the new patcher)</li>
<li>Hungary/ Switzerland/ Romania (Has the new patcher)</li>
</ol><br><b>Phase 2 (Complete) </b>
<ol><li>Poland (Has the new patcher)</li>
<li>Spain/ Turkey (Has the new patcher)</li>
<li>Italy/ Austria/ Belgium/ Portugal/ Greece/ Ireland (Has the new patcher)</li>
</ol><br><b>Phase 3 (Complete) </b>
<ol><li>United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland/ France (Has the new patcher)</li>
<li>Germany (Has the new patcher)</li>
<li>United States of America (Has the new patcher)</li>
</ol><br><b>Phase 4 (Complete) </b><br>
This phase will encompass all other countries where ESO is available, that are not listed above. (All countries where ESO is available now have access to the launcher.)<br><br><b>Known Issues</b>
<ul><li>Some Czech Republic players may not have their country recognized, thus making them unable to upgrade the patch at this time. We are aware of the issue and working toward a solution.</li>
<li>Audio issues with sound volume and sound effects. We have a bug in for this and are working on a fix for the future.</li>
</ul>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>Forum</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>