<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>ESO Announcements</title>
        <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/</link>
        <description>Combined ESO blog and forum post announcements feed</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>Magic</generator>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hack at Horrors and Harrow Hollowjack Himself as the Witches Festival Returns]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66853</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66853</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Face down the horrors of Tamriel, including Lord Hollowjack himself, for special in-game rewards during 2024's Witches Festival in-game event!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/10/4280e902d3771c04640124ffe367e184.jpg" /><p><i>Face down the horrors of Tamriel, including Lord Hollowjack himself, for special in-game rewards during 2024's Witches Festival in-game event!</i></p> 
<p>This year's Witches Festival begins next Thursday, October 24 and runs until Wednesday, November 6 at 10AM EST. During this spoopy seasonal event, you can claim ghoulishly good event-specific rewards including Plunder Skulls, XP boosts, Event Tickets, and more!</p> 
<p>During the Witches Festival, all adventurers will enjoy a passive 100% boost to XP gain at all times. However, the Witchmother's Whistle, once the source of this bonus (and a skeletal transformation!), is still available. To collect the whistle and down ladles of hag's brew for frightful fun, simply follow the steps listed below:</p><ul><li>Open the Crown Store and acquire the free quest “The Witchmother's Bargain.”</li><ul><li>You can also pick up this quest by speaking with the Crow Caller, who you'll find outside of each Olyve's Brewery in Stonefalls, Glenumbra, or Auridon.</li></ul><li>Complete the introductory quest to receive the Witchmother's Whistle tool.</li><ul><li>You won't need to acquire the Witchmother's Whistle if you finished the quest in a previous year's event.</li></ul><li>Blow the whistle to summon the “Witchmother's Cauldron,” from which you can drink to polymorph yourself into a spooky scary skeleton.</li><ul><li>You cannot summon the Cauldron in Cyrodiil.</li></ul></ul>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/10/991d1046fcd318cc37e6a3c7474bb240.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Drink the witches' brew straight from the cauldron</i></p> 
<h2>A Wicked Harvest</h2> 
<p>During the Witches Festival event, whenever you defeat a boss monster, you'll be offered a Plunder Skull container in addition to any regular rewards.</p> 
<p>When you open a Plunder Skull, you have the chance to receive the following items:</p> 
<ul><li>Alchemy reagents</li><ul><li>A festival-themed furnishing recipe</li><li>A festival-themed provisioning recipe</li><li>A complete festival-themed furnishing</li><li>A festival-themed sellable treasure</li></ul><li>A small chance for one of the following:</li><ul><li>A Hollowjack style item</li><li>A Dremora style item</li></ul><li>Worms, Crawlers, Guts, or Insect Parts</li></ul> 
<p>What's more, whenever you fell a unique boss type for the first time each day, you'll be rewarded instead with a special Dremora Plunder Skull that contains some of the above items in addition to a chance at one of the following:</p> 
<ul><li>A Witches Festival Writ</li><li>A Glenmoril Treasure Map</li><li>A Glenmoril armor outfit style page</li><li>A Crowborne Hunter outfit style page</li><li><b>NEW </b>Plunder Skull Blunder Memento Runebox</li><li><b>NEW </b>Senchal Horned Owl pet fragment</li><li><b>NEW </b>tradeable style page for the Eltheric Revenant outfit style</li></ul> 
<p>Both varieties of Plunder Skull are offered by arena bosses, incursion bosses (from Dark Anchors, Harrowstorms, Volcanic Vents, etc.), delve bosses, final dungeon bosses, Trial bosses, public dungeon bosses, world bosses, and Tho'at Replicanum in Infinite Archive (new for this year!).</p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/10/2214c2af9555ae05cfeb6d375a6b7eba.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Perilous plunder, yours for the taking</i></p> 
<p>There are two additional Plunder Skulls acquirable by those brave (or foolish) enough to face the worst of the Witches Festival's horrors. </p> 
<p>The first of these frightful fiends, the Crowborne Horror, returns to Tamriel to bedevil its denizens. To locate and slay this living nightmare, acquire the daily quest “Plucking the Crow” by speaking with Witchmother Taerma, located inside Olyve's Brewery and at every Impresario tent found throughout Tamriel.</p> 
<p>For your courage, the first time you overcome the Crowborne Horror and turn in your quest each day, you'll be rewarded with a Dremora Plunder Skull. This creepy container has a small chance to grant you an incredible offering of tradeable Witches Festival valuables instead of regular Dremora Plunder Skull items, including:</p> 
<ul><li>The FULL style book for the Dremora motif</li><li>A folio of ALL Glenmoril treasure maps</li><li>All 10 Senchal Horned Owl Pet Fragments</li><li>Runebox: Plunder Skull Blunder</li><li>All of the Eltheric Revenant Outfit style pages</li></ul> 
<p>If even the Crowborne Horror does not daunt you, you may test that fearlessness against the master of monstrosity and sovereign of spookiness, Lord Hollowjack himself. You can acquire the quest to challenge him from the Priest Maxien, located inside Olyve's Brewery. Once you've completed this quest at least once on a given character, you can take it again on subsequent days and skip ahead to challenge Hollowjack directly.</p> 
<p>Should you emerge victorious against the Daedric Lord, you'll find the quest reward each day grants a special Dremora Plunder Skull unique to Lord Hollowjack. It has a chance to contain a jackpot like that from the Crowborne Horror, and it awards a special achievement and trophy furnishing to commemorate your victory. A matching collectible bust furnishing can sometimes be acquired from looting Lord Hollowjack.</p> 
<h2>Impresario &amp; Event Tickets</h2> 
<p>During the Witches Festival, you can collect two Event Tickets from the first boss you defeat each day, earning up to 28 tickets by the end of the event. But don't forget: You can only hold up to 12 Event Tickets at a time.</p> 
<p>For this event, the Impresario will stock the following items:</p> 
<ul><li>All three Molag Bal Illusion Imp pet fragments:</li> <ul><li>Anchor Chain Fragment</li> <li>Dark Anchor Pinion</li> <li>Effigy of the Dominator</li> </ul><li>The first two fragments for the Haven of the Five Companions house:</li> <ul><li>Varen Aquilarios's Key</li> <li>Lyris Titanborn's Key</li> </ul><li>Eltheric Revenant outfit style</li> <li>Senchal Horned Owl pet fragments</li> <li>Assorted spooky Witches Festival-themed furnishings</li> <ul><li>Webs, Cone furnishing</li> <li>Hollowjack Lantern, Ouroboros furnishing</li> <li>Specimen Jar, Spare Brain furnishing</li> <li>Ruby Candlefly Gathering furnishing</li> <li>Vampiric Lamp, Azure Tall furnishing</li> <li>Vampiric Lightpost, Azure Single furnishing</li> <li>Vampiric Container, Yellow Liquid furnishing</li> </ul><li>Group Repair Kit</li> <li>Companion Guild Commendations</li> <li>Witches Grab Bag <b>(This is purchasable only if you haven't yet collected all the items contained within)</b></li> <ul><li>Skeletal Marionette memento</li> <li>Spectre Mask collectible</li> <ul type="square"><li>There are four variations of this collectible</li> </ul><li>Apple-Bobbing Cauldron fragment</li> <li>Throw Bones memento fragment</li> <li>Marshmallow Toasty Treat emote</li> <li>Witch's Bonfire Dust</li> <li>Ghastly Visitation memento</li> <li>Witch-Tamed Bear-Dog pet fragment</li> <li>Witchmother's Servant outfit style pages</li> <li>Tome of Forbidden Appetites memento</li> <li>Ghost Netch pet</li> <li>Grave Dancer Weapon style pages</li> </ul></ul> 
<p>Of note: The Witches Festival will be your first opportunity to begin gathering the fragments for the final event morphing collectible of 2024, the Haven of the Five Companions house!</p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/10/97dea21c97fb3c7b4e1acf590083b989.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center; "><i>Haven of the Five Companions morphing collectible</i></p> 
<p>Additionally, the Impresario's colleague, Nenulaure the Indrik Vendor, has the following items available for purchase using Event Tickets:</p> 
<ul><li>Nascent Indrik Feathers</li> <li>Pure Snow Indrik Berries</li> <li>Crimson Indrik Berries</li> <li>Frost-Light Indrik pet</li> <li>Rosethorn Indrik pet</li> </ul> 
<p>Lastly, the Impresario's Assistant is offering the following, which you can acquire with Event Tickets:</p> 
<ul><li>All three Unstable Morpholith fragments</li> <ul><li>Deadlands Flint</li> <li>Rune-Etched Striker</li> <li>Smoldering Bloodgrass Tinder</li> </ul><li>All three Dagonic Quasigriff fragments</li> <ul><li>Smoke-Wreathed Gryphon Feather</li> <li>Black Iron Bit</li> <li>Bridle Black Iron Stirrups</li> </ul></ul> 
<ul><li>All three Soulfire Dragon Illusion Imp pet fragments</li> <ul><li>Hallowed Hourglass Basin</li> <li>Illuminated Dragon Scroll</li> <li>Kvatchian Incense</li> </ul></ul> 
<ul><li>All three fragments for the Daggerfall Paladin outfit</li><ul><li>Blessed Rubedite Enamel</li><li>Captured Dragonflame</li><li>Sanctified Metalworking Tools</li></ul></ul> 
<p>It's Tamriel's most frightful time of year, and only brave heroes can bring light to the shadows of the season. Will you step up to strike down Lord Hollowjack? You'll be rewarded with XP boosts, collectibles, and other boons for your efforts during the 2024 Witches Festival in-game event. Share your spooky stories with us via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>. </p> 
<p><i>The Witches Festival in-game event begins Thursday, October 24 at 10AM EDT, and runs until Wednesday, November 6 at 10AM EST.</i></p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Events</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/10/4280e902d3771c04640124ffe367e184.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Discover Bonus Rewards When Venturing Across Tamriel during the Explorer's Celebration]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66809</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66809</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Make the most out of buffs to XP and more during the Explorer's Celebration in-game event!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/10/9e63d34ac3dbadf1ad8dbe5b1fed0b55.jpg" /><p><i>Make the most out of buffs to XP and more during the Explorer's Celebration in-game event!</i></p><p>The #ESOFam completed an immense number of quests during the <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/fallenleaves">Fallen Leaves of West Weald</a> event. Now, it's time to reap the rewards! Starting today, October 8 at 10AM EDT, you can enjoy bonus rewards (almost) anywhere in Tamriel during the limited-time Explorer's Celebration in-game event.</p><p>During the event, you can gain bonuses from the following sources:</p><ul><li>Increased drops from harvest nodes (this does not include fishing or creature drops such as leather)</li><li>+100% XP gains from every source</li><ul><li>These bonuses stack with other XP boosts such as scrolls or group multipliers</li></ul><li>+100% gold earned from monster kills, quest rewards, and similar sources</li></ul><p>The bonuses listed above are available to all <i>ESO</i> players in any zone across Tamriel and beyond! </p><p>Keep in mind that the Explorer's Celebration event doesn't feature Event Tickets or unique quests, and there aren't any special collectibles or achievements to gather. Additionally, the Impresario has decided to take some time off work, so her shop is not open for business during this event.</p><p>This Explorer's Celebration wouldn't have happened without the hard work put forth by the <i>ESO</i> community during the <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/fallenleaves">Fallen Leaves of West Weald</a> event, so be sure to enjoy the fruits of your labors! </p><p>Speaking of rewards, you have until October 18 to claim your Fallen Leaves of West Weald prizes free from the Crown Store. Don't forget, you need access to the <i>Gold Road</i> Chapter to claim them—don't miss out!</p><p> </p><p><i>The Explorer's Celebration runs from Tuesday, October 8 at 10AM EDT, until Thursday, October 17 at 10AM EDT. </i></p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Events</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/10/9e63d34ac3dbadf1ad8dbe5b1fed0b55.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Seek Ayleid Relics to Unlock Rewards during the Fallen Leaves of West Weald Event]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66731</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66731</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Delve into the history of the Heartland elves and unlock special rewards for all Gold Road players during a new event!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/6253fe1592c434ba342735c098e603e6.jpg" /><p><i>Delve into the history of the Heartland elves and unlock special rewards for all Gold Road players during a new event!</i></p><p><i><br></i></p><p> </p> <p><b>Challenge complete!</b> <i>Gold Road</i> Chapter players can now claim the Fallen Leaves of West Weald Reward Bundle free from the in-game Crown Store until Friday, October 18 at 10AM EDT—don't miss out!</p><p><br></p><p>The Fallen Leaves of West Weald in-game event kicks off on Thursday, September 26 at 10AM EDT and continues until Tuesday, October 8. During the event, you can seek out lost relics of the ancient Ayleid empire, learn about the history surrounding Cyrodiil's ancient rulers, and unlock collectible rewards for ALL <i>Gold Road</i> Chapter owners. </p> <h2>Seek Lost Knowledge, Together!</h2> <p>Throughout the event period, you can acquire the new daily quest, “Fallen Leaves of West Weald,” available from Gandrinar, located outside the Skingrad Impresario's tent. To complete this new daily, collect lost Ayleid relics, bundle them, and bring them back to Gandrinar. Doing so will grant event quest rewards (and on occasion, some additional lore about the region's ancient rulers), in addition to progressing the Fallen Leaves of West Weald meter, found on the <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/fallenleaves">event's official page</a>. </p> <p>As the community completes the new daily quest, they help progress a new event meter, unlocking three tiers of rewards:</p> <ul><li>33%—Vineyard Voriplasm pet</li><li>66% —Luminescing Varla Stone memento</li><li>100%—Russet Brekka mount, Tree-Sap Legion arms pack, and a nesting rewards box </li></ul>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/3c1a54c350bddc00784efdb8f3d12c41.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Unlock these event rewards</i></p> 
<p>When the event ends on October 8 (or as soon the meter reaches 100%), the community can claim all unlocked rewards free from the in-game Crown Store for a limited time. Note that these rewards can be unlocked and claimed ONLY by <i>Gold Road</i> Chapter players, so if you've yet to own <i>ESO</i>'s latest adventure, be sure to pick it up. </p> 
<p>Be sure to visit the official <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/fallenleaves">Fallen Leaves of West Weald page</a> often to check the community's progress and see what rewards have been unlocked. </p> 
<p><b>Bonus Explorer's Celebration</b></p> 
<p>In addition to the event's main meter and rewards, you and your fellow players can also unlock additional days of the subsequent Explorer's Celebration event by completing ANY quests within the West Weald zone. </p> 
<p>For every 33% of the bonus meter completed (also found on the <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/fallenleaves">official event page</a>), we'll enable three days of the Explorer's Celebration. This bonus mini-event kicks off as soon as the Fallen Leaves of West Weald event ends on October 8 and grants additional XP, Gold, and resource harvesting for everybody in Tamriel during the event period. </p> 
<h2>Earn Coffers While Adventuring</h2> 
<p>While the event (and community chase) is ongoing, you can receive a <b>special Sublime Fallen Leaves Coffer</b> for the first West Weald zone daily quest you complete each day AND then earn <b>regular Fallen Leaves Coffers</b> for various activities after. </p> 
<p>Note that you can also acquire regular Fallen Leaves Coffers by defeating bosses and monsters, harvesting resource nodes, pickpocketing, or opening treasure chests, safeboxes, psijic portals, Thieves Troves, or other lootable objects within West Weald. </p> 
<p>Fallen Leaves Coffers can contain the following items: </p> 
<ul><li>A chance for random crafting materials </li><li>A chance for a <i>Gold Road</i> saleable treasure</li><li>A chance for a style item for <i>Gold Road</i> motifs</li><li>A chance for a <i>Gold Road</i> overland set item</li><li>A chance for Companion gear (with any Companion unlocked) </li><li>A chance for one of the following</li><ul><li><i>Gold Road</i> furnishings </li><li><i>Gold Road</i> furnishing recipe </li><li><i>Gold Road</i> Treasure Map or Survey Report</li><li><i>Gold Road</i> motif page </li></ul><li>A small chance for a tradeable style page of the new Tree-Sap Legion armor style. </li></ul> 
<p>Note that the once-daily Sublime Fallen Leaves Coffer has a higher chance of containing the above rewards than the regular one, but there's no limit to the number of regular coffers you can earn in a single day. </p>
<a href="https://youtube.com/v/IFhXEeO_g88?autoplay=1&rel=0"><img src="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/IFhXEeO_g88/maxresdefault.jpg" /></a>
<p><b>Additional Rewards </b></p> 
<p>As you collect coffers during the event, you can also enjoy the following bonuses within West Weald: </p> 
<ul><li>Zone daily quests and Trial weekly quests (Lucent Citadel) award double non-event reward boxes</li><li>Harvest node yields within <i>Gold Road</i> are increased (not including fishing holes)</li><li><i>Gold Road</i> world bosses, public dungeon bosses, Trial bosses, and delve bosses all award double loot</li></ul> 
<h2>Impresario &amp; Event Tickets</h2> 
<p>During the Fallen Leaves of West Weald event, you can earn two Event Tickets per day by completing Gandrinar's quest, any zone daily quest, or the Lucent Citadel weekly quest. In addition, the Impresario will stock the following items: </p> 
<ul><li>All three <b>Molag Bal Illusion Imp </b>pet fragments </li><ul><li>Anchor Chain Fragment</li><li>Dark Anchor Pinion</li><li>Effigy of the Dominator</li></ul><li>All three <b>Anchorborn Welwa</b> mount fragments</li><ul><li>Bizarre Daedric Meat</li><li>Fine Ebonsteel Chain</li><li>Strengthened Welwa Muzzle</li></ul><li>Bound style pages for the Tree-Sap Legion style </li><li>Group Repair Kits </li><li>Companion Guild Commendations</li></ul> 
<p>This is your chance to complete the fearsome Anchorborn Welwa mount! </p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/af0386db601ae6d77643abe680d4f866.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Anchorborn Welwa mount</i></p> 
<p>At the same time, the Impresario's Assistant will stock the following goods:</p> 
<ul><li>All three Unstable Morpholith pet fragments</li><ul><li>Deadlands Flint</li><li>Rune-Etched Striker</li><li>Smoldering Bloodgrass Tinder</li></ul><li>All three Deadlands Firewalker personality fragments</li><ul><li>Vial of Simmering Daedric Brew</li><li>Vial of Bubbling Daedric Brew</li><li>Vial of Scalding Daedric Brew</li></ul><li>All three Soulfire Dragon Illusion Imp pet fragments</li><ul><li>Hallowed Hourglass Basin</li><li>Illuminated Dragon Scroll</li><li>Kvatchian Incense</li></ul><li>All three Aurelic Quasigriff mount fragments</li><ul><li>Aurelite Gryphon Feather</li><li>Gilded Gryphon Barding</li><li>Sacred Seeds of Akatosh</li></ul></ul><p>Finally, the Indrik vendor will have Nascent Indrik Feathers, Onyx Indrik Berries, Mossheart Indrik Berries, the Ebon-Glow Indrik pet, and the Sapling Indrik pet—phew!</p> 
<h2>Return to Gold Road</h2> 
<p>Scour West Weald for the remnants of the Heartland elves and you can help your fellow players unlock rewards for all <i>Gold Road</i> Chapter owners. Are you excited to return to this autumnal Imperial region? Let us know if you're excited for the Fallen Leaves of West Weald event via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, or <a href="https://www.facebook.com/ElderScrollsOnline">Facebook</a>, and don't forget to check the community's progress on the <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/fallenleaves">official event page</a>! </p> 
<p><i>The Fallen Leaves of West Weald in-game event begins Thursday, September 26 from 10AM EDT, and runs until Tuesday, October 8 at 10AM EDT. </i></p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Events</category>
            <category>Gold Road</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/6253fe1592c434ba342735c098e603e6.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Crown Store Showcase—October 2024]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66779</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66779</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Get your ghastly goodies from the Crown Store this October and prepare to summon the spooky season.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/f0c3a6b4025ebb06f5672a8733a6e2e2.jpg" /><p><i>Get your ghastly goodies from the Crown Store this October and prepare to summon the spooky season.</i></p> <p>Feast your eyes on the ghoulish, the grotesque, the grim, and all manner of other goods besides. On this dread page we feature the most fearful—and desirable—goods to find in all Tamriel, in the form of all the items that will be available in the in-game Crown Store throughout October 2024. </p> <p>You may also check out what's currently available by visiting the <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/crownstore">Crown Store page</a>. Anything catch your eye? Be sure to visit the <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/buycrowns">Buy Crowns page</a> to acquire however many crowns you need! Certain items and offers are available for a limited time only, so be sure to read their details below and don't miss out.</p><p><b>Update: </b>This Crown Store Showcase initially listed the Crown Crafting Motifs for the Blind Path Cultist and The Recollection crafting styles as limited time offers, as well as listing the Volkihar Death Hound for the period of October 7 to October 10. This has been corrected, as the motifs in question will remain in the Crown Store from the dates listed until further notice, and the Volkihar Death Hound will be in the Crown Store from October 10 to October 14. Thank you for your understanding!<br></p> <h2>ESO Plus Deals</h2> <p>All ESO Plus™ members have access to a monthly selection of exclusive deals and items. You can find more information about them in <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/54825">this article</a>.</p> <p><b>Exclusive Free Items</b></p> <p><b>Painting: Oathsworn Pit</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/3cd5b4e0a29547f55b4127cf4b4ff88b.jpg" />
<p><i>A painting of Oathsworn Pit, where followers of Malacath train in three different forms of combat.</i></p> 
<p>Painting: Oathsworn Pit will be available in the Crown Store FREE, exclusively to ESO Plus Members on all platforms for a limited time, from October 3, 2024 at 10 AM EDT, to November 20, 2024 at 10 AM EST.</p> 
<h2>Crown Gem and Seals of Endeavor Items</h2> 
<p><b>Bonfire Wicker-Steed</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/a72ec3470f6c7a30033f60a0a3aeb17f.jpg" />
<p><i>Woe to any who ride this fiery steed without its consent! Sanctified by ashes from the funeral pyres of venerated witches, this wicker steed blazes a path across Tamriel and beyond, reminding any mortals who see it of their own short lifespans.</i></p> 
<p>The Bonfire Wicker-Steed mount will be available for Crown Gems and Seals of Endeavor on all platforms for a limited time, from October 3, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to October 17, 2024 at 10AM EDT.</p> 
<h2>Crafting</h2> 
<p><b>Crown Crafting Motif: Kindred's Concord </b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/86f3b0cce3cd92084b89fd4688239ea1.jpg" />
<p><i>High Priest Blightcrown writes of those using this style, "Many of you are entrusted with duties that require you to move without notice among the scoffers and persecutors of our world." Use to learn the Kindred's Concord crafting style. </i></p> 
<p>The Crown Crafting Motif: Kindred's Concord Style returns to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 7, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to October 10, 2024 at 10AM EDT. The Kindred's Concord chapters, and very rarely the complete book, have a chance to drop from Bastion Nymic and Bastion Nymic Coffers, awarded from Ordinator Tandasea in Necrom.</p> 
<p><b>Crown Crafting Motif: Blind Path Cultist</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/88816444446e56c9ab1cfe5499ae37b9.jpg" />
<p><i>Camp Prefect Acilius Hayn writes of this style, "It is frustrating to admit that the crystalline material used extensively on this armor eludes many of the standard testing methodologies I've brought to bear. It is clearly some form of creatia but formed and latticed in a manner I've never seen before." Use to learn the Blind Path Cultist crafting style.</i></p> 
<p>The new Crown Crafting Motif: Blind Path Cultist will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms, from October 10, 2024 at 10AM EDT. Blind Path Cultists chapters, and very rarely the complete book, have a chance to drop from the Blind in Bedlam Veil. Harder difficulties will increase the chances of the style pages dropping.</p> 
<p><b>Crown Crafting Motif: The Recollection</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/574e3affff389484772a28665d8e66b7.jpg" />
<p><i>The Bosmer in the Recollection, who are dedicated to a forgotten Daedric Prince, designed standardized equipment to help them better face challenges. Use to learn the Recollection crafting style.</i></p> 
<p>The new Crown Crafting Motif: The Recollection will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms, from October 24, 2024 at 10AM EDT. The Recollection chapters, and very rarely the complete book, have a chance to drop from Aradros the Awakened in the Oathsworn Pit. Harder difficulties will increase the chances of the style pages dropping.</p> 
<p><b>Outfit Style</b></p> 
<p><b>Scourge Harvester Arms Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/4fcf71b27ceb27c9ba47b522656d4ba4.jpg" />
<p><i>Malubeth the Scourger attacks any Undaunted who dare confront Master Pellingare in Wayrest's sewers. Alter your weapon's appearance to match the Undaunted Scourge Harvester awards by using this complete set of Outfit styles.</i></p> 
<p>The Scourge Harvester Arms Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 7, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to October 10, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item. The matching mask page will have a small chance to drop from Varaine or Allene Pellingare from Veteran Wayrest Sewers II. The matching shoulder page can be purchased from Maj al-Ragath for 50 undaunted keys, or has a chance of dropping from Maj's Mystery Coffer for 1 key. Having the achievement “Pellingare Ghoul Slayer” increases the drop chances of both items.</p> 
<p><b>Crowborne Hunter Arms Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/1543113cdd1156173a72cdb9761ddd4b.jpg" />
<p><i>Sergeant Qasim of Evermore notes, "The combination of fastidious detail work and exquisite balance on these weapons make them perfect for any seeking a more shiveringly totemic look as they hunt." Alter your weapon's appearance by using this complete set of Crowborne Hunter Outfit styles.</i></p> 
<p>The Crowborne Hunter Arms Pack returns to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 17, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to October 21, 2024 at 10AM EDT. Matching armor pages will have a small chance to drop from Plunder Skulls. Bound versions of the armor pages can be purchased from the Impresario for 5 Event Tickets each during the Witches Festival event.</p> 
<p><b>Maarselok Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/95fa5e0bef0eaeda528d9218edbecae4.jpg" />
<p><i> Summon your most stalwart companions to face the Dragon Maarselok in his lair and prevent him from corrupting the Changeling Selene. Then, perhaps, celebrate your victory by altering your weapon's appearance to match the Undaunted Maarselok awards by using this complete set of Outfit styles.</i></p> 
<p>The Maarselok Arms Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 21, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to October 24, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item. The matching mask page will have a small chance to drop from the eponymous boss from Veteran Lair of Maarselok. The matching shoulder page can be purchased from Urgarlag Chief-bane for 50 undaunted keys, or has a chance of dropping from Urgarlag's Mystery Coffer for 1 key. Having the achievement “Selene's Savior” increases the drop chances of both items.</p> 
<p><b>Sentinel Regal Guard Armor Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/b3bc039490c2121adc98da4469b1d1b3.jpg" />
<p><i>Basila of Sentinel notes, “You can see elements of the Phyllocid Dynasty in the gear of the royal guards of Sentinel. I approve.” Alter your armor's appearance by using this complete set of Sentinel Regal Guard Outfit styles.</i></p> 
<p>The new Sentinel Regal Guard Armor Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 31, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to November 7, 2024 at 10AM EST. </p> 
<h2>Adornment</h2> 
<p><b>Skull Face Tattoo Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/45b503ac01afeff5ac86524cdcb05847.jpg" />
<p><i>Face marking bundle including the Verdant, Floral, and Spoked Skull Face Tattoos.</i></p> 
<p>The Skull Face Tattoo Pack adornment will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 31, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to November 4, 2024 at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<h2>Wardrobe</h2> 
<p><b>Costumes</b></p> 
<p><b>Toxin Doctor</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/228ed7adb818292c7a7cb978a9ef22b8.jpg" />
<p><i>When you specialize in venoms and poison-making, you invest in special protective garb to keep from being poisoned by your own experiments—or else! And if your clients are just a little intimidated by your creepy attire, all the better.</i></p> 
<p>The Toxin Doctor costume will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 3, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to October 7, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<p><b>Za'ji's Sailing Apparel</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/6e58f6d4f2ff6c3d8f105d1c9d7b6eca.jpg" />
<p><i>"Say what you want about Za'ji, but he has style. His uniform gets more elaborate every time I see him. You can always tell when he's visited a city since there's usually more than one person wearing something inspired by him."—Puurri, Dragonguard</i></p> 
<p>The Za'ji's Sailing Apparel costume will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 24, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to October 28, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<p><b>Tribal Shamans Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/c378af494250e29bb37c07d7f500329a.jpg" />
<p><i>A costume pack that offers three variations of a mystic tribal spellcaster.</i></p> 
<p>The Tribal Shamans Pack costume will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 28, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to October 31, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<p><b>Dark Shaman</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/ee7dc84a023d1d6f1d27b7272a4e7450.jpg" />
<p><i>Far from town, temple, and market, those of ill intent meet in secret conclave to importune the forces of darkness for power and mastery. Behold here the dire raiment they don for this fell purpose.</i></p> 
<p>The Dark Shaman costume will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 31, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to November 4, 2024 at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<p><b>Hats</b></p> 
<p><b>Moonshadow Wings Mask</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/2a89cae7fe04223cebfea2ea2a716402.jpg" />
<p><i>The Lepidopterans are a sect of Azura cultists who conceal their features with elaborate butterfly masks. These have recently become a fad among the jaded youth of mainland Morrowind—and now you can wear one, too!</i></p> 
<p>The Moonshadow Wings Mask hat will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 14, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to October 17, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<p><b>Icereach Masks Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/87d6aa7f36918cc9e84dfbce7ed3d31d.jpg" />
<p><i>Join the witches of Icereach by donning the visages of necromancer Bani and cryomancer Gohlla. Handcrafted during the darkest hours of the night, these masks make manifest the wicked spirits of those two coven leaders.</i></p> 
<p>The Icereach Masks Pack hat will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 28, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to October 31, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<p><b>Floral Skull Fascinator</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/41d9e68e2c79aef9f637521590c9b58a.jpg" />
<p><i>Flowers! For your head! Flaunt your colorful style with this hat, and bring floral joy to everyone around you.</i></p> 
<p>The Floral Skull Fascinator hat will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 31, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to November 4, 2024 at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<h2>Crown Crate</h2> 
<p><b>Hollowjack Crate</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/5bad25b611015e543c1ff916b22adead.jpg" />
<p><i>A mystery collection of Hollowjack-related items!</i></p> 
<p>Hollowjack Crates will return to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 3, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to October 17, 2024 at 10AM EDT. </p> 
<p><b>New Moon Crate</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/30c44a18278f2fb9ee885cdf6313314c.jpg" />
<p><i>A mystery collection of New Moon items!</i></p> 
<p>New Moon Crates will return to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 17, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to October 31, 2024 at 10AM EDT. </p> 
<h2>Events </h2> 
<p><b>Currency</b></p> 
<p><b>Event Tickets</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/0bf70b83c90e00def052849c3db186f1.jpg" />
<p><i>A ticket used to purchase rare goods from The Impresario, Event Merchant. Curious as to what goods? Well, chat with her to see what she has to offer!</i></p> 
<p>Single Event Tickets will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time during the Witches Festival event, from October 24, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to November 6, 2024 at 10AM EST. Event Tickets are also giftable to other players from within the Crown Store. </p> 
<h2>Furniture </h2> 
<p><b>Furnishing Pack: Hollowjack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/537fbadeae54eac6708ad78f3a818c04.jpg" />
<p><i>Lanterns lure and pumpkins trip</i></p> 
<p><i>Webs ensnare and grave hands grip</i></p> 
<p><i>Crows will mock as wraith-scythes hack</i></p> 
<p><i>All in thrall to Hollowjack!</i></p> 
<p>The Furnishing Pack: Hollowjack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 3, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to October 17, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<p><b>Furnishing Pack: Haunted Housewares</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/a6798c0065bf4abf2fb1073350473258.jpg" />
<p><i>A door that won't shut. A painting cursed by an ominous apparition. A broom that endlessly sweeps. Decorate your cherished haunt with these and other eerie furnishings, then relish the lived-in/died-in atmosphere you've imbued with restless spirits!</i></p> 
<p>The new Furnishing Pack: Haunted Housewares will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 10, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to October 31, 2024 at 10AM EDT.</p> 
<p><b>Target Harrowing Reaper, Trial</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/e11c95f8f4901131308b069ef5cf8726.jpg" />
<p><i>This is a large house item. This may be attacked and, when destroyed, will regenerate. This creature is equivalent to a veteran trial boss. Its abilities include granting a resource-restoring synergy opportunity, performance buffs, and self debuffs.</i></p> 
<p>The Target Harrowing Reaper, Trial will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 14, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to October 17, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<p><b>Furnishing Pack: Witches' Coven</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/048e42752105b21fef1a8446a6bfaa64.jpg" />
<p><i>Bring the moody atmosphere of Hag Fen to your home with these tools and trappings of the witch's trade. Whether brewing potent poisons or cooking cauldrons of questionable stew, craft in true coven style with the included alchemy and provisioning stations!</i></p> 
<p>The Furnishing Pack: Witches' Coven will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 24, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to November 6, 2024 at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<p><b>Music Box, The Ghosts of Frostfall </b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/2d7d64cfd4d9a28e40e148c93e97df35.jpg" />
<p><i>When activated, plays the music box composition "The Ghosts of Frostfall."</i></p> 
<p>The Music Box, The Ghosts of Frostfall returns to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 24, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to November 6, 2024 at 10AM EST.</p> 
<p><b>Music Box, Witchmother's Bubbling Brew</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/18ec97380dbfe1a5e7b435ffa13c2340.jpg" />
<p><i>"Pulp of pumpkin, dash of guts. Prep your cauldron, make your cuts. Capture death 'cause it's your due. Stir it all and then you're through." When activated, plays a music box arrangement of the macabre "Witchmother's Bubbling Brew" composition.</i></p> 
<p>The Music Box, Witchmother's Bubbling Brew returns to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 24, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to November 6, 2024 at 10AM EST.</p> 
<h2>Houses</h2> 
<p><b>Shadow Queen's Labyrinth</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/10a52277fb6907da4b06d52584895cf4.jpg" />
<p><i>A winding maze dominates the grounds of this twilight-enshrouded estate, creating endless opportunities to perplex visitors. The visceral awe evoked by Nocturnal's Evergloam skies provides an exquisite contrast to the spacious, Summerset-inspired home.</i></p> 
<p>The Shadow Queen's Labyrinth returns to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 10, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to October 24, 2024 at 10AM EDT. Furnished and unfurnished versions will be available.</p> 
<p><b>Exorcised Coven Cottage</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/c34910e561ab6df63a94824c9de8f7a8.jpg" />
<p><i>Pay no attention to the rumors: this witches hut on the edge of Hag Fen in Glenumbra is guaranteed NOT to be haunted by the dead, the undead, or restless spirits of any kind. It does come with tumbledown walls to keep the crocodiles and wolves out. Spooky!</i></p> 
<p>The Exorcised Coven Cottage returns to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 24, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to November 6, 2024 at 10AM EST. Furnished and unfurnished versions will be available.</p> 
<p><b>Wraithhome</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/36845c0863d2de9497f4a54cd17fa0dd.jpg" />
<p><i>With its pillars of skulls, stained glass, and ghostly portals, this abode can accommodate even the most tormented soul. Take advantage of its open layout to set up large-scale rituals, and use its vaults and lofty balconies for vile experiments.</i></p> 
<p>The Wraithhome returns to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 31, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to November 14, 2024 at 10AM EST. Furnished and unfurnished versions will be available.</p> 
<h2>Houseguests</h2> 
<p><b>Heiruna</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/22373a3a6b6fc5ba200609cba0e8dec6.jpg" />
<p><i>Oh, the ignominy of being an agent of justice trapped inside a small floating doll! Now Heiruna intends to plot vengeance—in your retreat. After adding Heiruna to your home, you can set her on a path, plus you and your visitors can speak with her.</i></p> 
<p>Heiruna returns to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 10, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to October 14, 2024 at 10AM EDT. </p> 
<h2>Mounts</h2> 
<p><b>Hollowjack Indrik</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/b4632f7a1e21dfcb601fd9781953039b.jpg" />
<p><i>"Twisted twigs, a scent of death, a dance amid the briars. A dash of howls and drip of gore starts sinister fires. Stir round with haunted bone, then call me with your screams. If I approve, a mount you gain to torment your foes' dreams."—Lord Hollowjack </i></p> 
<p>The Hollowjack Indrik mount returns to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 7, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to October 10, 2024 at 10AM EDT.</p> 
<p><b>Brimstone Death Hound</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/7048330df396f2231937010c1a3e1a40.jpg" />
<p><i>"Be careful! This beast is meaner than a durzog and hot as a fire atronach. The furnace in its chest gives it incredible power and an appetite to match. I can't remember when last this one was fed. Best not to find out."—Kallin, House Ravenwatch</i></p> 
<p>The new Brimstone Death Hound mount will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 10, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to October 14, 2024 at 10AM EDT. </p> 
<p><b>Black Senche-Panther</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/c94cf3adb037f3fc1e9df562a30b61d9.jpg" />
<p><i>A mount said to have been bred by Baandari Pedlars for ease in hastily leaving town after dark.</i></p> 
<p>The Black Senche-Panther mount will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 14, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to October 17, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<p><b>Mind-Shriven Horse</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/b957ff5d49b51a66b58a49e67d735689.jpg" />
<p><i>With its equine psyche stolen by Daedric magic, the mind-shriven horse is a docile yet terrifying mount.</i></p> 
<p>The Mind-Shriven Horse mount returns to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 14, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to October 17, 2024 at 10AM EDT.</p> 
<p><b>Black Bear</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/47f76247b2bea03ff0e48b118431ddbc.jpg" />
<p><i>The Black Bear is common across Cyrodiil, but is also seen north into High Rock and Skyrim, where it is considered a warrior's mount.</i></p> 
<p>The Black Bear mount will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 21, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to October 24, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<p><b>Reaper's End Quasigriff</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/772a306e5a5876cb9a633c3792e1b227.jpg" />
<p><i>Having been created through selective breeding and magic, quasigriffs have a penchant for absorbing any excess magicka they're exposed to. This stock was raised within the penumbral realms of Evergloam, as you can see.</i></p> 
<p>The new Reaper's End Quasigriff mount will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 24, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to October 31, 2024 at 10AM EDT.</p> 
<p><b>Clouded Senche-Leopard</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/c730075a2dfad8e3aabbd283d0744996.jpg" />
<p><i>A strong yet nimble mount, bred for hunting in the Tenmar forest.</i></p> 
<p>The Clouded Senche-Leopard mount returns to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 28, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to October 31, 2024 at 10AM EDT.</p> 
<p><b>Voideater Durzog</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/ee3ce267922c552279cde7217ef7ad41.jpg" />
<p><i>No one knows how these beasts found their way into Blackreach, but it didn't take long for them to heed the Dark Heart's call. Drenched in the void's corruption, this mount will chill your enemies to the bone.</i></p> 
<p>The Voideater Durzog mount returns to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 31, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to November 4, 2024 at 10AM EST.</p> 
<h2>Customized Actions</h2> 
<p><b>Grovetender's Sweep</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/e34f38fb330380aadef4493890b50688.jpg" />
<p><i>The druids of the Systres often use a blessed sickle to harvest plants and herbs. Why not give it a try yourself?</i></p> 
<p>The Grovetender's Sweep customized action returns to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 10, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to October 14, 2024 at 10AM EDT.</p> 
<h2>Polymorph</h2> 
<p><b>Werewolf Lord</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/8bd029a06c2d34c42b6092fb768dcf1c.jpg" />
<p><i>Wear Hircine's Gift with pride as the leader of the lycanthrope pack with the Werewolf Lord polymorph. Time to howl!</i></p> 
<p>The Werewolf Lord polymorph will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 7, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to October 10, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<p><b>Shadowsilk Goblin</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/17506a409953ec5ba75bc24db94ad5c8.jpg" />
<p><i>Feel left out? Alienated? Alone? Adopt the form of a Shadowsilk Goblin, and you might* find that sense of belonging you crave among these creatures! Fleas not included, but easily attainable. *Might is no guarantee. They may try to eat you instead.</i></p> 
<p>The Shadowsilk Goblin polymorph will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 10, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to October 14, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<p><b>Pumpkin Spectre</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/de48d51e651c1a38e5f0634ab16243a9.jpg" />
<p><i>A Pumpkin Spectre is like a horrific figure from a skooma-induced nightmare! And with this costume, the wearer can take on the semblance of these dread monsters.</i></p> 
<p>The Pumpkin Spectre polymorph will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 14, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to October 17, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<p><b>Reaper's End Scarecrow Spectre</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/e8a82a072a7a4c3f6ce0ba9f567749f2.jpg" />
<p><i>"Harvest's reaping brings out all sorts of ill-omened beings. I avoid that nonsense by looking like a scarecrow spectre animated by amethyst flames. An illusion, yes, but yours if you can handle the terror you'll inflict."—Othreloth Hlaalo, Illusionist</i></p> 
<p>The new Reaper's End Scarecrow Spectre polymorph will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 24, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to October 31, 2024 at 10AM EDT.</p> 
<h2>Pets</h2> 
<p><b>Skeletal Senche-Leopard</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/2bdc1cdb04ca1e17fec95a33cd7aef0a.jpg" />
<p><i>Is Necromancy always wrong? Not even death can stop this loyal senche-leopard from stalking to adventure at your side!</i></p> 
<p>The Skeletal Senche-Leopard pet will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 7, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to October 10, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<p><b>Volkihar Death Hound</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/e6db2ad5cc61360c08daf14ee734f4bd.jpg" />
<p><i>“Rarely do these inky black death hounds venture beyond Castle Volkihar—most serve their master's purpose at home better than abroad. The ones wandering after folk are probably some form of spy for the Volkihar vampires.”—Nalana, Advisor to House Tamrith</i></p> 
<p>The Volkihar Death Hound pet will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 10, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to October 14, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<p><b>Daedric Scamp</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/7fa38b4449a985949850c101be5a68da.jpg" />
<p><i>A foul-smelling Daedric minion, who will follow you loyally, though it won't fight for you.</i></p> 
<p>The Daedric Scamp pet will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 14, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to October 17, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<p><b>Shornhelm Shepherd</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/60a1d638e9195aed0f9d0fe94002f1a0.jpg" />
<p><i>This hardy dog was bred for herding sheep in the rugged terrain of Rivenspire.</i></p> 
<p>The Shornhelm Shepherd pet will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 21, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to October 24, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<p><b>Ghostly Housecat</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/cd2d198e4418a029806ea0105a4264a0.jpg" />
<p><i>According to Nibenese legend, a house where its owner was murdered will be haunted by the shade of their cat, sent from beyond by Lord Hollowjack to torment the killer with eternal shame and guilt.</i></p> 
<p>The Ghostly Housecat pet will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 21, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to October 24, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<p><b>Witch's Infernal Familiar</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/f31545c960b88211f62bbf354fe5dc49.jpg" />
<p><i>Equipped with a hat, this black cat makes its way in the world at your side, leaving little fiery pawprints behind as it goes.</i></p> 
<p>The Witch's Infernal Familiar pet will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 24, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to November 6, 2024 at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<p><b>Skeletal Pack Wolf</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/e450baf4a2dd9a909782bb384c78edbb.jpg" />
<p><i>When the Two Moons are full, the undead wolf pack rises from the grave, point their canine craniums at the sky, and try to howl—but the only sound is a dismal rattling in their bony throats.</i></p> 
<p>The Skeletal Pack Wolf pet will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 28, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to October 31, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p>Ready yourself for spooks and scares and perhaps pick up a few of your own with your Crown Store purchases this month! Have you found the perfect fright to delight amidst this month's offerings? Don't forget to stock up on crowns by heading to the <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/crowns">Buy Crowns page</a> first. Which of these new or returning items featured in this showcase are you most excited to acquire? Let us know via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Crown Store</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/f0c3a6b4025ebb06f5672a8733a6e2e2.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ESO's October 2024 Survival Guide]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66751</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66751</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[More events, promotions, and the launch of Update 44 on PC/Mac awaits in the jam-packed month of October!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/3cbf05a253c6170679dc18563f6bc5f0.jpg" /><p><i>More events, promotions, and the launch of Update 44 on PC/Mac awaits in the jam-packed month of October! </i></p> 
<p>This coming October 2024, we have the continuation of the Fallen Leaves of West Weald event, the Witches Festival, and the launch of the Update 44 base-game patch. Want to know more? Check out (almost) everything coming to <i>ESO </i>below. </p> 
<p><i> </i></p> 
<p><b>Xbox Game Pass Perks #3 (8/14-10/13)</b></p> 
<p>If you've yet to claim the Attribute Respecification Scroll and three Gold Coast Experience Scrolls from the third wave of this year's Xbox Game Pass Perks, there's still time! Check out <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66537">the details here</a>.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Fallen Leaves of West Weald Event (9/26-10/8)</b></p> 
<p>Likewise, the Fallen Leaves of West Weald event continues. There's still time to help the community unlock a host of great in-game rewards (including a pet, style, and mount). <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/fallenleaves">Visit the official page</a> to check the progress and find out more. </p> 
<p><i> </i></p> 
<p><b>TESOctober 2024! (10/1-10/31)</b></p> 
<p>The #ESOFam once again comes together to create and share <i>ESO</i>-themed fan art and screenshots in October. Keep an eye out for an official announcement (and this season's prompts) at the start of the month! </p> 
<p><i> </i></p> 
<p><b>Anniversary Spotlight: Dress to Impress (Your Coven) (10/1-11/6)</b></p> 
<p>Fashion IS the real <i>ESO</i> end game, and this month you can get your hands on some spooky looks, just in time for the Witches Festival! Check out <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66745">this announcement blog</a> for all the details on what you need to do to unlock both the Witchmother's Servant Arms Pack and the Grisly Mummy Wrap costume. </p> 
<p><i> </i></p> 
<p><b>Explorer's Celebration Event (10/8-TBD)</b></p> 
<p>All of Tamriel's adventures can enjoy a 100% boost to XP, Gold gains, and more during the Explorer's Celebration event. Note that this mini-event's end depends on how many days the community has earned during the <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/fallenleaves">Fallen Leaves of West Weald</a> event. </p> 
<p><i> </i></p> 
<p><b>Battlegrounds Deathmatch Weekend (10/17-10/22)</b></p> 
<p>Before the new-look Battlegrounds arrive with Update 44, fight for your team in furious 4v4v4 combat and earn bonus Alliance Points as you do! </p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Witches Festival Event (10/24-11/6)</b></p> 
<p>Tamriel gets spoopy! Earn special rewards by hunting down <i>ESO</i>'s monsters and completing event quests during the in-game Witches Festival. Check for more details closer to the event start date—boo!</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Update 44 PC/Mac Launch (10/28)</b></p> 
<p>Recruit two new companions, clash with your fellow players in the new two-sided Battlegrounds, and more with the Update 44 base game patch. Do you play on console? Don't worry, Update 44 arrives on Xbox and PlayStation consoles November 13. </p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/5a66640e8de3fd4fc352e936e4e95e09.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>October 2024 Roadmap</i></p> 
<p>October brings all manner of spooky fun with a host of special events, promotions, and a massive new base-game update. What are you most excited about next month? Let us know via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>.</p><div><div id="_com_1" language="JavaScript" onmouseover="msoCommentShow('_anchor_1','_com_1')" onmouseout="msoCommentHide('_com_1')"> </div> </div>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Community</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/3cbf05a253c6170679dc18563f6bc5f0.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Daily Login Rewards—October 2024]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66763</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66763</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Create a spooky scene in your home with this month's Daily Login Rewards.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/ec9cca28f84ee38379dec1176998163c.jpg" /><p><i>Create a spooky scene in your home with this month's Daily Login Rewards.</i></p> 
<p>Tamriel's frightful festival is just around the corner, and the Daily Login Rewards are here to help! Seasonal goodies abound, as well as items and currencies that can help you <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66701">get ready for Update 44</a> (coming October 28 to PC/Mac and November 13 for Xbox and PlayStation consoles).</p> 
<p>Curious about how Daily Login Rewards work? Check out <a href="https://help.elderscrollsonline.com/#en/answer/41950">this help article</a> to discover all you need to know and take a peek at some of the highlights you can enjoy throughout October2024 below!</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Frightful Furnishings—Days 4-7 &amp; 14</b></p> 
<p>Assorted fearful fancies to darken your doorstep (or any other part of your home!) are available over a total of five different days throughout the month. Mark your yard with gravestones or light your halls with sinister braziers and let everyone know your fondness for the season.</p> 
<ul><li><i>Day 4: Vampiric Brazier, Taloned × 2</i></li><li><i>Day 5: Vampiric Mirror, Standing × 1</i></li><li><i>Day 6: Vampiric Goblet, Full × 4</i></li><li><i>Day 7: Gravestone, Cracked × 3</i></li><li><i>Day 14: Soul-Shriven Robed Creature × 1</i></li></ul> 
<p><i> </i></p> 
<p><b>Research Scrolls—Days 16-19</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/53dd6a68560fdd8515e6a88652d4e828.png" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Master the crafts of Tamriel</i></p> 
<p>Get your crafting skills up to speed for making spooky outfits (and homes) with these research scrolls. One is available for each of Blacksmithing, Clothing, and Woodworking, as well as a universal research scroll that speeds the progress through research on all tradeskills.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Luminous Ink—Day 21</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/f94e25f6524a6566850f985dff57ca5b.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Pen a mighty Grimoire</i></p> 
<p>You can claim three Luminous Ink for yourself and your Scribing efforts by logging in for a total of 21 days this month. It'll go great with the <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66701">new Banner-Bearer Grimoire</a> coming in Update 44!</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>PvP Currencies—Days 29-30</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/113312822316adacf4c54f809ded5712.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Exchange Tel Var for goods in the Imperial City</i></p> 
<p>Acquire 2,000 additional Alliance Points and 1,500 Tel Var Stones to get a swift start on what you can earn in the newly revamped Battlegrounds of Update 44, or to buy items from the refreshed vendors in the Imperial City.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p>Whether furnishing a haunted manor or scribbling in the margins of a Grimoire, you can find something handy in this month's login rewards. Let us know how you'll be putting them to use via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>. </p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Daily Rewards</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/ec9cca28f84ee38379dec1176998163c.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Save Up to 50% on the Gold Road Chapter During the Fallen Leaves of West Weald]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66753</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66753</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Save BIG on the newest ESO Chapter and begin exploring the West Weald region during this special sale and event period.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/ac91dcfeb1c7907f09e7223aec4ec836.jpg" /><p><i>Save BIG on the newest ESO Chapter and begin exploring the West Weald region during this special sale and event period.</i></p> <p>The Fallen Leaves of West Weald sale is now live on all platforms, including The Elder Scrolls Online Store, Steam, Epic Games Store, as well as Xbox (Xbox One, Xbox Series X|S) and PlayStation (PlayStation 4, PlayStation 5). Throughout the sale period, you can save up to 50% on <i>The Elder Scrolls Online: Gold Road</i> and up to 70% on <i>The Elder Scrolls Online</i>: <i>Standard Edition</i>. Be aware that this discount is currently available only for Standard Editions of <i>ESO: Gold Road</i> on PlayStation consoles.</p><p></p><p><br></p><p>This sale coincides with the <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66731">Fallen Leaves of West Weald event</a>, allowing you to participate in the zone event AND claim the unlocked rewards. Check the <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/fallenleaves">event's official page</a> for the community's progress and learn more.</p><p>If you're a fledgling adventurer ready to embark on a new Tamrielic journey, we recommend the <i>Gold Road</i> Collection (Deluxe Edition and Standard), which includes the base game, <i>Gold Road</i> Chapter, and ALL previous Chapters. However, if you're a grizzled <i>ESO</i> veteran, the <i>Gold Road </i>Upgrade (Collector's Edition and Standard) grants access to all the new Chapter content (including zone, storyline, and Scribing system).</p><p>This sale is available for a limited time only and may end on different dates depending on your platform and territory. Check your preferred retailer to confirm.</p><p><b>Xbox</b></p><ul><li>Standard Edition—September 26-October 8</li><li>Deluxe <i>Gold Road</i> Editions—September 26-October 8</li></ul><p><b>PlayStation</b></p><ul><li>Standard Edition—September 25-October 9</li><li>Deluxe <i>Gold Road</i> Editions—September 25-October 9</li><li>Standard <i>Gold Road</i> Editions—October 9-October 23<br></li></ul><p><b>Elder Scrolls Online Store</b></p><ul><li>Standard Edition—September 26-October 8</li><li>All <i>Gold Road</i> Editions—September 26-October 8</li></ul><p><b>Steam Store</b></p><ul><li>Standard Edition—September 26-October 8</li><li>All <i>Gold Road</i> Editions—September 26-October 8</li></ul><p><b>Epic Games Store</b></p><ul><li>Standard Edition—September 26-October 8</li><li>All <i>Gold Road</i> Editions—September 26-October 8</li></ul><h2>Venture into West Weald</h2><p>Kickoff a new adventure and unlock bonus rewards by questing throughout the Colovian Highlands during the <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66731">Fallen Leaves of West Weald</a>—<i>Gold Road</i> awaits! Are you ready to capitalize on these discounts for the <i>Gold Road</i> Chapter and <i>ESO</i> base game? Let us know via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Sales</category>
            <category>Gold Road</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/ac91dcfeb1c7907f09e7223aec4ec836.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Anniversary Spotlight—Dress to Hex with this Ghoulish Apparel]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66745</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66745</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Pick up an assortment of creepy goodies, including frightening costumes and furnishings, during October's Anniversary Spotlight!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/79c1434d6af6a16e210cbd8942aa1cb0.jpg" /><p><i>Pick up an assortment of creepy goodies, including frightening costumes and furnishings, during October's Anniversary Spotlight!</i></p> 
<h2>Spread Terror and Look Good While Doing it!</h2> 
<p>Anniversary Spotlight—Dress to Impress (Your Coven) arrives during the spookiest month of the year and includes a plethora of unlockable rewards that'll leave your foes frozen in fear. This October, you can acquire the Witchmother's Servant Arms Pack to demonstrate your loyalty to the coven. </p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/8e2b37659961f6e3bda97a82486aee2e.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Witchmother's Servant Arms Pack</i></p> 
<p>To unlock this reward, you must first earn the “Fully Styled” achievement by applying a style to all eight slots (seven armor and one weapon) using the Outfit System. After fulfilling the requirements, you can obtain the free Arms Pack from the in-game Crown Store between October 3 and November 6.</p> 
<h2>Unwrap this Eerie Reward</h2> 
<p>In addition to gaining some spooky styles this month, you can arise and frighten away trespassing crypt delvers by earning the Grisly Mummy Wrap costume. To unlock this reward, you'll first need to complete the achievement “What a Hoot!” by collecting and using 10 Horned Owl Feathers and summoning the Senchal Horned Owl pet during the upcoming Witches Festival in-game event.</p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/27b7589ecb8115b08220ffc9b0ee634e.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Grisly Mummy Wrap Costume</i></p> 
<p>Once you earn the required achievement, you'll be able to pick up the costume for free from the in-game Crown Store during the event period, which will run from October 24 to November 6.</p> 
<h2>Decorate with Haunted Furnishings</h2> 
<p>Finally, you'll also have the chance to gather various spooky goodies by logging in to <i>ESO </i>each day in October. Included in this month's Daily Login Rewards will be various seasonal furnishings such as the Vampiric Mirror and Cracked Gravestone—guaranteed to add a macabre vibe to your in-game abode. Keep your eyes out for October's Daily Login Rewards blog to learn more about these frightful items.</p> 
<h2>Spotlight Spooky Styles</h2> 
<p>The season of scares has arrived, so dress appropriately with this cursed apparel! Are you prepared to claim the haunted treasures included as part of the October spotlight? Let us know via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>. </p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Community</category>
            <category>10th Anniversary</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/79c1434d6af6a16e210cbd8942aa1cb0.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Update 44 Now Live on the Public Test Server!]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66721</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66721</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Recruit new Companions and battle your fellow players in the reworked Battlegrounds with Update 44, now available on the Public Test Server.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/a579aaddafe27a54330a4575583bbffe.jpg" /><p><i>Recruit new Companions and battle your fellow players in the reworked Battlegrounds with Update 44, now available on the Public Test Server.</i></p> 
<p>The Public Test Server (PTS) has now been updated to include the Update 44 base-game patch, giving you access to updated and reworked Battlegrounds, two new Companions, a new Scribing Grimoire, and more! </p> 
<p>To access the PTS, go to the Settings menu within the PC/Mac ESO launcher by toggling the “Show Public Test Environment” option. You can then download and access the game client. Don't forget to leave feedback and report any bugs you come across by typing “/feedback” or “/bug” in chat.</p> 
<p>If you want to learn about the features coming in Update 44 or anything else to do with the patch, be sure to check out the <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66701">preview blog</a> and <a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/665758/pts-patch-notes-v10-2-0">PTS Patch Notes</a> on the <i>ESO </i>forums.</p> 
<p>Which of Update 44's new features are you most excited to experience? Let us know <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>. </p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Community</category>
            <category>Update 44</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/a579aaddafe27a54330a4575583bbffe.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Check Out What You Missed During the Update 44 Preview Livestream]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66715</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66715</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Missed the Update 44 preview livestream? Get caught up on the Battlegrounds refresh, new Companions, and more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/f2645f6b4b0bcfed8826e132934b3404.jpg" /><p><i>Missed the Update 44 preview livestream? Get caught up on the Battlegrounds refresh, new Companions, and more.</i></p> 
<p>Earlier this week, members of the <i>ESO</i> development and community teams got together on <a href="https://www.twitch.tv/Bethesda">Twitch.tv/Bethesda</a> to share a live preview of the upcoming Update 44 base-game patch and Fallen Leaves of West Weald event. If you were unable to tune in to the live broadcast, don't worry! You can check out the entire recorded livestream below:</p>
<a href="https://youtube.com/v/WiA5eVXBzzg?autoplay=1&rel=0"><img src="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/WiA5eVXBzzg/maxresdefault.jpg" /></a>
<p>Check out our <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66701">Update 44 preview blog</a> for more on what is coming to Tamriel throughout the rest of 2024 and look out for additional previews on <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/">elderscrollsonline.com</a> in the coming months. Are you excited for any of the new Update 44 features, additions, and improvements? Let us know via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>.<br></p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Community</category>
            <category>Update 44</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/f2645f6b4b0bcfed8826e132934b3404.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Embrace Sithis with the New Dark Brotherhood Crown Crates]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66631</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66631</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Stalk about Tamriel in secretive and sinister styles with the items and collectibles found in the new Dark Brotherhood Crown Crates.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/a4fb645df39e245deea7130baf3d1c80529287.jpg" /><p><i>Stalk about Tamriel in secretive and sinister styles with the items and collectibles found in the new Dark Brotherhood Crown Crates.</i></p> 
<p>***</p> 
<p><i>Crimson limned shadows move just beyond sight. Blades glint in the darkness as the Night Mother's children move to strike. A Black Sacrament has been enacted. Will you take up the implements of the Dark Brotherhood? Sithis whispers secrets to those willing to do what must be done. Taste the flavor of fear, and enter the Sanctuary. After all. We Know.</i></p> 
<p>***</p> 
<p>The new Dark Brotherhood Crown Crates arrive in the Crown Store this Thursday, September 12, 2024 at 10 AM EDT. When opening these crates, you have a chance to acquire the shadowy treasures of the Dark Brotherhood in the form of new and returning items and collectibles.</p> 
<p>These goods include unique mounts, pets, furnishings, and much more. You can see just some of the items available within Dark Brotherhood Crown Crates below.</p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/e73902dceaf748f1b4611b2b05d68115.jpg" />
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/dfc512eead98b730c01339eb47f7c7db.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Minotaur polymorph and Woebringer skin</i></p> 
<p>If you are especially lucky, you may find you have freed a radiant apex mount from the Dark Brotherhood's stables. One can only hope the assassins don't mind it going missing!</p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/597fc066e14b5701ed0a77abf6e1209a.jpg" />
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/7fdaf18cb690f172677c7ddd035bfff2.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Bloodmoon Wolf and Hollowsoul Steed mounts</i></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/e030f692d6d7a58dfc992fd2f8066f19.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Ardor's Devotion Senche-Raht mount</i></p> 
<p>Dark Brotherhood Crown Crates will be available in one-, four-, 15-, and 25-crate bundles in addition to a unique 25-crate offering, the Whispers of Sithis Bundle, that is available as a one-time purchase only. In addition to the crates, this special bundle includes the Whisper of Sithis Arms Pack and the Sithis Shaman costume.</p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/0a0d52bfa464e13100d69538beda50fa.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>The whispers of Sithis are not to be ignored</i></p> 
<p>When you first purchase the one-off bundle, you unlock the arms pack and costume automatically and they are added to your collectibles. They are not part of the Dark Brotherhood crates themselves.</p> 
<p>Of course, the above are just some of the rewards the Dark Brotherhood offers. If you wish to see the full list of items you have a chance to receive when opening a Dark Brotherhood Crown Crate, check out <a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/665274">this thread on our official forums</a>.</p> 
<p>Be warned, when the new crates go live, the currently available Diamond Anniversary Crates will be removed from the Crown Store, so don't forget to pick them up while they're still available!</p> 
<p>Dark Brotherhood Crown Crates arrive this Thursday, September 12 at 10AM EDT, and you can acquire them from the Crown Crate section of the in-game Crown Store. Will you listen to the call of Sithis echoing in the void? Break the silence and let us know via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>. </p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Crown Store</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/a4fb645df39e245deea7130baf3d1c80529287.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Earn Bonus Loot When Delving into Tamriel's Dungeons during the Undaunted Celebration]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66691</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66691</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Receive exciting bonus rewards when conquering Tamriel's dungeons during the Undaunted Celebration in-game event.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/c629c32077f04cbce3e489482b00e791.jpg" /><p><i>Receive exciting bonus rewards when conquering Tamriel's dungeons during the Undaunted Celebration in-game event.</i></p> 
<h2>Adventure Fearlessly</h2> 
<p>Take up arms, brave warriors! The Undaunted Celebration returns Thursday, September 12 at 10AM EDT, and runs until Tuesday, September 24 at 10AM EDT. During this in-game PvE event, you and other hardy adventurers can obtain special rewards and Event Tickets by conquering any of <i>ESO</i>'s group dungeons. </p> 
<p>Once the event kicks off next week, you can begin your expedition into any of Tamriel's many dungeons via your map, the Activity Finder, or the dungeon's entrance. Additionally, you can obtain the Undaunted Celebration's introductory quest “Glory of the Undaunted” by speaking to Serileth (located at any Undaunted Enclave), traveling to an Impresario tent, or snagging free from the in-game Crown Store.</p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2022/09/73f5287c12ad2a1ac276c76934e2f4bb.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Locate Serileth!</i></p> 
<h2>Great Deeds Yield Greater Rewards</h2> 
<p>The dungeons scattered across Tamriel are dangerous and challenging, but the rewards that await are worth the risk! Each day, the first time you complete a dungeon throughout the duration of the event, you'll receive a Glorious Undaunted Reward Box as an additional loot drop. Contained within these boxes are various goodies including gold, consumables, style pages, Undaunted Keys, Opal Weapon styles, and more.</p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/ab8d5573767012eeb4141a834d3abaa0.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Slay Dungeon Bosses to Unlock Bonus Rewards</i></p> 
<p>In addition, each subsequent final dungeon boss defeated yields a regular Undaunted Reward box, which can include the following items:</p> 
<ul><li>A guaranteed chance to drop an item set piece from the dungeon in which the box was acquired.</li><li>A guaranteed chance to drop one of the following items:</li><ul><li>A random motif style page from the following:</li><ul><li>Ascendant Order </li><li>Blessed Inheritor </li><li>Blind Path Cultist </li><li>Bloodforge </li><li>Crimson Oath </li><li>Dreadsail </li><li>Drowned Mariner </li><li>Fang Lair </li><li>Hazardous Alchemy</li><li>Huntsman </li><li>Icereach </li><li>Mazzatun </li><li>Moongrave Fane </li><li>Pyre Watch </li><li>Scalecaller </li><li>Scribes of Mora </li><li>Silver Dawn </li><li>Silken Ring </li><li>Silver Rose </li><li>Stags of Z'en </li><li>Recollection </li><li>Thorn Legion </li><li>True Sworn </li><li>Waking Flame </li><li>Y'ffre's Will</li></ul><li>1,000 Gold</li><li>An Undaunted Key</li><li>A Crown Repair Kit</li><li>A Riding Lesson</li></ul><li>A chance to drop an Opal monster weapon style for:</li><ul><li>Bloodspawn</li><li>Chokethorn</li><li>Engine Guardian</li><li>Ilambris </li><li>Troll King </li></ul><li>A chance to drop an Earthgore Opal weapon style </li></ul>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/08/2902ba89fc08efd34d77bb9f81e55f91.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Earthgore Opal weapon style</i></p> 
<p>The Glorious Undaunted Reward Box can contain any of the above items, but instead always drops one of the following Opal monster weapon styles: </p> 
<ul><li>Bloodspawn</li><li>Chokethorn</li><li>Engine Guardian</li><li>Ilambris </li><li>Troll King</li></ul> 
<p>You can obtain regular Undaunted Reward Boxes by completing Bolgrul's Daily Undaunted Delve quest. You can locate Bolgrul within any Undaunted Enclave. </p> 
<p><b>Opal Monster Mask Style Pages</b></p> 
<p>Throughout the Undaunted Celebration, slaying and looting a specific dungeon's final boss on veteran hard mode provides a greater chance to obtain its associated Opal Monster Mask style page. This includes the following bosses and dungeons: </p> 
<ul><li>Bloodspawn (Spindleclutch II)</li><li>Chokethorn (Elden Hollow I) </li><li>Engine Guardian (Darkshade Caverns II)</li><li>Ilambris (Crypt of Hearts I)</li><li>Troll King (Blessed Crucible)</li></ul> 
<p><b>Opal Monster Shoulder Outfit Style Pages</b></p> 
<p>If you happen to own a base version of a specific monster shoulder style, you can also acquire the Opal version of that same style from Undaunted vendors at a cost of 50 Undaunted Keys. These vendors also sell mystery boxes that provide random Opal shoulder style pages for 25 Keys. Luckily, all Undaunted Pledges provide double the Key rewards throughout this event's duration to help you take advantage of these limited-time offers.</p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2022/09/9ba1f1d588e3187458648345f4a149d9.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Trade your Undaunted Keys for style pages</i></p> 
<h2>Event Tickets &amp; The Impresario</h2> 
<p>Throughout the event, you can earn <b>two Event Tickets</b> for the first time you've defeated a final dungeon boss each day. Please keep in mind that you can hold up to 12 Event Tickets at any one time. If you earn any more while already at that Event Ticket limit, they'll be lost to Oblivion!</p> 
<p>During the Undaunted Celebration, you can spend your Event Tickets at the Impresario vendor to acquire the following items: </p> 
<ul><li>All three <b>Molag Bal Illusion Imp </b>pet fragments </li><ul><li>Anchor Chain Fragment</li><li>Dark Anchor Pinion</li><li>Effigy of the Dominator</li></ul><li>The first TWO <b>Anchorborn Welwa </b>mount fragments </li><ul><li>Bizarre Daedric Meat</li><li>Fine Ebonsteel Chain</li></ul><li>Bound style pages for the Earthgore Opal weapons and Opal Masks and Shoulders</li><li>Impresario Group Repair Kits</li><li>Companion Guild Commendations</li></ul>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/af0386db601ae6d77643abe680d4f866.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Acquire the next fragment for the </i><i style="">Anchorborn Welwa<b> </b></i><i>mount</i></p> 
<p>In addition, the Impresario's Assistant stocks the following:</p> 
<ul><li>All three Unstable Morpholith pet fragments</li><ul><li>Deadlands Flint</li><li>Rune-Etched Striker</li><li>Smoldering Bloodgrass Tinder</li></ul><li>All three Deadlands Firewalker personality fragments </li><ul><li>Vial of Simmering Daedric Brew</li><li>Vial of Bubbling Daedric Brew</li><li>Vial of Scalding Daedric Brew</li></ul><li>All three Soulfire Dragon Illusion Imp pet fragments </li><ul><li>Hallowed Hourglass Basin</li><li>Illuminated Dragon Scroll</li><li>Kvatchian Incense</li></ul><li>All three Aurelic Quasigriff mount fragments </li><ul><li>Aurelite Gryphon Feather</li><li>Gilded Gryphon Barding</li><li>Sacred Seeds of Akatosh</li></ul></ul> 
<p>Finally, the Indrik vendor Nenulaure will have: </p> 
<ul><li>Nascent Indrik Feathers</li><li>Onyx Indrik Berries</li><li>Mossheart Indrik Berries</li><li>Ebon-Glow Indrik Pet</li><li>Sapling Indrik Pet</li></ul> 
<h2>Riches and Glory Await! </h2> 
<p>Slay the monsters that lurk within Tamriel's various dungeons and be handsomely rewarded for your efforts during the Undaunted Celebration in-game event. Are you ready to team up with your fellow indomitable adventurers and plunge into <i>ESO</i>'s group dungeon challenges? Let us know via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, or <a href="https://www.facebook.com/ElderScrollsOnline">Facebook</a>.</p> 
<p><i>The Undaunted Celebration begins Thursday, September 12 from 10AM EDT, and runs until Tuesday, September 24 at 10AM EDT.</i></p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Events</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/c629c32077f04cbce3e489482b00e791.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Update 43 Base-Game Patch Now Live on All Platforms]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66487</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66487</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Return to the Infinite Archive, receive new visitors with Home Tours, and discover other additions and fixes—all part of the Update 43 base-game patch.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/08/ac41c359749773197532e468db0d09e4.jpg" /><p><i>Return to the Infinite Archive, receive new visitors with Home Tours, and discover other additions and fixes—all part of the Update 43 base-game patch. </i></p> <p>The Update 43 base-game patch is now live on PC/Mac, Xbox One, Xbox Series X|S, PlayStation 4, and PlayStation 5. This update introduces new features, content, and improvements to <i>The Elder Scrolls Online</i>, completely free for all <i>ESO</i> players.</p> <h2>New Features</h2> <p>Those who enjoy delving deep into the Infinite Archive or showing off their latest home builds will appreciate the two big new features included in Update 43. </p> <p><b>Infinite Archive Update</b></p> <p>Return to the twisting halls of the Infinite Archive (<i>ESO</i>'s near-endless PvE arena) and you'll discover two new unique areas, new monsters, a host of new Visions and Verses, and new rewards. These rewards include new collectibles and seven all-new class sets, not found anywhere else in Tamriel! </p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/08/80ebe975c599f3401b74f0d6a176f86a.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Discover new challenges and rewards in the Archive</i></p> 
<p>To learn more about the additions coming to the Infinite Archive, check out <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66519">this preview blog</a>. </p> 
<p><b>Home Tours</b></p> 
<p>Share and showcase your flair for interior design and decoration with Home Tours, a new feature added to <i>ESO</i>'s Housing System. With Home Tours, you can search for homes owned and decorated by another player and filter through labels, such as “Cozy” or “Festive.” </p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/08/6cc578d8e8c04208c086cff373a71fc1.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center"><i>Share your homes with the rest of the community</i></p> <p>You can also browse the top player homes in the Recommended tab, recommend those homes to others, and favorite them to return to later. List your own home and see what people think of your creation! </p> <p>To learn more about Home Tours, check out <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66495">this preview blog</a>. </p> <h2>Additional Improvements</h2> <p>Update 43 also introduces a host of quality-of-life improvements for all <i>ESO</i> players. This includes six new skill styles (for the Silver Bolts, Roar, Twin Slashes, Momentum, Elemental Storm, and Annulment skills) that can have their fragments dropped from base-game activities or acquired with Archival Fortunes from Infinite Archive. </p> <p>In addition, item set curation expands to include monster sets acquired via Undaunted Keys (from the Undaunted vendors), weekly Trial coffers, Trial leaderboard coffers, and Imperial City monster mask coffers. Finally, this update also adds improvements to mount previews within the Crown Store, and both Guild Trader and Guild Bank interfaces now remember the last Guild you interacted with. </p> <p>For a full list of all the changes, new features, and improvements arriving as part of the Update 43 base-game patch, check out the patch notes on <a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/categories/patch-notes">the official <i>ESO </i>forums</a>. </p> <h2>Free for All</h2> <p>As a base-game patch, Update 43 is free for all current <i>ESO</i> players—no additional purchases required! Are you excited to share and showcase your home to the rest of <i>ESO</i>'s housing community? Or perhaps you're eager to conquer the Infinite Archive's new stages and claim its new rewards? Let us know what aspects of Update 43 you're most interested in via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline;">Facebook</a>. </p> <p><i>The Update 43 base-game patch is now live on PC/Mac, Xbox One, Xbox Series X|S, PlayStation 4, and PlayStation 5.</i><br></p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Update 43</category>
            <category>Infinite Archive</category>
            <category>Homestead</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/08/ac41c359749773197532e468db0d09e4.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Retreat to a Serene Seaside Home with the New Housing Starter Pack!]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66671</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66671</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Pick up the all-new Housing Starter Pack today to enjoy the stunning Seabloom Villa home and Crown bundle.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/d05b659168f21703278e61a6a7e12740.jpg" /><p><i>Pick up the all-new Housing Starter Pack today to enjoy the stunning Seabloom Villa home and Crown bundle.</i></p><p>Do you dream of owning your own piece of Tamriel? Lucky for you, starting today, September 4,<sup> </sup>2024, you can become a Tamrielic homeowner with the new Housing Starter Pack!</p><p>This new bundle is available for purchase from the Xbox, PlayStation, Steam, Epic Games, and ESO Stores for <b>$4.99</b> <b>USD </b>and features items to help you kickoff (or expand) your housing adventure in <i>ESO.</i> </p><p>After purchasing this bundle, you'll immediately receive a System Mail message in your in-game mail inviting you to visit your new abode: an unfurnished, medium-sized home called <b>Seabloom Villa</b>. Once you've taken in the breathtaking mountaintop view of Auridon's cerulean coastline, be sure to also pick up the <b>“Handbook for New Homeowners” furnishing </b>that also awaits within. </p><p> </p><p>Finally, in addition to the home and handbook, the Housing Starter Pack also contains a <b>bundle of 800 Crowns</b> for you to spend in the in-game Crown Store. We suggest looking at some Crown Store furnishings to help decorate your new getaway. Even better, there's a plethora of furnishings available this month as <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66629">Daily Login Rewards</a>! Need some decoration inspiration? Try checking out how other players are furnishing their houses through the new <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66495">Home Tours</a> tool.</p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/5c1a33e0562979ae89f71511429a98ec.png" />
<p style="text-align: center"><i>Housing Starter Pack bundle</i></p><p> </p><p>Are you ready to move into this gorgeous coastal retreat? Be sure to head over to your preferred platform's store to claim your new Housing Starter Pack starting today. How do you plan to decorate your new house? We'd love to see your personalized Seabloom Villa, so feel free to share screenshots of your new home with us via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline;">Facebook</a>. </p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/09/d05b659168f21703278e61a6a7e12740.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Get a Glimpse of ESO's End-of-Year Adventures in the Update 44 Preview Livestream]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66609</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66609</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Discover what's in store for The Elder Scrolls Online throughout the rest of 2024 by watching the September preview livestream.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/08/db3c7043007b37b8e9f28315abf3cfb7.jpg" /><p><i>Discover what's in store for The Elder Scrolls Online throughout the rest of 2024 by watching the September preview livestream. </i></p> <p>Tune in to <a href="https://www.twitch.tv/Bethesda">Twitch.tv/Bethesda</a> on <b>Tuesday, September 10 at 2:30PM EDT</b>, as the team provides a first look at what is coming to <i>ESO</i> with Update 44. </p> <p>Together, they'll reveal all the major (and minor) additions and changes coming to the game, including updates to PvP, the upcoming Fallen Leaves of West Weald event, and more.</p> <p>Watch the livestream on Twitch, and you can earn the brand-new Chaosball Cohort PvP-themed pet as a drop! Be sure to <a href="https://help.elderscrollsonline.com/#en/answer/41809">link</a> your ESO and Twitch accounts.</p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/08/1aa19d71f894784c56a085866984d6de.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Chaosball Cohort pet </i></p> 
<p>We'll share additional details about the livestream closer to the date, but if you're eager to discover what lies ahead for <i>ESO</i> in 2024, save the date and don't miss this show!</p> 
<p>Are you excited to learn more about Update 44 and the rest of the year's adventures? Let us know via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Community</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/08/db3c7043007b37b8e9f28315abf3cfb7.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ESO's September 2024 Survival Guide]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66653</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66653</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Celebrate 10 years of ESO AND the full release of Update 43 by not missing a beat during what is set to be a very busy month for The Elder Scrolls Online!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/08/f99a363886f0be954168a81dc2783c38.jpg" /><p><i>Celebrate 10 years of ESO AND the full release of Update 43 by not missing a beat during what is set to be a very busy month for The Elder Scrolls Online!</i></p> 
<p>This coming September 2024, you can check out a host of fantastic in-game events, participate in a special community contest, and discover what's coming in Update 44. Here's everything you need to know about this upcoming month!</p> 
<p> </p> 
<p><b>Xbox Game Pass Perks (8/14-10/13)</b></p> 
<p>If you're an Xbox player and have yet to claim the latest Game Pass Perk rewards (one Attribute Respecification Scroll and three Gold Coast Experience Scrolls), there's still time. <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66537">Visit this blog</a> for more information about this latest wave of goodies.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Anniversary Spotlight: Dungeon Runners, Rise Up (9/1-9/30)</b></p> 
<p>Our next Anniversary Spotlight focuses on Tamriel's myriad challenging dungeons and the players who take them on. Claim two free DLC dungeons (as Daily Login Rewards), unlock the Dungeon Explorer costume and Thurvokun arms pack, and receive Undaunted Keys when completing dungeon-themed Endeavors. Learn more about this new spotlight <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66575" target="_blank" style="">in this blog</a>.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Daily Login Rewards (9/1-9/30)</b></p> 
<p>A new month means new Daily Login Rewards, and September is going to be another great one. Pick up a host of furnishings in addition to the two DLC dungeons and more. Check out our <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66629" target="_blank" style="">preview blog here</a> for all the details.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>U43 Console Launch (9/4)</b></p> 
<p>Xbox and PlayStation players finally get their hands on <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66487">Update 43</a>, allowing them to explore all the new additions to the Infinite Archive and make use of the new Home Tours tool.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>ESO Home Tours Contest (9/4-10/1)</b></p> 
<p>In celebration of the new Home Tours tool, we're inviting the community to share their homes with us for a chance to win some fantastic prizes. Keep an eye out for this new contest's official announcement on September 4. We can't wait to see what you create!</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>U44 Preview Livestream (9/10)</b></p> 
<p>Discover what lies ahead for <i>ESO </i>throughout the rest of 2024 with a brand-new preview livestream! Tune in to <a href="https://www.twitch.tv/Bethesda">Twitch.tv/Bethesda</a> to learn about the update to PvP, our 10-Year Anniversary plans, and more!</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Undaunted Celebration (9/12-9/24)</b></p> 
<p>WE. ARE. UNDAUNTED! Get bonus rewards when delving into Tamriel's dungeons during the Undaunted Celebration in-game event. Check the <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/home" target="_blank">official website</a> for more details closer to the event's kickoff.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>ESO 10-Year Anniversary Italian Celebration In-Person Event (9/14)</b></p> 
<p>The Italian #ESOFam commemorates a decade of <i>ESO</i> with an unforgettable night of mystery and fun in Grazzano Visconti, Italy.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>ESO 10-Year Anniversary North American Meetup (9/21)</b></p> 
<p>Mix and mingle with members of the <i>ESO </i>community and development teams at a new North American gathering in San Diego. Check out <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66589" target="_blank">the details here</a><b></b>!</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Fallen Leaves of West Weald (9/26-10/8)</b></p> 
<p>Jump back into West Weald and work together to unlock special rewards for the community during the Fallen Leaves of West Weald in-game event. Visit the <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/home" target="_blank">official website</a> for more details soon. </p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/08/8e092d8cc39433334f71c14feb48214d.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>September 2024 Roadmap</i></p> 
<p>September brings your first look at Update 44, fun community gatherings, and rewarding in-game events. Note that some of the above dates and items may change in the coming weeks, so don't forget to keep an eye on <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/">elderscrollsonline.com</a> for all the latest. Are you ready for another action-packed month for <i>The Elder Scrolls Online</i>? Let us know via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>. </p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Community</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/08/f99a363886f0be954168a81dc2783c38.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Crown Store Showcase—September 2024]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66651</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66651</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Behold the vast assortment of incredible collectibles coming to the in-game Crown Store this September 2024!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/08/5a802b2465042119b5044ceed5fcc6b2.jpg" /><p><i>Behold the vast assortment of incredible collectibles coming to the in-game Crown Store this September 2024!</i></p> 
<p>You can check out all the items coming to the in-game Crown Store throughout September 2024 below and see what's currently available by visiting the <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/crownstore">Crown Store page</a>. Anything catch your eye? Visit the <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/buycrowns">Buy Crowns page</a> to acquire the crowns you need. Certain items and offers are available for a limited time only, so be sure to read their details below and don't miss out.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>ESO Plus Deals</h2> 
<p>All ESO Plus™ members have access to a monthly selection of exclusive deals and items. You can find more information about them in <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/54825">this article</a>.</p> 
<p><b>Exclusive Free Items</b></p> 
<p><b>Painting: The Stitches</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/662c356ad984b2791d1fc4a9296c6302.jpg" />
<p><i>Located within the Scar in Northern Elsweyr, the Stitches draws the eye of many an artist seeking the challenge of illustrating a more vertically oriented settlement.</i></p> 
<p>The Painting: The Stitches will be available in the Crown Store FREE, exclusively to ESO Plus Members on all platforms for a limited time, from August 29, 2024 at 10 AM EDT, to October 3, 2024 at 10 AM EDT.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Crafting</h2> 
<p><b>Crown Crafting Motif: Ascendant Order Style </b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/08/b5c8840434f33f6fd117c343d270f267.jpg" />
<p><i>The Ascendant Champion states, “While we must hide our faces as we go about the Order's work, it is important that our arms and our uniforms declare our allegiance for all to see.” Use to learn the Ascendant Order crafting style. Also teaches the equivalent Ascendant Order Outfit Styles. </i></p> 
<p>The Crown Crafting Motif: Ascendant Order Style will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from September 3, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to September 9, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item. Ascendant Order Motif chapters, and very rarely the complete book, have a chance to drop from Varallion in the Coral Aerie dungeon. Harder difficulties will increase the chances of the item dropping.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Crown Crafting Motif: Greymoor</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/08/257d45c5b749fbc2c2f96626a9cee306.jpg" />
<p><i>Captain Viddgryr, Guard of Solitude, writes, "The Gray Host needs little introduction. The ancient army, risen anew, plagues our lands with little regard for the lives they take. Many have clashed blades with these terrors, but are woefully misinformed about their weapons and armor." Use to learn the Greymoor crafting style. Also has a chance to drop by participating in Harrowstorm daily encounters in Western Skyrim.</i></p> 
<p>The Crown Crafting Motif: Greymoor will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from September 23, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to September 30, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item. Greymoor Motif chapters, and very rarely the complete book, have a chance to drop from Skyrim Daily Reward Coffers awarded from Swordthane Jylta in Solitude.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Outfit Style</b></p> 
<p><b>Sellistrix Arms Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/08/1ca3c18871849715704636501e8c4ff9.jpg" />
<p><i>Glirion the Redbeard notes of Arx Corinium, home to Sellistrix the Lamia Queen: "A relic of the fallen Empire. Drowned and consumed by swamps and serpents, as you will be should you travel there." Alter your weapon's appearance to match the Undaunted Sellistrix awards by using this complete set of Outfit styles.</i></p> 
<p>The Sellistrix Arms Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from September 5, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to September 12, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item. The matching mask page will have a small chance to drop from Sellistrix from Veteran Arx Corinium. The matching shoulder page can be purchased from Glirion the Redbeard for 50 Undaunted Keys, or has a chance of dropping from Glirion's Mystery Coffer for 1 Key. Having the achievement “Snake Skinner” increases the drop chances of both items.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Shadowrend Arms Pack </b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/08/e28c041b9608411c3356870460e4627b.jpg" />
<p><i>Maj al-Ragath says of the Banished Cells, home to Shadowrend the clannfear, "Beneath Auridon lies a boil of dark magic and family hate." Perfect challenge for an Undaunted to overcome. Alter your weapon's appearance to match the Undaunted Shadowrend awards by using this set of Outfit styles. </i></p> 
<p>The Shadowrend Arms Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from September 9, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to September 16, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item. The matching mask page will have a small chance to drop from High Kinlord Rilis from Veteran The Banished Cells I. The matching shoulder page can be purchased from Maj al-Ragath for 50 Undaunted kKeys, or has a chance of dropping from Maj's Mystery Coffer for 1 Key. Having the achievement “Soul Splitter” increases the drop chances of both items.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Guild's Eye Arms Pack </b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/08/70a9af44a039dffc9b26c87fbfbaa117.jpg" />
<p><i>Aspiring Mages Guild apprentices seek out arms featuring the guild's symbol. Alter your weapon's appearance to match the Guild's Eye Weapons by using this complete set of Outfit styles. </i></p> 
<p>The new Guild's Eye Arms Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from September 12, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to September 19, 2024 at 10AM EDT.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Aldmeri Eagle Knight Armor Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/08/f0110b741cb7d4b5d13af8e3619b2d9f.jpg" />
<p><i>Knights of the Aldmeri Dominion often adorn their armor with the Aldmeri eagle symbol, which honors Auri-El. Alter your armor's appearance by using this complete set of Aldmeri Eagle Knight Outfit styles.</i></p> 
<p>The new Aldmeri Eagle Knight Armor Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from September 19, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to September 26, 2024 at 10AM EDT.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Elder Scrolls Artifact: Bow of Shadows</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/08/54ea316bf9e5e30f91d78e94f0da2cf5.jpg" />
<p><i>Alter your bow's Outfit style with a replica of the Bow of Shadows Elder Scrolls Artifact, a weapon created by the Daedric Prince Nocturnal.</i></p> 
<p>The Elder Scrolls Artifact: Bow of Shadows will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from September 5, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to September 12, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Timbercrow Arms Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/08/fd8f45a32746bc712913c8c01a655569.jpg" />
<p><i>Whether you work from the shadows or strike within plain sight, these simple and light armaments from the Timbercrow clan should serve you well. Alter your weapon's appearance by using this complete set of Timbercrow Outfit styles.</i></p> 
<p>The Timbercrow Arms Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from September 23, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to September 30, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Imperial Champion Armor Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/08/bfd6dd4d4d2f3f2f378715580179a691.jpg" />
<p><i>Stalwart soldiers within the Imperial Legion receive a special suit of armor after a particularly heroic deed. Alter your armor's appearance by using this complete set of Imperial Champion Outfit styles.</i></p> 
<p>The Imperial Champion Armor Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from September 30, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to October 7, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<h2>Adornment</h2> 
<p><b>Xanmeer Doyen's Feather Tiara</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2022/01/8630516d672714f26524d5256b75b482.jpg" />
<p><i>This gorgeous tiara is replicated from the intricate regalia of the Xanmeer Priesthoods. Wow the crowd and stand out with this beautiful plumage waving above your brow.</i></p> 
<p>The Xanmeer Doyen's Feather Tiara adornment will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from September 30, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to October 7, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Wardrobe</h2> 
<p><b>Harboursworn Occultist</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2021/11/12e45a158289db92535c2a4a1c176f52.jpg" />
<p><i>"After the last time someone tried to hug me at a Dark Anchor, I designed this attire. It's particularly effective at staving off such shows of … excessive and nonconsensual exuberance."—Pelynwe the Untouchable</i></p> 
<p>The Harboursworn Occultist costume will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from September 3, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to September 9, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Renegade Dragon Priest </b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2022/01/eec411f1dda0a522217621d3fef7e08a.jpg" />
<p><i>Sure, Dragon Priests were evil overlords who ruled mortals in the name of tyrannical Dovah, but what a fashion sense they had! Now you can adopt the appearance of the Renegade Dragon Priest from Scalecaller. </i></p> 
<p>The Renegade Dragon Priest will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from September 9, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to September 16, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Stealthy Rogues Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/08/8ae8bbd6b184deda4f5ea479d2e2ad1d.jpg" />
<p><i>A costume pack that offers three variations of outfits for thieves and assassins.</i></p> 
<p>The Stealthy Rogues Pack costume will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from September 23, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to September 30, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Events </h2> 
<p><b>Currency</b></p> 
<p><b>Event Tickets</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/07/0eca6e67f5bc52c1eb8932d18cb2e7ce.jpg" />
<p><i>A ticket used to purchase rare goods from The Impresario, Event Merchant. Curious as to what goods? Well, chat with her to see what she has to offer!</i></p> 
<p>Single Event Tickets will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time during the Undaunted Celebration event and Fallen Leaves of West Weald event. Event Tickets are also giftable to other players from within the Crown Store.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<h2>Furniture </h2> 
<p><b>Music Box, Dancing Among the Flowers Fine </b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/08/bb9301ac3b40ed4b86d029451fe61d14.jpg" />
<p><i>When activated, plays a music box arrangement of the soothing "Dancing Among the Flowers Fine" composition.</i></p> 
<p>The Music Box, Dancing Among the Flowers Fine will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from September 5, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to September 12, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Music Box, The Shadows Stir</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/c02ff37390b302ebb6d48ace2a6a6426.jpg" />
<p><i>When activated, plays a music box arrangement of the haunting "The Shadows Stir" composition.</i></p> 
<p>The Music Box, The Shadows Stir will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from September 5, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to September 12, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Furnishing Pack: Moons-Blessed Oasis</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2022/06/4708ac50f55b4c74e0e2829f31ab2c1c.jpg" />
<p><i>Bring the stark beauty of an Anequine oasis to your courtyard with this bundle of Elsweyr plants and statuary, complete with a luminous fountain blessed by Jone and Jode.</i></p> 
<p>The Furnishing Pack: Moons-Blessed Oasis will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from September 19, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to September 26, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Furnishing Pack: Mad Alchemist</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2022/10/d2cc877ee2f3fda19445751449451138.jpg" />
<p><i>At last, you can demonstrate your true genius! Enhance your laboratory with these tanks and specimens then experiment to your heart's content! And, because the simple-minded may fear your work, keep your combat arts well-honed on a sturdy Bloodknight.</i></p> 
<p>The Furnishing Pack: Mad Alchemist will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from September 26, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to October 3, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Houses</h2> 
<p><b>Tel Galen </b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2022/06/d0601e4b353981e71939f7486f3d8e97.jpg" />
<p><i>Fulfill your fantasies of a fungal flat with this fabulous Telvanni wizard's tower, on a private island on Azura's Coast! Comes complete with grand foyer, workshop, suite, and tower chamber ideal for magical research. </i></p> 
<p>Tel Galen returns to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from August 29, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to September 12, 2024 at 10AM EDT. Furnished and unfurnished versions will be available.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Stone Eagle Aerie</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2022/10/17b88e3f456be4b6be572f778e0d50b8.jpg" />
<p><i> From its majestic position above the city of Markarth, the Stone Eagle Aerie features breathtaking views, several water features, and sturdy Dwarven stonework. Rumors claim a hidden exit provides easy access to the Markarth Outlaws Refuge.</i></p> 
<p>The Stone Eagle Aerie returns to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from September 16, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to September 30, 2024 at 10AM EDT. Furnished and unfurnished versions will be available.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>The Erstwhile Sanctuary </b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2022/03/f0c28d1d94ecc56e1837071412141850.jpg" />
<p><i>Built into the foundations of Kvatch itself, this ancient complex was abandoned by the Dark Brotherhood after a subterranean collapse tumbled one wall of the Speaker's bedchamber into a massive natural cavern.</i></p> 
<p>The Erstwhile Sanctuary returns to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from September 26, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to October 10, 2024 at 10AM EDT. Furnished and unfurnished versions will be available.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Houseguests</h2> 
<p><b>J'baanluk</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/08/7c340f957cf6875c0639f9dc42a18d92.jpg" />
<p><i>No job is too small for this Pahmar-raht resistance fighter. That said, he needs a place to rest before his next efforts against his oppressors. After adding J'baanluk to your home, you can set him on a path, plus you and your visitors can speak with him.</i></p> 
<p>J'baanluk returns to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from September 16, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to September 23, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Jakarn</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/08/6402c0c5fe7d747869d5948b529d8a66.jpg" />
<p><i>Thief though he is, Jakarn promises not to steal from your house if you allow him to stay. But as to your heart? Well, that's a different matter. After adding Jakarn to your home, you can set him on a path, plus you and your visitors can speak with him. </i></p> 
<p>The Jakarn will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from September 26, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to October 3, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Mounts</h2> 
<p><b>Silver Rose Senche-Serval</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/08/9f4d7664184a1c5498f478b02f737668.jpg" />
<p><i>The Knights of the Silver Rose spent years finding the best felines to rid their fortress of pests and annoyances. Generations later, and these senche-servals can clear out banekin infestations in a single day.</i></p> 
<p>The Silver Rose Senche-Serval mount will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from September 3, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to September 9, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Sapiarchic Senche-Serval</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/08/68b52c59326bb3767dc78f3c81248125.jpg" />
<p><i>"As the Sub-Sapiarch of Domestic Livestock, I was assigned by Larnatille to breed an appropriate mount for our sages to ride upon when working in the field. I proudly present my result: the loyal and majestic senche-serval!"—Corderil of Sunhold</i></p> 
<p>The Sapiarchic Senche-Serval mount will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from September 5, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to September 12, 2024, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Quasigriff </b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/08/2c43e310c37da3f8e0801468884167c4.jpg" />
<p><i>A product of wizardry and selective breeding, these chimeric steeds descend from Summerset gryphons. According to creator Irastimil Direnni, their wingless frame kept upkeep costs low, while maintaining superiority over the upstart Bretons' clumsy steeds. </i></p> 
<p>The Quasigriff mount returns to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from September 16, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to September 23, 2024 at 10AM EDT.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Whispering-Claw Senche-raht</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/08/a3220c0077c19ddfaca8e6076247b908.jpg" />
<p><i>Feanirr witnessed the demise of her proud adeptorium, not to war, but to a sickness faster and stealthier than all but her. Since then, she lives only in the moment, knowing that at any moment something deadlier than her could catch her by the tail.</i></p> 
<p>The Whispering-Claw Senche-raht mount will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from September 19, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to September 26, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Cyan Dwarven Senche</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/08/d3335e4e5c1d8a13a1f267dff0b58299.jpg" />
<p><i>"The Dwemer of old are known for their clever inventions. Here, they've captured the likeness of a senche through ingenious carving and materials. All these years later, the creature still easily heeds its master's call."—Dwarven Constructs: A Guide</i></p> 
<p>The new Cyan Dwarven Senche mount will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from September 26, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to October 3, 2024 at 10AM EDT.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Druid-Bound Ursauk</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/08/6262e20ecd88e92b53971eff18448016.jpg" />
<p><i>"I prefer the company of animals over people. Communing with the Evergrowth provides a calming respite from the need to speak. This ursauk, for example, has proven most personable. And now, it needs a rider."—Druid Dolvasie</i></p> 
<p>The Druid-Bound Ursauk mount will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from September 30, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to October 7, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Polymorph</h2> 
<p><b>Dread Anka-Ra</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/08/7dc8bba47c177c5563608ceadcbb68d5.jpg" />
<p><i>When Emperor Tarish-Zi returned out of the mists of the past, his ancient warriors rose from the dead to serve him as the stony Anka-Ra, undead that seemed hewn from rock itself. …It could be a good look for you.</i></p> 
<p>The Dread Anka-Ra polymorph will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from September 23, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to September 30, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Pets</h2> 
<p><b>Sphynx Lynx</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2022/06/3100ba433a8944322160ffe04a07bd18.jpg" />
<p><i>The discovery of this "lynx" created waves in noble circles when certain of their number realized they could have a feline around without succumbing to fur-based allergies. Now you see them everywhere.</i></p> 
<p>The Sphynx Lynx pet will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from September 9, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to September 16, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Half-Hatched Guarling</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/08/0c29068b5c89473c19f008b71d71a832.jpg" />
<p><i>"One morning I found a little guarling in my garden. Rushing around, bouncing off things. I'm not entirely sure why it wanted to keep bits of its shell, but I don't care. Look at how cute it is! I think we're friends now, and I would die for it."—Faylva</i></p> <p>The new Half-Hatched Guarling pet will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from September 16, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to September 23, 2024 at 10AM EDT.</p><p><br></p><p><b>Pale-Plume Fledgling </b><br></p><p> </p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/08/22cb788e27520fccf0b77171863a92b3.jpg" />
<p><i>Less common than the usual variety, the Pale-Plume Gryphons are found only along the seacoast cliffs near the Tower of Dusk in southeast Summerset. Their Fledglings make engaging pets that can be trained to follow their masters even into danger.</i></p> 
<p>The Pale-Plume Fledgling Gryphon pet will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from September 19, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to September 26, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p>From charming houseguests to exotic animal friends, a massive selection of exciting items are on sale in the Crown Store this September. Which of these goodies are you going to pick up this month? Don't forget to stock up on crowns by heading over to the <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/crowns">Buy Crowns page</a> beforehand. Let us know via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Crown Store</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/08/5a802b2465042119b5044ceed5fcc6b2.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Elder Scrolls Online is Now Playable on Steam Deck!]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66641</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66641</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[ESO players on Steam can now explore Tamriel using the portable Steam Deck!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/08/8ec7467b58e0c7aa9dd7f30ed91cc9ba.jpg" /><p><i>ESO players on Steam can now explore Tamriel using the portable Steam Deck! </i></p> 
<p>We are thrilled to announce that <i>The Elder Scrolls Online </i>now has “Playable” status on the <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/steamdeck">Steam Deck</a>. This means that Steam <i>ESO</i> players can now venture into Tamriel's Second Era using the portable PC gaming device. Never miss a Daily Login Reward again! </p> 
<p>If you play on Steam and have a Steam Deck, simply find the game in your Library to begin the download. Note that while the game is now officially “Playable,” it won't have full “Verified” status until a future update, meaning you might encounter some unexpected UI issues. </p> 
<p>To discover more about the Steam Deck, <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/steamdeck">visit their official website</a>. For help or support for your Steam Deck, visit <a href="https://help.steampowered.com/en/wizard/HelpWithSteamDeck">Steam Support here.</a> Can't wait to get started? Tell us if you're excited to explore Tamriel on Steam's portable device via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, or <a href="https://www.facebook.com/ElderScrollsOnline">Facebook</a>—have fun! </p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/08/8ec7467b58e0c7aa9dd7f30ed91cc9ba.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Daily Login Rewards—September 2024]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66629</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66629</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Get digging through dungeons and flowerbeds alike with these free rewards available just by logging in to The Elder Scrolls Online!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/08/eb9baa58f2097d3c2c8815392b39e6ed.jpg" /><p><i>Get digging through dungeons and flowerbeds alike with these free rewards available just by logging in to The Elder Scrolls Online!</i></p> 
<p>Whether you're journeying into distant dungeons or having a cozy staycation at your in-game house, there's plenty to enjoy about this month's free rewards.</p> 
<p>Curious about how Daily Login Rewards work? Check out <a href="https://help.elderscrollsonline.com/#en/answer/41950">this help article</a> to discover all you need to know and take a peek at some of the highlights you can enjoy throughout September 2024 below!</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Fang Lair &amp; Scalecaller Peak—Days 3 &amp; 4</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/08/0a7d6b72b5a8ff28ae7cdddc5205c7cd.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i><!--EndFragment -->Unlock free DLC dungeons</i></p> 
<p>You can unlock the DLC dungeons Fang Lair and Scalecaller Peak for free this September simply by logging in. Fang Lair unlocks upon your third login, while Scalecaller Peak unlocks with your fourth. Both dungeons are part of this month's <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66575">Anniversary Spotlight</a>, so prepare to challenge necromancers and cultists while you untangle the ancient legacy of the Dragon Thurvokun.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Assorted Furnishings—Days 5-6 &amp; 8-10</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/08/410668130a68a3e9fcf996fc614c991b.png" />
<p style="text-align: center; "><i><!--EndFragment -->Make yourself at home with these cozy additions</i></p> 
<p>While logging in during September, you can claim a steady stream of delightful decorations. These start with a set of three lovely “Alinor Windowbox, Blue Wisteria” furnishings on your fifth day of logging in and conclude on your tenth day with a “Blue Butterfly Flock” furnishing. During this period, you'll receive too many great furnishings to list here, so check the in-game calendar for full details!</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Luminous Ink—Day 7</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/f94e25f6524a6566850f985dff57ca5b.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center; "><i>Customize your Grimoires with Luminous Ink</i></p> 
<p>Receive a trio of Luminous Ink after your seventh day of logins. Prepare a new Grimoire or modify a few skills. Alternatively, sell or trade them to another player to help them along their own Scribing journey.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Weald Arbor Headdress—Day 14</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/08/5eb0bfd0b41e23452ede4939e533c819.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center; "><i>Adorn yourself in autumn</i></p> 
<p>Bedeck yourselves in leaves and flowers suitable to the autumnal colors of West Weald. You can claim this handsome harvest headpiece on your fourteenth day logging in this September.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Seals of Endeavor ×300—Day 21</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/10/cbf054f9fa4122ee9be26996607da8d2.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center; "><i>Receive a hefty helping of Seals</i></p> 
<p>You can pick up some Crown Crate goods with Seals of Endeavor—a purchase that can be made much more convenient with this handy bonus, available when you log in for 21 days this September. You can learn more about Seals of Endeavor <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/59925">in this blog</a>.</p><p><br></p> 
<p>As thrilling as these rewards and their ties to the <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66575">new Spotlight</a> are, they're not the only things you can claim this upcoming month. You can venture in-game to see the full list in the Daily Rewards section of the in-game Crown Store. Are you eager to claim September 2024's in-game Daily Login Rewards? Let us know what you think via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>. </p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Daily Rewards</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/08/eb9baa58f2097d3c2c8815392b39e6ed.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Anniversary Spotlight—Dungeon Runners, Rise Up]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66575</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66575</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Delve deep into special rewards, including free DLC dungeons, during September's Anniversary Spotlight!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/08/8787fc99a79102570403cf9050d2801b.jpg" /><p><i>Delve deep into special rewards, including free DLC dungeons, during September's Anniversary Spotlight!</i></p> 
<p>The latest 10-Year Anniversary Spotlight comes to you this September as it shines into the hidden corners of Tamriel's dungeons. Get free dungeon DLC from Daily Login Rewards, unlock and claim a free costume and arms pack, and earn Undaunted Keys as you complete daily Endeavors!</p> 
<h2>DLC Dungeons Delivered Free</h2> 
<p>Log in for just a few days during September 2024 to unlock free DLC dungeons. Your third login during the month unlocks the Fang Lair dungeon, while your fourth unlocks the Scalecaller Peak dungeon. </p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/08/0a7d6b72b5a8ff28ae7cdddc5205c7cd.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Unlock (and survive) Fang Lair</i></p> 
<p>These exciting dungeons feature unique rewards including item sets, titles, motifs, and more. Challenge the Blackmarrow necromancers or the cult of Peryite to claim them—good luck! </p> 
<h2>Dress from Success</h2> 
<p>Of course, the rewards included in the dungeon content itself aren't the only things you can claim. The Anniversary Spotlight also includes additional unlockable rewards. Complete both dungeons to earn the “Fang Lair Vanquisher” and “Scalecaller Peak Vanquisher” achievements and you can acquire the Dungeon Explorer Costume for free by claiming it from the Crown Store between September 3 and September 24. You can also claim the costume if you have the achievements from prior completions of the dungeons.</p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/08/643d1913ad7c32b4b4281a842b17166a.jpg" />
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/08/ef5c43c99a04ccd93eee2c44f004e3b6.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Earn achievements to unlock free rewards</i></p> 
<p>The Undaunted are of course eager to get in on any dungeon-delving action, so you can earn rewards by completing Undaunted Pledges as well. If you earn or already have the achievement “Returned Undaunted” for completing 10 Undaunted Pledges bestowed by Maj al-Ragath, you can claim the Thurvokun Arms Pack from the Crown Store completely free during the same period as the costume.</p> 
<h2>Endeavor Alongside the Undaunted</h2> 
<p>Of course, one of the things the Undaunted are most known for is their treasure, shared with the worthy who earn their Undaunted Keys. During the month of September, these rewards are easier to earn than ever, with certain thematic Endeavors available during the month awarding Undaunted Keys in addition to the normal seal amount for the day's Endeavors.</p> 
<p>Get ready to dive into dungeons and deal with terrible foes! Are you excited for the treasures of this new spotlight? Tell us all about your adventures via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>. </p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Community</category>
            <category>10th Anniversary</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/08/8787fc99a79102570403cf9050d2801b.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Feedback On Console Environmental Sustainability Features]]></title>
            <link>https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/660783/feedback-on-console-environmental-sustainability-features</link>
            <guid>https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/660783/feedback-on-console-environmental-sustainability-features</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 15:09:23 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[Hi all. We're gathering some feedback regarding the Environmental Sustainability Features added in U42. Specifically, we would like feedback on the following patch note:
<ul><li>Reduced GPU use in Contextual Menus (Xbox Series X|S and PS5): When viewing most menus, (eg. managing inventory, achievements, quest journal, etc) framerate is now capped to 30fps. Some menus are exempt on a case-by-case basis (eg. conversations, various mini-games). Testing in Performance Mode while in these menus shows a 50% reduction in GPU consumption, resulting in overall power consumption going from approximately 63% of the maximum possible on a console down to 37%.</li>
</ul>
We're seeing your feedback about menus capped to 30fps is causing issues for some of you. Please let us know how it is impacting your play experience. We are sharing this with our teams to better inform them of your feedback and how we can improve the experience overall. Additionally, if you are experiencing other framerate issues with either your menus or player character, please note those here as well. Thanks, all.]]></content:encoded>
            <category>Forum</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Crown Store Gifting Update – October 2023]]></title>
            <link>https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/644559/crown-store-gifting-update-october-2023</link>
            <guid>https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/644559/crown-store-gifting-update-october-2023</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 20:22:11 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[Following up on Studio Director Matt Firor's message last month about the <a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/643289/update-on-current-and-future-status-of-gifting">current and future status of Crown Store Gifting</a>, we are moving forward with re-enabling this functionality for eligible players at the account level. In this post, we will detail what to expect.<br><br>
In September, we temporarily disabled Crown Store gifting due to a rapidly growing issue of "bad actors" using various fraudulent means to amass crowns without paying for them, then using them in turn to sell Crown Store items to players for real-world cash outside of the game client. That said, we recognize that gifting is a meaningful part of our community, and we are in the process of manually re-enabling Crown Store gifting access for select players who meet our specific criteria. This work will be complete tomorrow, October 11, during the maintenance window from 09:00 AM ET to 12:00 PM ET.<br><br>
Gifting eligibility is determined by an evolving list of factors including but not limited to the account being at least 180 days past its first login and previous engagement with in-game features. You may check if you have access to gifting in-game via the Crown Store as well as via <a href="https://account.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/account/billing/billing-history">your billing history page</a> in the ESO account center. If you have access to Crown Store gifting, you will see "Allow Crown Store Gifting" in your billing history. If you try to send a gift via the in-game Crown Store and do not have access, you will see a "Gifting Locked" pop-up message. Please note that we are exploring better ways to display this information in-game in the future, such as updating the Gifting Tutorial.<br><br>
If you do not have access to Crown Store gifting after it is re-enabled on October 11, 2023, and wish for a review of your account, please visit <a href="https://help.elderscrollsonline.com">https://help.elderscrollsonline.com</a> and submit a Customer Support ticket. Please choose the Billing / Purchase / Code category then Platform &gt; I have a question about a sale / offer &gt; I want to send gift items from this account.<br><br>
We appreciate everyone's understanding and patience while we get this solution up and running. Multiple teams have worked long hours to evaluate the best technical solutions that we could stand up in a reasonably short time, while also prioritizing the Crown Store gifting player experience. We are dedicated to continuing to explore ways to make this better and reduce fraudulent activity in ESO. Thanks again for being a part of our community and for your continued support.]]></content:encoded>
            <category>Forum</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[New Patcher Rollout]]></title>
            <link>https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/642066/new-patcher-rollout</link>
            <guid>https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/642066/new-patcher-rollout</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 20:49:19 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[Hello everyone! After plenty of testing <a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en-gb/discussion/632782/new-eso-launcher-testing-and-launch-plan-pc-and-mac">during the last PTS period</a>, we are pleased to announce the rollout of our new patcher on the live servers for PC/Mac. The rollout of the new patcher will happen in four phases, with new countries being added during each phase. As we give countries access to the new patcher, we will make note of it in the list below by noting next to the country name (has the new patcher.) We will also note what phase we are currently in by specifying whether it has not started, in progress, or complete, next to the phase number. The countries getting the patcher are listed in order below.<br><br>
Thanks for your patience as we roll this out to all countries listed below. A special thanks to everyone who helped test out the launcher during the last PTS and provided feedback.<br><br>
Edit for 3/4/2024: All phases have now been complete.<br><br><b>Phase 1 (Complete) </b>
<ol><li>Netherlands (Has the new patcher)</li>
<li>Sweden (Has the new patcher)</li>
<li>Czech Republic/ Finland (Has the new patcher)</li>
<li>Norway/ Denmark (Has the new patcher)</li>
<li>Hungary/ Switzerland/ Romania (Has the new patcher)</li>
</ol><br><b>Phase 2 (Complete) </b>
<ol><li>Poland (Has the new patcher)</li>
<li>Spain/ Turkey (Has the new patcher)</li>
<li>Italy/ Austria/ Belgium/ Portugal/ Greece/ Ireland (Has the new patcher)</li>
</ol><br><b>Phase 3 (Complete) </b>
<ol><li>United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland/ France (Has the new patcher)</li>
<li>Germany (Has the new patcher)</li>
<li>United States of America (Has the new patcher)</li>
</ol><br><b>Phase 4 (Complete) </b><br>
This phase will encompass all other countries where ESO is available, that are not listed above. (All countries where ESO is available now have access to the launcher.)<br><br><b>Known Issues</b>
<ul><li>Some Czech Republic players may not have their country recognized, thus making them unable to upgrade the patch at this time. We are aware of the issue and working toward a solution.</li>
<li>Audio issues with sound volume and sound effects. We have a bug in for this and are working on a fix for the future.</li>
</ul>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>Forum</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>