<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>ESO Announcements</title>
        <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/</link>
        <description>Combined ESO blog and forum post announcements feed</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>Magic</generator>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Daily Login Rewards—June 2024]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66115</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66115</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Take a peek at some of the in-game rewards you can earn simply by logging in to The Elder Scrolls Online this June.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/adbdeae6be8c3716dffaf6726a3b6e26.jpg" /><p><i>Take a peek at some of the in-game rewards you can earn simply by logging in to The Elder Scrolls Online this June.</i></p> 
<p>Whether you and your fellow heroes are exploring West Weald or just beginning your <i>ESO</i> saga, you won't want to miss out on this month's tantalizing login rewards. Curious to learn more about Daily Login Rewards? Check out <a href="https://help.elderscrollsonline.com/#en/answer/41950">this help article</a> to discover all you need to know! </p> 
<p>Now, let's take a peek at some of the highlights you can receive throughout June 2024:</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Seals of Endeavor—Day 7</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/10/cbf054f9fa4122ee9be26996607da8d2.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Your Endeavors Pay Off!</i></p> 
<p>Log in this June and lay claim to a whopping <b>500</b> Seals of Endeavor, helping you obtain that one Crown Crate item you've had your eye on. Learn more about Seals of Endeavor and how to gain them in <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/59925">this help blog</a>.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Instant All Research Scroll x10—Day 14</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2021/11/1b9ed166a516ef5d656a69ce1ce41496.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Learn New Crafting Traits Swiftly</i></p> 
<p>Expedite the process needed to unlock new Blacksmithing, Clothing, Woodworking, and Jewelry crafting traits by one day through this set of ten Instant All Research Scrolls, available on day 14!</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>100,000 Gold—Day 21</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/4fd2fa272aef9a9fb443be645a775da3.png" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Gleaming, Glittering Gold!</i></p> 
<p>If your coin purse is a little light, don't worry. We've prepared a care package of 100,000 Gold for you to snag after your 21<sup>st</sup> login this month. You can use these newly obtained riches to help fund your adventures in Gold Road but try not to spend it all at once!</p><p><br></p> 
<p>This is just a brief preview of the 30 login rewards you can claim each day this month. If you'd like to view the full list, head over to the Daily Rewards section of the in-game Crown Store on June 1 to learn more! Are you excited to enjoy these complimentary login rewards while adventuring in the new <i>Gold Road</i> Chapter? Let us know via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>. </p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Daily Rewards</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/adbdeae6be8c3716dffaf6726a3b6e26.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Community Spotlight—Hearth and Homes]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66109</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66109</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Admire this selection of intricately designed homesteads, produced by creative members of the ESO community.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/617acf8193de6405c67e3b1f0adedbd1.jpg" /><p><i>Admire this selection of intricately designed homesteads, produced by creative members of the ESO community.</i></p> 
<p>To celebrate May's <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65941">Anniversary Spotlight—Hearth and Homes</a>, we offered the Sword-Singer's Redoubt household as a free login reward to all players. Then, we challenged our passionate community of <i>ESO</i> home designers to transform this vacant abode into a fully decorated home. Well, the submissions are in, and we wanted to share just a few of our favorites with you:</p><p><br></p> 
<p><a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/comment/8106431/#Comment_8106431">EmperorRemanIV</a></p> 
<p><i>"The Dragontail Camp, containing its own wayshrine, is the Imperial fortified border between the Daggerfall Covenant and Reman IV's Second Empire of Cyrodiil territory taken from the Tharn's Seventh Legion in the March of Ephesus."</i></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/bc0962d1da9a06cee03e09c4da9613ef.jpg" />
<p><br></p><p><a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/comment/8106593/#Comment_8106593">Googoo</a></p> 
<p><i>"Redguard style bedroom. For those who seek rest after a long day of trading at the market. Or mining in the crystal cave."</i></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/b20b8d785d0e6390a64a7d0b94e1e725.jpg" />
<p><br></p><p><a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/comment/8106749/#Comment_8106749">JohnBlacksad</a></p> 
<p><i>"Aladdin's cave of Wonders. This is a project I wanted to do for YEARS. Thank you for giving it away like this; it ended up being such an unexpected perfect match."</i></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/39461cc503ba9e1d9b00ccd659c15ea2.jpg" />
<p><br></p><p><a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/comment/8107403/#Comment_8107403">EdjeSwift</a></p> 
<p><i>"Because of the split-up nature of the structure, I'm doing various things with it. I'm more of a spartan, yet striking kind of decorator. The Bangkorai doorway is a tribute to the Dark Brotherhood."</i></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/9f1446cf32ab368748dc758783c00e13.jpg" />
<p><br></p><p><a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/comment/8108660/#Comment_8108660">Olen_Mikko</a></p> 
<p><i>"Khajiit takeover in Alik'r"</i></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/aff6de73e04082925bc58cf6cb7f0e66.jpg" />
<p><br></p><p><a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/comment/8110122/#Comment_8110122">MageCatF4F</a></p> 
<p><i>"Redguards love technology. After all, they invented cannons while the rest of Tamriel was muttering evil eye curses. Here a gang of international pirates (Inter-Rat) has contracted Mad Scientist Biro Dar to build them an airship raider, the steam powered "Zubenelgenubi" of 10 guns. Join the crew, climb aboard, and wreak havoc from the sky. EHT needed to fire cannons. An EHT open house named: Zubenelgenubi."</i></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/206fe4e21a0de580b39f8badb709363c.jpg" />
<p><br></p><p><a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/comment/8113043/#Comment_8113043">Wolfcrisp</a></p> 
<p><i>"Redguards are my favorite race, so I made a small Redguard sword academy. This house is open, it's my sword singer aerie in NA, and I'm </i><a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/profile/wolfcrisp"><i>@wolfcrisp</i></a><i>.</i><i>"</i></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/79d2db5e1d88d8af20b0422640ae6dcd.jpg" />
<p><br></p><p><a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/comment/8110832/#Comment_8110832">Grizzbeorn</a></p> 
<p><i>"I've re-conceptualized the Redoubt as kind of a makeshift Dark Brotherhood sanctuary, having Hilde and Kor onsite as its ‘caretakers,' with a secondary, though related, focus as a space where Hilde can find the inner peace she seeks, based on cues from the DB storyline."</i></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/5c61713086f61f11f220725faf23b94f.png" />
<p><br></p><p><a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/comment/8110855/#Comment_8110855">Futerko</a></p> 
<p><i>"Ganesha temple."</i></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/4c18726307309a7dd5dc70430adc922a.jpg" />
<p><br></p><p><a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/comment/8111053/#Comment_8111053">Emilyhyoyeon</a></p> 
<p><i>"The Desert Pass Oasis is a rest stop along a small trade route in Hammerfell, especially known for its refreshing lounge pool and washing pavilions. It's popular among traders and travelers alike with its many cozy gathering tents and quaint amenities. PC EU open for public visit. ign @ emilypumpkin."</i></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/2d5832fe365ea8517565227ad2e21694.jpg" />
<p><br></p><p><a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/comment/8110895/#Comment_8110895">Seecodenotgames</a></p> 
<p><i>"This is my new Redguard themed house: Alik'r Oasis Paradise."</i></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/83f770887d93e0a680cad7377f55a5ee.jpg" />
<p><br></p><p><a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/comment/8112192/#Comment_8112192">Lorros</a></p> 
<p><i>"I decided to take a different approach to the new Sword-Singer's Redoubt home, turning it into a crafting library and bazaar."</i></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/25c669c0ff0c506b7c64804d61ddc153.jpg" />
<p><br></p><p><a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/comment/8113148/#Comment_8113148">TeruKisuke</a></p> 
<p><i>"The build started with an idea for a ‘Pretty Pink Stationery Store.' Then, I built a city around it. TeruKisuke on Xbox NA server."</i></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/25dbdf5bff58f943eb06e471b993cdbf.jpg" />
<p><br></p><p><a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/comment/8110567/#Comment_8110567">SilverBride</a></p> 
<p><i>"My Sword-Singer's Redoubt is a place for travelers to stop and rest on their journeys through Alik'r and Bangkorai. It offers some sitting areas to read and relax, and some food and drink to replenish. There is also a sauna room to soak their weary bones. The underground cave area has some Druidic furnishings and candles that provide a peaceful place to meditate away from the heat of the desert sun."</i></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/09a8df8fb9ba1f1fdd79eb740baba571.jpg" />
<p><br></p><p>A massive “thank you” to the awesome members of the #ESOFam for sharing their <a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/657931/show-us-your-sword-singers-redoubt-housing-creations">renovations</a> on the Sword-Singer's Redoubt! Don't forget, there's still time to claim it for yourself, <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65941">simply by logging in</a>! Have you claimed your free house this month? If so, we'd love to see how you've transformed this desert fortress. Feel free to share your designs with us via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (Formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/ElderScrollsOnline">Facebook</a>. </p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>10th Anniversary</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/617acf8193de6405c67e3b1f0adedbd1.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Time is Running Out! Pre-Purchase Gold Road Now to Receive Exclusive Rewards]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66073</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66073</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Don't miss your chance to pre-purchase The Elder Scrolls Online: Gold Road and gain access to unique in-game items at launch!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/b9e68fa29ddb5e9a9178b5bd557c54b9.jpg" /><p><i>Don't miss your chance to pre-purchase The Elder Scrolls Online: Gold Road and gain access to unique in-game items at launch!</i></p> 
<p>Your adventure across West Weald is just around the corner (June 3 for PC/Mac and June 18 for Xbox and PlayStation consoles), but there is still time to pre-purchase your copy of <i>The Elder Scrolls Online: Gold Road</i>. Even better, by pre-purchasing now, you will immediately receive the <b>Welkyndstone Ruins Wolf mount</b>.</p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/695dd22b343dbff1bcd1cbff8cec0b46.png" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Welkyndstone Ruins Wolf Mount</i></p> 
<p>In addition to receiving this mount, any pre-purchase of <i>Gold Road</i> will grant you the following bonus items at launch:</p> 
<ul><li>Eyebright Raven pet</li><li>Strid River Fisherfolk costume</li><li>×1 Diamond Anniversary Crate</li><li>Gold Road Treasure Maps</li><li>×2 Experience Scrolls (+100% for 1 hour)</li></ul>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/61987905918d3f483aa51b4455721207.jpg" />
<p>These items are only available until the launch of <i>Gold Road</i> in June, so be sure to pick up your copy soon! </p> 
<p>Struggling to decide which version of <i>ESO:</i> <i>Gold Road </i>suits you? We recommend checking out <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65365">this blog</a> for a breakdown of what each edition of the Chapter offers. Once you've carefully considered all your options, you can click the button below to pre-purchase <i>Gold Road.</i></p><p><br></p><p>Are you excited to explore West Weald and confront the agents of the Forgotten Prince? Perhaps you're looking forward to tailoring your very own custom skills via the new <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65899">Scribing system</a>? Let us know which aspects of <i>The Elder Scrolls Online: Gold Road</i> you're most looking forward to<i> </i>via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>!</p><p><i>The Elder Scrolls Online: Gold Road arrives for PC/Mac on June 3, 2024, and for Xbox and PlayStation consoles on June 18, 2024. Pre-purchase Gold Road now to receive unique bonus rewards at launch and immediate access to the Welkyndstone Ruins Wolf mount. Don't miss out!</i> </p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Gold Road</category>
            <category>Update 42</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/b9e68fa29ddb5e9a9178b5bd557c54b9.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enjoy Bonus Gold, XP, & More as the Explorer's Celebration Returns]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66063</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66063</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Explore the far reaches of Tamriel and receive bonus rewards during the Explorer's Celebration!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/e101d13d0410d44eae3082858431c07f.jpg" /><p><i>Explore the far reaches of Tamriel and receive bonus rewards during the Explorer's Celebration!</i></p> 
<p>Starting today, May 23 at 10AM EDT, and running until May 28 at 10AM EDT, the Explorer's Celebration returns, granting you bonus rewards as you explore Tamriel.</p> 
<p>During the bonus period, <i>ESO</i>'s intrepid explorers can enjoy the following:</p> 
<ul><li>Increased drops from harvest nodes (this does not include fishing or creature drops such as leather)</li><li>+100% XP gains from every source</li><ul><li> These bonuses stack with other XP boosts such as scrolls or group multipliers</li></ul><li>+100% gold earned from monster kills, quest rewards, and similar sources</li></ul> 
<p>These bonuses are available in all of <i>ESO</i>'s zones! From the maddening stacks of Apocrypha to the serene isle of Artaeum, you can earn additional rewards no matter where you go!</p> 
<p>Remember, the Explorer's Celebration isn't a quest- or ticket-based event, and no unique achievements or collectibles are available. Additionally, the Impresario's shop will remain closed during this period as the merchant takes a bit of time for herself. The Explorer's Celebration runs for a limited time, so get exploring and have fun!</p> 
<p><i>The Explorer's Celebration starts on May 23 at 10AM EDT, and it runs until Tuesday, May 28 at 10AM EDT.</i></p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Events</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/e101d13d0410d44eae3082858431c07f.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Follow-up Q&A from ESO 10-Year Celebration Event Community Roundtable]]></title>
            <link>https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/658726/follow-up-q-a-from-eso-10-year-celebration-event-community-roundtable</link>
            <guid>https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/658726/follow-up-q-a-from-eso-10-year-celebration-event-community-roundtable</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 20:28:13 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[Below are some questions we received during the in-person Community Roundtable session at the ESO 10-Year Celebration Event in April that we promised to follow up with answers. We hope you find these answers helpful!<br><br><b>Q: Has there been any consideration for guild mounts that show off the guild tabard in some way? (Maybe a raised banner?) What would that take?</b><br>
A: We love this idea and hear it often from our many players in guilds. We've talked about this internally over the years as well. It's one of those things that is quite a bit trickier on the technical side than it sounds due to how guild tabards and overhead guild nameplates are coded, players being able to be in five guilds, etc. Know that we are aware of the desire for this as a guild feature.<br><br><b>Q: Have there been any discussions about integrated voice chat for PC/Mac, even if just to coordinate for instanced group content? Sometimes people don't want to install new apps to talk with each other and instead opt to communicate via in-game chat. This is especially painful for pick-up groups. </b><br>
A: While many players do opt to use Discord or other external voice chat solutions, we understand the pick-up group communication pain point. We've discussed integrated voice chat for PC/Mac servers and while it's not a hard "No, never", this is another one that requires a significant technical investment and isn't something we currently have on the roadmap.<br><br><b>Q: What happens to guilds if the guild leader passes away? What is the official process for passing on the role of guild leader?</b><br>
A: If a guild leader becomes inactive for at least 60 days, for any reason, someone from the guild can contact Customer Support to request transfer of the guild leader role. From there, we look to transfer the role of guild leader to the person who meets the following criteria:
<ul><li>Active within the last 60 days</li>
<li>A member of the next highest rank in the guild (one of the guild's existing "officers")</li>
<li>The person who has been in the guild the longest, if everyone else is the same guild rank</li>
<li>Not already the leader of another guild</li>
</ul>
We use this specific ranking system because it is fair, neutral, and allows us to be consistent. It also helps us minimize situations where guild leadership is stolen, passed to a newer member of the guild, etc. Once guild leadership is transferred, that person is welcome to pass it to someone else in the guild if they wish.<br><br>
While it is a bit more involved, there is also a process in place if someone wants or needs to claim a deceased family member's account. This process is in accordance with similar laws related to what happens to online accounts when someone passes away.<br><br><b>Q: Will we ever get proper guild halls in ESO?</b><br>
A: We love the idea of guild halls in ESO and recognize that our community has asked for them since the game launched. We have had many internal conversations about them over the years. The current challenge is the necessary caps. Much like the item limit caps in player housing, there is also a limit to how many characters can simultaneously be in a player home (it's 25). As with items, these caps are in place to ensure that players on lower spec machines don't encounter significant performance issues while in player homes.<br><br>
When we've asked ourselves in the past if a 25-person cap would feel good for a guild hall, especially if it's a guild of 500 active players, the answer has always been no. It's not the kind of guild hall experience we'd want to give you. So, while the idea of guild halls isn't completely off the table, it's important to us that we find a solution that allows us to do it right, and support the ability to have more than 25 simultaneous players in the guild hall.<br><br><b>Q: Do you have any plans for improved guild tools in ESO?</b><br>
A: While we don't have any specific plans to share currently, there are many things on our backlog that we'd love to do with ESO's guild system and the related tools. Over the years, we've collated pages of ideas from you, our community, as well as from internal suggestions.<br><br>
We do want to improve guilds, in general, and the tools that players use to run them. As with anything we add to ESO, it all comes down to time and resources, determining what will have the greatest positive impact for our players, and prioritizing against all the other items on our game features and improvements backlog.<br><br>
Please keep the suggestions and ideas coming, though. We do want to hear them!<br><br><b>Q: Will we ever get the ability to hide our guild tabard, like we can hide helms?</b><br>
A: This is another request that has come up often over the years. We understand how important this is to some of our players, especially our roleplay and ESO fashion enthusiasts! Like the suggestion for guild heraldry on mounts, this is something we do have on our backlog and want to improve the overall experience. It's also not as simple as turning off the visibility of armor pieces such helms and shoulders, for example, due to how our guild tabards and overhead guild nameplates are coded on the back-end.<br><br><b>Q: You all should send out surveys to guilds to get feedback about guild tools and what quality-of-life guild features players want. Would you consider that?</b><br>
A: Great idea! Yes, we will talk with our amazing Research team about creating a guild-focused survey. Thank you for the suggestion!<br><br>
One thing you all can do to help us is ask your guild members to consider opting into getting emails from us here. While we can share links to surveys on our social media channels, forums, and in Discord, being able to email it to more players who are in guilds would greatly help us hit a much broader and more diverse population.<br><br><b>Q: Could we get a solution for the guild MOTD text getting bumped/interrupted by automated game messages when typing it up? It's so frustrating when that happens!</b><br>
A: Thank you for sharing this with us! We agree that isn't a great experience. We've passed this along to our UX and QA teams for investigation.<br><br><b>Q: Will we ever get Steam achievements for ESO?</b><br>
A: Steam achievements require a separate (and additional) process from achievements on any other platform. Due to this, we have no current plans to add Steam achievements for ESO.<br><br><b>Q: We'd like to be able to get empty plots of existing player houses, or the ability to "remove" the house from the plot. Is that something you might consider?</b><br>
A: Interesting suggestion! Historically, the empty plots aren't nearly as popular as the houses; that said, we will pass this suggestion along to the Housing team for consideration. Due to how we build out the housing spaces, it is unfortunately not as simple as just "removing" the house from an existing space. Even existing player housing spaces would require additional world building where the house is/was.<br>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>Forum</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Register Today for the 10-Year Elder Scrolls Online Celebration Event in São Paulo, Brazil!]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66045</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66045</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Join up with other passionate fans for an evening of fun during Brazil's first ever Elder Scrolls Online in-person community event.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/379ede50239afc3e4021271dafddb3d2.jpg" /><p><i>Join up with other passionate fans for an evening of fun during Brazil's first ever Elder Scrolls Online in-person community event.</i></p> 
<p>The global celebration of <i>ESO</i>'s 10-Year Anniversary continues, this time taking us to São Paulo, Brazil, where we have prepared a party the local #ESOFam won't want to miss! </p> 
<p>On May 27, the Taverna Medieval will be host to the 10-Year Celebration event, Brazil's <b>first ever in-person community gathering</b> that promises a variety of fun, <i>Elder Scrolls</i>-themed activities! </p> 
<p>Attendees can expect an evening of non-stop Tamrielic entertainment, including potion crafting, archery training, rune readings, and more! Feeling peckish? Grab a slice of anniversary cake and enjoy an assortment of medieval bites while mingling with your fellow fans. We've even arranged several game stations with <i>ESO </i>ready to play.</p> 
<p>Eager to sign up? Click the button below and follow the instructions to register for this new in-person event. Note that places are limited, so don't hesitate to show your interest.</p><p><br></p><p>This event is one of many being hosted across the world, so be sure to keep an eye out for further news on upcoming celebrations you won't want to miss. Are you ready to join us in Brazil and continue celebrating <i>ESO</i>'s 10-Year Anniversary alongside your fellow community members? Let us know via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline" target="_blank">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>.</p><p><i>If you have any questions regarding event details, please reach out to us on our Brazilian social channels via <a href="https://twitter.com/BethesdaBrasil" target="_blank" style="">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/bethesdabrasil/" style="">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/BethesdaBrasil/" style="">Facebook</a>.</i></p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Community</category>
            <category>10th Anniversary</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/379ede50239afc3e4021271dafddb3d2.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Listen to The Elder Scrolls Online: Necrom Soundtrack Online Now!]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65643</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65643</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Grab your copy of the ESO: Necrom Official Soundtrack, now available for digital purchase and download!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/02/a97678539c0c7b6e14e2b8d25b4efd28.png" /><p><i>Grab your copy of the ESO: Necrom Official Soundtrack, now available for digital purchase and download!</i></p> 
<p>Immerse yourself in the weird and wonderful worlds of Apocrypha and the Telvanni Peninsula with the melodies featured on <i>The Elder Scrolls Online: Necrom</i> Official Soundtrack. You can get your hands on the collection right now from the following platforms:</p> 
<ul><li><a href="http://itunes.apple.com/album/id1742430033?ls=1&amp;app=itunes">Apple Music</a></li><li><a href="https://open.spotify.com/album/6IbTHbVWC7csK2lACOmgeI">Spotify</a></li><li><a href="https://music.amazon.com/albums/B0D2BDQB29">Amazon Music</a></li></ul> 
<p>Are you going to add the <i>Necrom</i> soundtrack to your music library? Let us know via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/ElderScrollsOnline">Facebook</a>!</p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Music</category>
            <category>Necrom</category>
            <category>Shadow Over Morrowind</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/02/a97678539c0c7b6e14e2b8d25b4efd28.png" length="0" type="image/png"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Anniversary Spotlight- Make A Home Away From Home With These Free Housing Rewards!]]></title>
            <link>https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/657959/anniversary-spotlight-make-a-home-away-from-home-with-these-free-housing-rewards</link>
            <guid>https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/657959/anniversary-spotlight-make-a-home-away-from-home-with-these-free-housing-rewards</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 14:22:38 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://us.v-cdn.net/5020507/uploads/editor/78/8yr54iz3smin.jpg"><br>
This is the official discussion thread for, "<a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65941">Anniversary Spotlight- Make A Home Away From Home With These Free Housing Rewards!</a>"<br><br><i>"Homeowners across Tamriel can claim the Sword-Singer's Redoubt House and friendly houseguests for FREE during May's 10-Year Anniversary promotion."</i>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>Forum</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Anniversary Spotlight—Make A Home Away from Home with These Free Housing Rewards]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65941</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65941</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Homeowners across Tamriel can claim the Sword-Singer's Redoubt House and friendly houseguests for FREE during May's 10-Year Anniversary promotion.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/ec015f0e2283df6f7f37c42795a7225e.jpg" /><p><i>Homeowners across Tamriel can claim the Sword-Singer's Redoubt House and friendly houseguests for FREE during May's 10-Year Anniversary promotion.</i></p> 
<h2>There's No Place Like Home</h2> 
<p>Part of the ongoing 10-Year Anniversary Celebration, the “Anniversary Spotlight—Hearth &amp; Home” kicks off today and continues until Friday, May 31, 2024. If you're a weary adventurer in need of a place to call home, you can pick up the all-new FREE Sword-Singer's Redoubt house and various other goodies during the promotional period. </p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/04/795f50a09dd23756ecd8977fe02c1ad5.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Log in to claim this home</i></p> 
<p>Collecting your complementary household is as simple as claiming the Sword-Singer's Redoubt as part of this month's <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65939">Daily Login Rewards</a>. You'll need to log in during May three times to get it—don't miss out!</p> 
<p>Of course, to transform this desert oasis into your new home, you'll need to decorate! Luckily, starting today, you can pick up various furnishings and houseguests on discount in the in-game Crown Store.</p> 
<h2>Host Friendly Houseguests </h2> 
<p>During the promotion period, you can claim the Necrom Guard Miraso houseguest from the in-game Crown Store <b>free </b>after earning the Party Planner achievement. To unlock this achievement, have three players visit your home simultaneously. Better start sending out those invitations!</p> 
<p>Additionally, you can also claim the Alchemy Houseguest <b>free </b>from the in-game Crown Store after completing the Expert Resin Harvester and Novice Alchemy Furnisher achievements. To earn the Expert Resin Harvester achievement, harvest 25 Alchemical Resin, and to unlock the Novice Alchemy Furnisher, learn any Alchemy formula.</p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/e9120514d38b418764e7b8375ed854b8.jpg" />
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/ded43ab4e89227fc8511ecbc56359bb8.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Unlock these two houseguests free! </i></p> 
<h2>Build Upon Your Endeavors</h2> 
<p>Throughout the Anniversary Spotlight, Daily and Weekly Endeavors will more frequently feature challenges related to housing, with increased rewards received upon completion. These include placing furnishings.</p> 
<h2>Welcome Home!</h2> 
<p>Experience the vast sea of opportunities for customization and decoration that came with owning your own household in Tamriel during the Anniversary Spotlight—Hearth &amp; Home! Don't miss your chance to claim valuable free rewards during this promotion period, taking place between now and May 31. How will you transform the Sword-Singer's Redoubt into your dream home? Share screenshots of the finished product with us via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>. </p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>10th Anniversary</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/ec015f0e2283df6f7f37c42795a7225e.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Crown Store Showcase—May 2024]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65943</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65943</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Check out these ancient artifacts, furry friends, and loads of furnishings that will transform your modest house into a palace, all arriving in the in-game Crown Store this May!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/5cb93b877bc43731b308c9736439a24b.jpg" /><p><i>Check out these ancient artifacts, furry friends, and loads of furnishings that will transform your modest house into a palace, all arriving in the in-game Crown Store this May!</i></p> 
<p>Take a peek at all the items arriving in the in-game Crown Store during May 2024. You can also check out what is currently available on the <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/crownstore">Crown Store page</a>. Do any of these goodies catch your eye? Visit the <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/buycrowns">Buy Crowns page</a> to acquire as many crowns as you need! Certain items and offers will be available for a limited time only, so be sure to read their details below and don't miss out.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>ESO Plus Deals</h2> 
<p>All ESO Plus™ members have access to a monthly selection of exclusive deals and items. You can find more information about them in <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/54825">this article</a>.</p> 
<p><b>Exclusive Free Items</b></p> 
<p><b>Statuette: Orc Warrior</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/e735e15239a9b9102e01a98cd4431e23.jpg" />
<p><i>A miniature statue of an Orc warrior emanating strength.</i></p> 
<p>The Statuette: Orc Warrior will be available in the Crown Store FREE, exclusively to ESO Plus Members on all platforms for a limited time, from May 30 to June 27, 2024, at 10AM EDT.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Painting: Infinite Archive</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/0acdcaa2fd0d8b91cdd7d0ed199736bf.jpg" />
<p><i>"Those whom Hermaeus Mora calls to the Infinite Archive may serve him—or may choose to leave. But who, upon understanding the limitless knowledge they may access, dares refuse the Lord of Secrets without feeling bereft forever after?"—Mage Allierwen</i></p> 
<p>The Painting: Infinite Archive will be available in the Crown Store FREE, exclusively to ESO Plus Members on all platforms for a limited time, from April 29 to May 30, 2024, at 10AM EDT.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Crafting</h2> 
<p><b>Crown Crafting Motif: Sunspire Style</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/886df7f89a1ef01f5456a01a23b39759.jpg" />
<p><i>Use to learn the Sunspire crafting style.</i></p> 
<p>The Crown Crafting Motif: Sunspire Style returns to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 2 to May 6, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item. Motif chapters, and very rarely the complete book, have a chance to drop from Nahviintaas in Normal or Veteran Sunspire.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Crown Crafting Motif: Welkynar</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/51218ce4b7609692172285d8d1fa91ec.jpg" />
<p><i>Use to learn the Welkynar crafting style.</i></p> 
<p>The Crown Crafting Motif: Welkynar will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 6 to May 13, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item. Motif chapters can be crafted by collecting Welkynar Bindings from the weekly quest for Cloudrest and ten Welkynar Bindings from defeating the final boss in Cloudrest.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Crown Crafting Motif: Annihilarch's Chosen</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/41419836f0a7eb88de48a4a4859b68ab.jpg" />
<p><i>Use to learn the Annihilarch's Chosen crafting style. </i></p> 
<p>The Crown Crafting Motif: Annihilarch's Chosen will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 20 to May 28, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item. Motif chapters, and very rarely the complete book, have a chance to drop from the reward chest after defeating Deadlands Oblivion Portals.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Outfit Styles</b></p> 
<p><b>Molag Kena Arms Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/4902e98ee01f99e0094c9881726beaf9.jpg" />
<p><i>Alter your weapon's appearance to match the Undaunted Molag Kena awards by using this complete set of Outfit styles.</i></p> 
<p>The Molag Kena Arms Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 6 to May 13, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item. The matching mask page will have a small chance to drop from Molag Kena from veteran White-Gold Tower. The matching shoulder page can be purchased from Urgarlag Chief-bane for 50 Undaunted Keys, or has a chance of dropping from Urgarlag's Mystery Coffer for 1 Key. Having the achievement “Ire of the Storm” increases the drop chances of both items.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Elder Scrolls Artifact: Sinweaver</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/2f2945532e96261e5c7f112bd5030d82.jpg" />
<p><i>Alter your two-handed sword's Outfit style with a replica of the Sinweaver Elder Scrolls Artifact, the legendary Elven claymore.</i></p> 
<p>The Elder Scrolls Artifact: Sinweaver will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 9 to May 16, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Selene Arms Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/d4b329ea500ec0668a1c499de865e314.jpg" />
<p><i>Alter your weapon's appearance to match the Undaunted Selene awards by using this complete set of Outfit styles.</i></p> 
<p>The Selene Arms Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 13 to May 20, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item. The matching mask page will have a small chance to drop from Selene from veteran Selene's Web. The matching shoulder page can be purchased from Glirion the Redbeard for 50 Undaunted Keys, or has a chance of dropping from Glirion's Mystery Coffer for 1 Key. Having the achievement “All Wrapped Up” increases the drop chances of both items.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Baron Zaudrus Arms Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/0d1e5b40aeb4a6dd8cb9e6bdba9f0ec2.jpg" />
<p><i>Alter your weapon's appearance to match the Undaunted Baron Zaudrus awards by using this complete set of Outfit styles.</i></p> 
<p>The Baron Zaudrus Arms Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 20 to May 28, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item. The matching mask page will have a small chance to drop from Baron Zaudrus from veteran Cauldron. The matching shoulder page can be purchased from Urgarlag Chief-bane for 50 Undaunted Keys, or has a chance of dropping from Urgarlag's Mystery Coffer for 1 Key. Having the achievement “Schemes Disrupted” increases the drop chances of both items.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Truth and Logic</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/07/945554111d463332a7a7cf4d87cb51e5.jpg" />
<p><i>Alter your weapon's appearance to match the Truth and Logic Weapons by using this complete set of Outfit styles.</i></p> 
<p>The Truth and Logic Outfit Style will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 28 to June 3, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Elder Scrolls Artifact: Spear of Bitter Mercy</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/9112db2481493934bc9b1fa09e52fe19.jpg" />
<p><i>Alter your staff's Outfit style with a replica of the Spear of Bitter Mercy Elder Scrolls Artifact, the signature weapon of the Daedric Prince Hircine.</i></p> 
<p>The Elder Scrolls Artifact: Spear of Bitter Mercy will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 30 to June 6, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<h2>Wardrobe</h2> 
<p><b>Costumes</b></p> 
<p><b>Nordic Knot Doublet and Breeches</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/5f3ccb9d5ab8a848bafef2fdbf140851.jpg" />
<p><i>"Nordic Knot designs symbolize the heritage of the people of Skyrim," says designer Jork of Windhelm. "This upscale ensemble pays tribute to that tradition, and looks good even on those not lucky enough to be Nords."</i></p> 
<p>The Nordic Knot Doublet and Breeches costume returns to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 13 to May 16, 2024, at 10AM EDT.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Shrike's Nocturnal Frock</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/cb99621e7a9c0b80dd1791294b54bad9.jpg" />
<p><i>Do you like to keep to the shadows, yet long for a striking look of your own? Any admirer of the Prince of Night and Darkness will appreciate this eye-catching costume.</i></p> 
<p>The Shrike's Nocturnal Frock costume will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 30 to June 6, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Telvanni Master Wizard</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/37d2cbd6372ebb33ee8d2968c1504c36.jpg" />
<p><i>Lesser mages are often surprised to find that the usual apparel of a Telvanni Master Wizard is more stately than ostentatious. The truth is, Wizard Lords such as Divayth Fyr have no need of gaudy display. Their power lies elsewhere.</i></p> 
<p>The Telvanni Master Wizard costume will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 20 to May 28, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<h2>Crate</h2> 
<p><b>Scalecaller Crate</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/fc1586244a8880a334ad7711df3737ce.jpg" />
<p><i>A mystery collection of Scalecaller-related items!</i></p> 
<p>Scalecaller Crates return to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 9 to May 23, 2024, at 10AM EDT.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Xanmeer Crate</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/f9baab7dc0449c7fba0cc17601fbbd0d.jpg" />
<p><i>A mystery collection of Murkmire related items!</i></p> 
<p>Xanmeer Crates return to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 23 to June 6, 2024, at 10AM EDT. Additionally, ESO Plus Members will receive a discount when purchasing the Xanmeer 15 Crate Bundle.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Furniture </h2> 
<p><b>Bust: Abnur Tharn</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/0a01525b1de77e006becfabdc0f8e6ff.jpg" />
<p><i>Experience the wisdom of Abnur Tharn within your very own home with this talking bust! Display this noble piece of statuary in a place of prominence so that you and every houseguest may listen intently to the former Grand Chancellor.</i></p> 
<p>The Bust: Abnur Tharn will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 2 to May 9, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Statue, Pride of Alkosh Hero</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/10fea1b6858009cc2f574ef223c959bb.jpg" />
<p><i>The Pride of Alkosh Hero brandishes an hourglass lantern while in a victory stance over a vanquished Dragon. The lantern shines forth with a warm glow, a bright beacon, or not at all; owner's choice!</i></p> 
<p>The Statue, Pride of Alkosh Hero will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 2 to May 9, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Furnishing Pack: Moon-Bishop's Sanctuary</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/8b14546e6e4c1739b3cabb3781d34d13.jpg" />
<p><i>Display your reverence for the Moons with this assortment of clerical Elsweyr furnishings. Luxurious tapestries, tasteful furniture, and even a target dro-m'Athra will make your home the envy of Khajiiti adepts everywhere.</i></p> 
<p>The Furnishing Pack: Moon-Bishop's Sanctuary will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 2 to May 9, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Furnishing Pack: Shadow and Stone</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/e0448cd99574ef2a96a502ddee4f6986.jpg" />
<p><i>By my hand blood enters the Marsh. By my deed the Marsh is fed and grows fertile. By my silent watch the Hist may thrive. Honor my doings, O Sithis, for my brethren show me but fear. Guard me not, O Sithis, for only my own strength honors you.</i></p> 
<p>The Furnishing Pack: Shadow and Stone will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 2 to May 9, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Furnishing Pack: Molag Bal</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/57b87346a4c139fd93317ab74e102a02.jpg" />
<p><i>Furnishings related to the Daedric Prince Molag Bal and Coldharbour.</i></p> 
<p>The Furnishing Pack: Molag Bal will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 9 to May 16, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Music Box, Diamond Melody</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/c246eac055cf547898977422d96d1087.jpg" />
<p><i>When activated, plays a music box composition of the traditional imperial song "Chim-el Adabal."</i></p> 
<p>The Music Box, Diamond Melody will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 9 to May 16, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Craglorn Multicultural Kitchen Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/cad04660576670638afc1599a8d23bab.jpg" />
<p><i>A selection of mainly Ra Gada-inspired cross-cultural kitchen furnishings, ideal for Earthtear Cavern.</i></p> 
<p>The Craglorn Multicultural Kitchen Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 9 to May 16, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Music Box, Songbird's Paradise</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/38cfdbbd622b6069ad08d2a5375fc9f5.jpg" />
<p><i>When activated, plays a music box arrangement of the uplifting "Songbird's Paradise" composition.</i></p> 
<p>The Music Box, Songbird's Paradise will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 16 to May 20, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Target Deadlands Harvester, Trial</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/3da4830f008a0b889872e0990b1a1d4d.jpg" />
<p><i>This is a large house item. This may be attacked and, when destroyed, will regenerate. This creature is equivalent to a veteran trial boss. Its abilities include granting a resource-restoring synergy opportunity, performance buffs, and self debuffs.</i></p> 
<p>The Target Deadlands Harvester, Trial will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 16 to May 23, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Furnishing Pack: Fargrave Bazaar</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/7c9007743da2f8a0444acddd043f94cd.jpg" />
<p><i>Bring Fargrave's Bazaar to your own abode with this collection of curious commodities. Floating books, suspicious specimens, drifting globules, and more await your mercantile merriment.</i></p> 
<p>The Furnishing Pack: Fargrave Bazaar will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 16 to May 23, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Furnishing Pack: Lord Vivec</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/d422359349635e3041d3552f5f082ff5.jpg" />
<p><i>Furnishings inspired by Lord Vivec, the Tribunal Temple, and Morrowind.</i></p> 
<p>The Furnishing Pack: Lord Vivec will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 16 to May 23, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Music Box, Fargrave Daydreams</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/68446297f808e44dde8f63b42154f28c.jpg" />
<p><i>When activated, this artistic rendering of the Celestial Palanquin plays a music box arrangement of the ominous "Fargrave Daydreams" composition.</i></p> 
<p>The Music Box, Fargrave Daydreams will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 23 to May 28, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Furnishing Pack: Tyrants of the Merethic Era</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/314edd4a992b7511ae062d3d21e03487.jpg" />
<p><i>These relics date back to the height of the Dragon Cult's power, long before the bloody revolution of the Dragon War. Though this particular Dragon's name is long forgotten, its story is still told by the ancient friezes found in its barrow.</i></p> 
<p>The Furnishing Pack: Tyrants of the Merethic Era will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 30 to June 6, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Music Box, Enigmas of the Elder Way</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/ddb493e96f6c92a22eca987db6a1b93a.jpg" />
<p><i>When activated, plays a music box arrangement of the mesmerizing "Enigmas of the Elder Way" composition.</i></p> 
<p>The Music Box, Enigmas of the Elder Way will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 30 to June 6, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Houses</h2> 
<p><b>Elinhir Private Arena</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/2eeaeb88ab0d6c9d2887febcfee3ee8c.jpg" />
<p><i>Pit Fighting promoter Crottus "Thumbs-Down" Lycus built this private arena atop the haunted ruins of Molavar because the land was cheap, and what could go wrong? He vanished mysteriously some time ago, and now his unique Arena Home is back on the market.</i></p> 
<p>The Elinhir Private Arena will return to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 16 to May 23, 2024, at 10AM EDT. Furnished and unfurnished versions will be available.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Houseguests</h2> 
<p><b>Caska</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/4a9d8d9634f3369a7349538bd5f3d9b1.jpg" />
<p><i>Caska the Senche-raht serves as the first mate on The Perfect Pounce, and she loves time off to pursue other interests, perhaps in your house! After adding Caska to your home, you can set her on a path, plus you and your visitors can speak with her.</i></p> 
<p>Caska will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 2 to May 9, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Hezehk</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/6a8b38d70b6c98b8b72f59b5b375ae88.jpg" />
<p><i>Fresh from Madam Whim's in Fargrave, this irrepressible Skaafin immediately imparts a surprisingly upbeat atmosphere to your abode. After adding Hezehk to your home, you can set him on a path, plus you and your visitors can speak with him.</i></p> 
<p>Hezehk will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 9 to May 16, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Sereyne</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/f3b691f6fbfbd499763cf3b1a8c769f7.jpg" />
<p><i>An outlaw with a talent for magic but a thirst for alcohol, Sereyne wants a cozy place to drink her troubles away. Perhaps you can provide? After adding Sereyne to your home, you can set her on a path, plus you and your visitors can speak with her.</i></p> 
<p>Sereyne will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 16 to May 23, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p> <b>Scruut</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/9a2ec54e60ae1c6b7aaf345beb59d3b9.jpg" />
<p><i>Divergences in fate's threads draw Scruut's attention. Yet, this mighty Watchling seeks your company until the Great Eye summons her. Coincidence? After adding Scruut to your home, you can set her on a path, plus you and your visitors can speak with her.</i></p> 
<p>The new Scruut houseguest will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 23 to May 30, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Arox the Mutilator</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/f64aaa9a27c2088ecda6d14e5dc46c08.jpg" />
<p><i>Kneel before the mighty Arox and he might just offer to crush your enemies for you! But, as a daedrat. Not his former much bigger self. After adding Arox to your home, you can set him on a path, plus you and your visitors can speak with him.</i></p> 
<p>Arox the Mutilator will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 30 to June 6, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Assistants</h2> 
<p><b>Xyn, Planar Purveyor</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/12dd55fdb222cd7b5d9b3fc0fe4cd9f2.jpg" />
<p><i>Xyn travels the Daedric realms looking for profitable opportunities. They'll happily take your goods (or those of your groupmates) in exchange for common mortal coinage.</i></p> 
<p>The new Xyn, Planar Purveyor will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 9 to May 16, 2024, at 10AM EDT.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Mounts</h2> 
<p><b>Dro-m'Athra Senche</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/bc3079fc4577c0014455caadac57136f.jpg" />
<p><i>The Senche-shaped dro-m'Athra are known to the Twilight Cantors as the sar-m'Athra, but everyone else just calls these eerie and uncanny mounts the Dro-m'Athra Senche.</i></p> 
<p>The Dro-m'Athra Senche mount returns to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 2 to May 6, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Spotted Duneracer Senche-raht</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/42eadc7022d663a151527a346ef162ec.jpg" />
<p><i>Years of winning racing competitions finally bored Hazazkheran, so he ran messages for the queen for a time. Alas, even that grew predictable. Now he wants to poke his whiskers into all the hidden corners of the world, perhaps with you.</i></p> 
<p>The Spotted Duneracer Senche-raht mount returns to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 6 to May 13, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Painted Wolf</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/aa393845450a0b38cf4066c46ad7de7c.jpg" />
<p><i>In the rugged badlands of central Hammerfell, even camels struggle to maneuver across the broken terrain. But wolves can go where even camels cannot, so the roving Redguards of the canyon lands have bred the local Painted Wolves into sure-footed mounts.</i></p> 
<p>The Painted Wolf mount will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 9 to May 13, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Riften Coalhorn Ram</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/5de2876c7731ea22af8c76645d96f2db.jpg" />
<p><i>None dare stare Riften's native ram in the eyes, it sees threats in many things, and only its owner can meet its gaze without needing to brace for an immediate headbutt. In short, would-be Riften Coalhorn Ram thieves are frequently airborne.</i></p> 
<p>The Riften Coalhorn Ram will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 28 to June 3, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Banded Guar Charger</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/9796950d1d85bf38d06322803f79e5b4.jpg" />
<p><i>A breed of guar bred for cavalry use, able to carry an armored warrior into battle.</i></p> 
<p>The Banded Guar Charger will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 30 to June 6, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Customized Action</h2> 
<p><b>Stonelore Split</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/b7bc6fc7b2b63976d5e55cfb21eb3820.jpg" />
<p><i>Trees grant gifts that linger after their passing. Druids recognize this gift as what it is, a blessing from Y'ffre. </i></p> 
<p>The Stonelore Split customized action will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 16 to May 20, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Malacath's Harvest</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/6b5f52a4c708a8abd963c2575e9f40be.jpg" />
<p><i>"Never underestimate any foe. And that includes the wilds of Wrothgar. Even the plants put up a fight here, which is why I use my ancestor's sharpest dagger and pray to Malacath with each sweep.” Ghaz of Orsinium.</i></p> 
<p>The new Malacath's Harvest customized action will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 30 to June 6, 2024, at 10AM EDT.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<h2>Pets</h2> 
<p><b>Dro-m'Athra Senche Cub</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/e501fd5cccbdf250f22e1e281f1c142f.jpg" />
<p><i>Combine Adorable with Abominable, and what do you get? The dro-m'Athra Senche Cub, the cutest thing ever to come out of the Dark Behind the World. Dance, kitten, dance!</i></p> 
<p>The Dro-m'Athra Senche Cub pet will return to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 2 to May 6, 2024, at 10AM EDT.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Dragontail Goat</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/3be02d6b67500e79088f7b5076b62475.jpg" />
<p><i>The brown Goats of the Dragontail Mountains are stronger than they look. There's a saying in Hammerfell: "Hits as hard as a Dragontail ram!"</i></p> 
<p>The Dragontail Goat pet will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 6 to May 13, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Vale Fawn</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/ce0467873f7b94be1ecb99b858666c68.jpg" />
<p><i>Though this adorable fawn's kin shimmer with hues different than its own, the first color ever seen was the pearly white glow on this one. Give it enough care and you can help it overcome its shyness, allowing it to cavort at your side.</i></p> 
<p>The Vale Fawn pet will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 13 to May 20, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Infernal Sep Adder</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/10e6028adc61b413856db7e89b952e0f.jpg" />
<p><i>Though it may look like it just crawled from the depths of the Deadlands, the Infernal Sep Adder is actually native to the higher altitudes of Hammerfell. As pets, they are not affectionate. Great conversation starters, though.</i></p> 
<p>The Infernal Sep Adder pet returns to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 20 to May 23, 2024, at 10AM EDT.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Ja'khajiit Khamira</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/35b8995e456060c6207d4fa7d28cf6e2.jpg" />
<p><i>Ready for action? Like Khamira herself, this kitten certainly is! With a roll and a hiss, Ja'khajiit Khamira enters your life, ready to face danger at your side.</i></p> 
<p>The Ja'khajiit Khamira pet will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 23 to May 28, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Anthorbred Avalanche Dog</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2021/11/f929b66cca21c527e1cc97aaa4540f73.jpg" />
<p><i>With this loyal dog at your side, you have a companion who can help you make it through even the most treacherous of avalanches in Pale Pass and other mountainous areas; even if it has to pull you out from under a pile of fallen snow and detritus.</i></p> 
<p>The Anthorbred Avalanche Dog pet returns to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 28 to May 30, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p>If you've been searching for some new furnishings or houseguests to populate your household, be sure to check out the in-game Crown Store this May! Want to pick up any of the items featured in this showcase? Don't forget to head over to the <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/crowns">Buy Crowns page</a> and stock up on crowns beforehand. Which housing accessories highlighted here are you looking to add to your homestead? Let us know via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline" target="_blank">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>. </p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Crown Store</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/5cb93b877bc43731b308c9736439a24b.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Daily Login Rewards—May 2024]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65939</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65939</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Keep cozy with a comfortable pile of rewards available just by logging in this May 2024.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/04/6eb60a409b1b03733f4ffdb84a1634e0.jpg" /><p><i>Keep cozy with a comfortable pile of rewards available just by logging in this May 2024.</i></p> 
<p>There are some huge login rewards coming to <i>The Elder Scrolls Online </i>you can claim in the month of May, including an entire house! Check out what exactly you can get below. Curious about Daily Login Rewards? Learn more by reading <a href="https://help.elderscrollsonline.com/#en/answer/41950">this help article</a>.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Sword-Singer's Redoubt—Day 3</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/04/795f50a09dd23756ecd8977fe02c1ad5.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Stay cool in the desert sun</i></p> 
<p>Make Hammerfell your home and get comfortable in this brand-new in-game house situated on the border of the Alik'r Desert and Bangkorai. Enjoy crystal caverns, oasis waters, and wide spans of sand and stone as part of the design of this remarkable reward.</p> 
<p>You'll receive the unfurnished house on just your third day of logins this month, starting things off with something spectacular. Speaking of spectacular, this house could be hinting at something special! You'll have to wait and see…</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Scalecaller Crown Crates—Days 4-8</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/04/07da169625f5e7a3e7bfcce2a2ef2af9.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Plunder Scalecaller's hoard</i></p> 
<p>Claim one crate a day for five days to collect five Scalecaller Crown Crates in total. You'll unlock creepy collectibles themed around Scalecaller Peak and Fang Lair, many of which are available for preview <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/26329">in this blog</a>.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Seals of Endeavor—Day 10</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/10/cbf054f9fa4122ee9be26996607da8d2.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Endeavor to get something nice</i></p> 
<p>More Seals of Endeavor make their way to you this month, helping you unlock the Crown Crate item of your dreams. Log in to claim a hefty purse of 500 Seals as your tenth daily reward this month. You can learn more about Seals of Endeavor <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/59925">in this blog</a>.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Bruma Spotted Pig pet—Day 14</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/04/f9a2004afe730908225e09db408854cb.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Too cute—don't even think about bacon!</i></p> 
<p>Don't you dare mention pork pies around this friendly fellow. He's far too charming to eat, but definitely a good option for head pats.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Xanmeer Crown Crates—Days 16-20</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/04/82e49ed369e9d008d5f33215e09040c3.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Treasures reclaimed from the mire</i></p> 
<p>More Crown Crates? That's right, there's another set of five crates that will be claimable over five more days. Acquiring all of them requires logging in at least twenty days in total, which seems like no time at all according to the Argonians of Black Marsh. You can preview a selection of the items available in the Xanmeer Crown Crates <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/55357">in this blog</a>.</p><p><br></p> 
<p>As fabulous as these rewards are, they are far from the only items on offer. To see everything, start your logins on May 1 and take a look at the full list! We think you'll find this month quite welcoming, so come right into Tamriel and make yourself at home.</p> 
<p>Which of the upcoming rewards are you most excited for? Let us know via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>. </p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Daily Rewards</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/04/6eb60a409b1b03733f4ffdb84a1634e0.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Gold Road Chapter & Update 42 Now Live on the PC/Mac Public Test Server!]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65909</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65909</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Wander paths untraveled by testing the new Gold Road Chapter and Update 42 base-game patch on the PC/Mac Public Test Server!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/04/b3ce5e4d284add2fef4a606f415460ad351985.jpg" /><p><i>Wander paths untraveled by testing the new Gold Road Chapter and Update 42 base-game patch on the PC/Mac Public Test Server!</i></p> 
<p>It's that time again—time to get an early look at <i>ESO</i>'s upcoming content and make the game better while you do so! The Public Test Server (PTS) has been updated to include the content from the <i>Gold Road</i> Chapter, including the new Scribing system, as well as the Update 42 base-game patch. To access the PTS environment, go to the Settings menu within the PC/Mac <i>ESO</i> launcher by toggling the “Show Public Test Environment” option. You can then download and access the test environment. Don't forget to leave feedback and report any bugs you come across by typing “/feedback” or “/bug” in chat.</p> 
<p>The PTS is open to any PC/Mac players, regardless of whether they own <i>ESO</i> or have pre-purchased <i>Gold Road</i>, so if you'd like to get your first look at the upcoming Chapter and more, be sure to jump in! </p> 
<p>For everything you need to know about <i>Gold Road</i>, Update 42, and this particular test, visit the <a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/656454/">PTS Patch Notes</a> on the official <i>ESO </i>forums.</p> 
<p>Are you excited for your first in-game look at West Weald and the all-new Daedric Prince? Let us know via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, or <a href="https://www.facebook.com/ElderScrollsOnline">Facebook</a>!</p> 
<p><i>The Elder Scrolls Online: Gold Road and Update 42 arrive June 3 on PC/Mac, and June 18 for Xbox and PlayStation consoles.</i></p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Community</category>
            <category>Update 42</category>
            <category>Gold Road</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/04/b3ce5e4d284add2fef4a606f415460ad351985.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enjoy Mountain Dew to Unlock a Free Mount, Experience Scroll, & More]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65855</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65855</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Get your hands on some Mountain Dew and you'll unlock in-game rewards, including the Karthwolf Charger mount, XP scrolls, and more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/04/fb1343a5009acb0888fcc83900e328e7289809.jpg" /><p><i>Get your hands on some Mountain Dew and you'll unlock in-game rewards, including the Karthwolf Charger mount, XP scrolls, and more. </i></p> 
<p>Right now, when you grab specially marked bottles of Mountain Dew, you can earn unique codes that allow you to unlock free in-game <i>ESO</i> items including: </p> 
<ul><li>Karthwolf Charger mount</li><li>Gold Coast Experience Scroll*</li></ul>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/04/5ac1bd7a337abd4f8b5d6ed793293c3c.jpg" />
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/04/2af627112155ed212f3db0dbaabf8d6b.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Unlock these rewards with Mountain Dew!</i></p> 
<p>To get started, visit the <a href="https://www.mtndewgaming.com/">Mountain Dew Gaming Rewards official website</a>, select Enter Code, register an account, and follow the prompts. You can then enter codes from any specially marked bottle of Mountain Dew and claim gaming rewards, including the above mount and experience scroll plus other Xbox goodies. Note that this promotion is available only for those who reside in North America. </p> 
<p>Enjoy a refreshing Mountain Dew and you'll unlock points for in-game rewards—easy! Are you planning to get your hands on the Karthwolf Charger mount and experience scroll? Let us know via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>.</p> 
<p><i>*Note: Gold Coast Experience Scrolls must be claimed within 14 days from in-game mail</i></p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/04/fb1343a5009acb0888fcc83900e328e7289809.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Grab Your Tickets for the 2024 ESO Tavern in Germany Today!]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65965</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65965</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Meet up with your fellow fans to enjoy a weekend of mirth and merry fun during this year's ESO Tavern community event.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/04/bdc53e8669d3f6a4c05a29882a079080.jpg" /><p><i>Meet up with your fellow fans to enjoy a weekend of mirth and merry fun during this year's ESO Tavern community event.</i></p> 
<p>The ESO Tavern returns once again this July as part of the year-long celebration of <i>ESO</i>'s 10-Year Anniversary Celebration! Since its inception in 2013, the ESO Tavern has remained the major European event for fans and developers alike to meet up and share their love for the game and community.</p> 
<p>This year, the ESO Tavern is moving to Wasserburg Heldrungen in Thuringia, Germany, and will run from Saturday, July 13 at 2PM CEST, until Sunday, July 14 at 4PM CEST. Community members will gather at this gorgeous castle to mingle, take part in various fun activities, and enjoy live musical performances. </p> 
<p>Throughout the weekend, Creative Director Rich Lambert, Art Director CJ Grebb, Project Lead Kira Ross Schlitt, Lead Encounter Designer Mike Finnigan, Lead Combat Designer Brian Wheeler, and Senior Community Manager Kai Schober will also be engaging with fans and celebrating <i>ESO</i>'s 10<sup>th</sup> anniversary. </p> 
<p>Admissions will be managed via Eventbrite. Please follow <a href="https://www.eventbrite.de/e/eso-taverne-2024-tickets-875930500707" target="_blank">this link</a> to register for the ESO Tavern 2024. There are three distinct ticket packages available:</p> 
<ul><li><b>The Weald package (€45)</b></li><ul><li>Includes a goodie bag with exclusive merch and codes, participation in all activities, access to musical performances, free campfire bread on a stick and marshmallows, as well as complimentary breakfast on Sunday.</li></ul><li><b>The Dawnwood package (€55)</b></li><ul><li>Includes everything from the Weald package plus one overnight stay in your own tent on the castle grounds, as well as car access to the site on arrival and departure.</li></ul><li><b>The Skingrad package (€75)</b></li><ul><li>Includes everything from the Weald package plus one overnight stay in one of the castle rooms*, and parking on the grounds.</li></ul></ul> 
<p>After registering for a ticket, you will be placed on a waiting list. If you'd like to register as a group (or just generally increase your odds of admission), email us directly at <a href="mailto:community_de@bethsofteurope.com">community_de@bethsofteurope.com</a> with "Tavern 2024" in the subject line. Include the email address(es) you used to register on Eventbrite and let us know why you would love to be invited. If you are accepted, you will need to confirm and pay for your purchase within 28 days. Your ticket(s) will remain refundable up to seven days before the event.</p> 
<p>Be sure to keep an eye out for further news on additional special guests and activities. Are you excited to continue celebrating <i>ESO</i>'s 10<sup>th</sup> birthday alongside your fellow fans in Germany? Let us know via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (Formerly Twitter</a>), <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>.</p> 
<p><i>*Note that the accommodation in the castle consists of (comfortable) youth hostel rooms. A total of eight 2-bedrooms, four 3-bedrooms, five 4-bedrooms, six 5-bedrooms, four 6-bedrooms and two 8-bedrooms are available. If you are interested in the Skingrad package, please organize yourselves into groups in advance and send an email with the subject "Skingrad" to </i><a href="mailto:community_de@bethsofteurope.com"><i>community_de@bethsofteurope.com</i></a><i> so that we can allocate the beds fairly.</i></p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Community</category>
            <category>10th Anniversary</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/04/bdc53e8669d3f6a4c05a29882a079080.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Take a Look at What Players are Saying About the 10th Anniversary Celebration Event!]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65955</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65955</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[See what attendees thought about the awesome experiences held at the 10th Anniversary Celebration event in Amsterdam this April.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/04/b44312df9e830a4a8651ca533cf5081d.jpg" /><p><i>See what attendees thought about the awesome experiences held at the 10<sup>th</sup> Anniversary Celebration event in Amsterdam this April.</i></p> 
<p>Celebrating a decade of <i>The Elder Scrolls Online</i>, the 10<sup>th</sup> Anniversary Celebration event in Amsterdam saw members of the #ESOFam join us from all over the globe. During this fun multi-day event showcasing the past, present, and future of <i>ESO,</i> attendees enjoyed unique panels and activities, mingled with fellow fans and game developers, and more. </p> 
<p>Check out what the <i>ESO </i>community members lucky enough to attend thought of the first major in-person event below.</p>
<a href="https://youtube.com/v/mi-VJDYhSEE?autoplay=1&rel=0"><img src="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/mi-VJDYhSEE/maxresdefault.jpg" /></a>
<p>Were you unable to make it to Amsterdam or eager to continue celebrating <i>ESO</i>'s 10<sup>th</sup> birthday? Lucky for you, there are more in-person events coming later during this year-long celebration!</p><p>Keep up with the latest announcements on these upcoming events by following us via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Community</category>
            <category>10th Anniversary</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/04/b44312df9e830a4a8651ca533cf5081d.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Anniversary Spotlight—Pick a Pocket to Claim the Thieves Guild DLC for Free & More]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65829</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65829</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Tamriel's stickiest fingers can claim the Thieves Guild DLC, a special mount, and more during this new 10-Year Anniversary promotion!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/04/b64ef251738565b6610a1b00e085a664.jpg" /><p><i>Tamriel's stickiest fingers can claim the Thieves Guild DLC, a special mount, and more during this new 10-Year Anniversary promotion! </i></p> 
<h2>Thieves of Tamriel </h2> 
<p>The Thieves Guild Anniversary Spotlight is part of the ongoing 10-Year Anniversary Celebration and begins this Monday, April 15, and continues until Monday, April 29, 2024. If you're the kind of adventurer who enjoys operating on the wrong side of the law, you'll enjoy additional rewards and goods by playing the outlaw during this time. </p> 
<p>To begin, should you earn (or have already earned) the “Pocket Picker” in-game achievement, you can claim the entire <i>Thieves Guild </i>DLC for free from the in-game Crown Store. Earning the Pocket Picker achievement is as easy as taking a sweetroll from a baby—simply pick the pocket of any citizen of Tamriel. If you're already an adept footpad, you might have not only Pocket Picker, but other achievements progressing from it that change the name in the in-game Achievements menu. Not to worry—should you have moved on to earn “Purse Snatcher” or “Sneak Thief Extraordinaire,” you can claim the <i>Thieves Guild</i> DLC all the same.</p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/04/4494a70f116fc065381a665b787798e1.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Pick a pocket to unlock a DLC!</i></p> 
<p>The <i>Thieves Guild</i> DLC grants you access to the Hew's Bane zone, the Thieves Guild organization and storyline, and the Thieves Guild Skill Line, helping you stay one step ahead of the law. </p> 
<p>Furthermore, <i>Thieves Guild</i> DLC owners can also claim the Treasure Hunter Horse mount for free from the in-game Crown Store by earning the Hew's Bane Cave Delver achievement. To unlock this achievement, simply visit and defeat the bosses within both explorable caves in the Hew's Bane zone. </p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/04/6447adf58112a16c5525c0ed21e0c895.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>The Treasure Hunter Horse mount</i></p> 
<h2>Endeavor to Get Rich</h2> 
<p>During the promotion window (April 15-29), some of the Daily and Weekly Endeavors will feature challenges relevant to both Thieves Guild and Dark Brotherhood members. For example, a Daily Endeavor may ask you to pick pockets or locks, while another may ask you to use poisons or even the Blade of Woe. Even better, the rewards for these thematic Endeavors will be increased—keep an eye out for them! </p> 
<h2>Dark Brotherhood Discounted!</h2> 
<p>If you don't own or have access to the <i>Dark Brotherhood</i> DLC and want to make the most out of the bonus Endeavors, you can acquire it during the promotion window from the Crown Store at 20% off. </p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/04/67cfd6ca2622f55e78b565419431ed03.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>We know … you'll enjoy this discount!</i></p> 
<p>The <i>Dark Brotherhood</i> DLC gives you access to the Gold Coast zone, the Dark Brotherhood organization and storyline, and access to both the Blade of Woe ability and the Dark Brotherhood Skill Line—everything an aspiring assassin needs!</p> 
<h2>Crime Pays</h2> 
<p>During the Thieves Guild Anniversary Spotlight, you can experience Tamriel on the wrong side of the law for free, simply by picking a pocket—easy! Are you planning a heist or two during this new promotion? Don't forget, this Anniversary Spotlight will take place only between April 15-29—don't miss it! Let us know if you're an existing or soon-to-be member of the Thieves Guild via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>. </p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>10th Anniversary</category>
            <category>Thieves Guild</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/04/b64ef251738565b6610a1b00e085a664.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ESO's 10th Anniversary Celebration Begins Now!]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65839</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65839</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Join us for 15 months of reveals, retrospectives, rewards, and more as we celebrate 10 amazing years of The Elder Scrolls Online.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/04/090e3b3410b3e3f18b3eab1d51e72ded.jpg" /><p><i>Join us for 15 months of reveals, retrospectives, rewards, and more as we celebrate 10 amazing years of The Elder Scrolls Online. </i></p> 
<p>We are thrilled to announce that <i>ESO</i>'s 10<sup>th</sup> Anniversary Celebration has officially begun! This massive celebration puts a spotlight on you (our players), the game, and the development team over the next 15 months*. </p>
<a href="https://youtube.com/v/sWP7NIOcBQo?autoplay=1&rel=0"><img src="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/sWP7NIOcBQo/maxresdefault.jpg" /></a>
<p>Kicking off with the (still ongoing) event in Amsterdam, the fun will continue all the way from today until June 2025. Between now and then, however, we're going to bring you a host of incredible 10<sup>th</sup> Anniversary-themed goodies, including new livestreams, special promotions, additional in-person events hosted all over the globe, and in-game activities and rewards. </p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/04/282ce3a2ad324038af70dcc7d911d144.jpg" />
<p>Want to ensure you don't miss a beat? Visit our <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/anniversary">official 10<sup>th</sup> Anniversary page</a> to stay on top of everything you need to know. </p> 
<h2>10<sup>th</sup> Anniversary Livestream &amp; Amsterdam Event</h2> 
<p>Of course, the celebration began today with the opening of the <i>ESO </i>10-Year Celebration Event in Amsterdam. Right now, attendees are mingling with their fellow #ESOFam members and the development team while also enjoying a host of unique panels, activities, and fun. </p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/04/5e725d7546636e28c6c198e161abf708.jpg" />
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/04/12f9e2cded2e59c88d5741a1cfefa7c6.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>10-Year Celebration In-Person Event</i></p> 
<p>Keep an eye out for recaps and highlights from this first massive in-person event soon, but until then, you can check out the opening acts of the celebration livestreamed via <a href="https://www.twitch.tv/bethesda">Twitch.tv/Bethesda</a>. </p> 
<h2>More In-Person Events Coming</h2> 
<p>The fun in Amsterdam is just the beginning of the 10<sup>th</sup> Anniversary festivities. There's going to be plenty of exciting events all over the globe between now and the celebration's end, too! </p> 
<p>Below, you can find some details on the next two upcoming in-person events. If you don't see an in-person event for your local territory, don't worry, we'll share more details on additional upcoming events in the coming months—keep an eye out. </p> 
<p><b><br></b></p><p><b>10<sup>th</sup> Anniversary Celebration at Elfia </b></p> 
<p>Join us at the Elfia fantasy cosplay festival this April! Meet fellow members of the #ESOFam and development team (including Creative Director Rich Lambert), enjoy giveaways, fun community cosplay-themed activities, and play the upcoming <i>Gold Road</i> Chapter!</p> 
<p><b>When: </b>April 20-21</p> 
<p><b>Where: </b>Haarzuilens, Netherlands</p> 
<p><b>Signup and tickets:</b> <a href="https://www.elfia.com/en/tickets/">https://www.elfia.com/en/tickets/</a></p> 
<p><b><br></b></p><p><b>2024 ESO Tavern </b></p> 
<p>The ESO Tavern returns in 2024, with a 10<sup>th</sup> Anniversary twist! Tickets for the longstanding community event will go on sale soon. Keep an eye on the official website for details. </p> 
<p><b>When: </b>July 13-14</p> 
<p><b>Where: </b>Wasserburg Heldrungen, Germany</p> 
<p><b>Signup and tickets:</b> Coming soon! </p> 
<h2>Alienware Plays ESO!</h2> 
<p>In celebration of <i>ESO</i>'s 10<sup>th</sup> anniversary, the team at Alienware is running a Steam community event, inviting all of Tamriel's adventurers to log in and unlock special community rewards. </p> 
<p>If you play <i>ESO</i> on Steam, you can help unlock a bunch of goodies including XP scrolls and even the coveted Karthwolf Charger mount, simply by playing the game between now and April 9. Don't own <i>ESO</i>? As it so happens, you can play free this week on Steam during the <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/freeplay">April 2024 Free Play Event</a>—go grab it!</p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/04/88b60d7712d5ec5af3ebfcbcd2a8acdf.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center; "><i>Kathwolf Charger mount</i></p><p>Visit <a href="https://na.alienwarearena.com/steam/community-event/the-elder-scrolls-online-community-event">Alienware Arena</a> for details on how you can sign up and participate in their Steam community event, and be sure to look out for additional 10<sup>th</sup> Anniversary Celebration fun from our friends at Alienware in the future. </p> 
<h2>A <i>Sneaky</i> April ESO Promotion</h2> 
<p>If you're accustomed to living on the wrong side of the law, you'll enjoy our upcoming 10<sup>th</sup> Anniversary April promotion. We're staying mum and <i>remaining silent</i> on the key details for now, but if you enjoy picking pockets and deadlier endeavors, you'll want to keep an eye out for more information later this month! </p> 
<h2>GeForce Now is Live! </h2> 
<p>In these last 10 years, <i>ESO </i>has found its way to many additional platforms beyond PC/Mac, and we are pleased to announce that this now includes NVIDIA GeForce NOW! <i>ESO</i> players** with access via <b>Steam</b> or the <b>Epic Games Store</b> can play the game streamed to their device of choice, including PC, Mac, under-powered laptop, and more using GeForce NOW cloud gaming. </p><p>Those who sign up with an Ultimate membership can stream at up to 4K and 120 fps, or experience the game at ultrawide resolutions on <a href="https://nvidia.custhelp.com/app/answers/detail/a_id/5462">supported devices</a>. </p> 
<p>To sign up or find more information and support, visit <a href="https://www.nvidia.com/en-us/geforce-now/">their official website</a>.</p> 
<h2>Celebrate on your Desktop or Device</h2> 
<p>To help you get into the spirit of the 10<sup>th</sup> Anniversary Celebration, we've created wallpaper versions of that incredible 10<sup>th</sup> Anniversary Celebration art. You can download it for your specific size below—enjoy!</p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/7c1c91911c4d35c3ead081d60af55b48.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center"><a href="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/28868d371805efdf0109a0e36ce4d794.jpg?no-resize" target="_blank">1920x1200</a> | <a href="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/0355d9307d6b5d536550995bf23a3837.jpg?no-resize" target="_blank">1920x1080</a> | <a href="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/9e4673e5efa313f9ad29e1d6e74e566f.jpg?no-resize" target="_blank">1242x2208</a> | <a href="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/f1b027fea5e687c8da5cfaa6f295519f.jpg?no-resize" target="_blank">1440x900</a> | <a href="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/de9f71c14e827b97fb33c21e39823b74.jpg?no-resize" target="_blank">1366x768</a> | <a href="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/e626add416beedbab45c87d373d0e1d1.jpg?no-resize" target="_blank">1280x1024</a> | <a href="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/690d218040e7477a177b915ff43624c8.jpg?no-resize" target="_blank">1024x768</a> | <a href="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/38c220b8fbc7f23deb7ea1c11987bc5e.jpg?no-resize" target="_blank">750x1334</a> | <a href="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/b6eb3e3285ede5e9cd84d29952f83ffe.jpg?no-resize" target="_blank">2880x2560</a> | <a href="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/ac2c45d7a1a453a4e45410c13a19f3e2.jpg?no-resize" target="_blank">2048x2732</a> | <a href="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/cbabe2b4efb1362c59a841ba88c1803b.jpg?no-resize" target="_blank">1536x2048</a> | <a href="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/01e5b5f8b50630943e4928420d66d771.jpg?no-resize" target="_blank">2560x1440</a> | <a href="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/7c1c91911c4d35c3ead081d60af55b48.jpg?no-resize" target="_blank;">3840x2160</a></p> 
<h2>10 Years of Adventures</h2> 
<p>We can't wait to reveal more about what we have in store for you during the 10<sup>th</sup> Anniversary Celebration, but don't worry, you won't have to wait long. Keep an eye on <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/">elderscrollsonline.com</a>, the <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/anniversary">10th Anniversary page</a>, and our social channels for the latest 10<sup>th</sup> Anniversary-themed fun and promotions. </p> 
<p>Are you excited to celebrate 10 years of <i>The Elder Scrolls Online</i> with us? Will you be joining us at any of our upcoming in-person events? Let us know via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>. </p> 
<p><i>*Why 15 months? While ESO initially launched for PC/Mac on April 2014, console launch was on June 2015, and we want to celebrate both! </i></p> 
<p><i>**Available in </i><a href="https://nvidia.custhelp.com/app/answers/detail/a_id/5023/~/what-are-the-supported-locations-for-geforce-now%3F"><i>supported GeForce NOW and GeForce NOW Alliance territories</i></a><i>. Currently requires ESO on Steam or the Epic Games Store to stream on GeForce NOW. GeForce NOW is not available on consoles.</i></p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>10th Anniversary</category>
            <category>Events</category>
            <category>Community</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/04/090e3b3410b3e3f18b3eab1d51e72ded.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Claim Free ESO Currency and Consumables with Xbox Game Pass]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65763</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65763</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Sign up for Xbox Game Pass Ultimate and collect free perks including a series of in-game ESO rewards!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/04/683b754a867a6be9f37c32434ca6921d.jpg" /><p><i>Sign up for Xbox Game Pass Ultimate and collect free perks including a series of in-game ESO rewards!</i></p> 
<p>Starting today, if you're an Xbox player, you can unlock bonus in-game items via your <a href="https://www.xbox.com/en-US/xbox-game-pass">Xbox Game Pass Ultimate</a> subscription. The first set, 10<sup>th</sup> Anniversary Pack #1, is now available via your Ultimate subscription, with more rewards arriving in future packs later in 2024 (be sure to keep an eye out for them). </p> 
<p>What's in 10<sup>th</sup> Anniversary Pack #1?</p> 
<ul><li>3× Grand Gold Coast Experience Scrolls</li><li>500 Seals of Endeavor</li></ul> 
<p>That's a trio of scrolls for massively increased experience gain and a sweet stack of Seals of Endeavor, which you can use to purchase Crown Crate goods. For more information on Seals of Endeavor, see <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/59925">this blog</a>.</p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/990e7c27d4c48bcf20d812439d8d58c4.jpg" />
<p>From now until June 2, 2024 at 12PM EDT, you can claim 10<sup>th</sup> Anniversary Pack #1 from your Xbox dashboard by following these simple steps:</p> 
<ol><li>Navigate to your Xbox Home dashboard and select Game Pass</li><li>Navigate to Perks</li><li>Find and select the <i>ESO </i>perks (10<sup>th</sup> Anniversary Pack #1)</li><li>Select the Claim button to receive a code</li><li>Select Redeem code and input it into the code field</li><ol><li>It will auto-populate the code field—do not alter it</li></ol><li>Select Check Code and then Next</li><li>Finally, select Confirm to receive your in-game items!</li></ol> 
<p>Once you've completed this process, you'll be able to get your Grand Gold Coast Experience Scrolls and Seals of Endeavour in game*.</p> 
<p><a href="https://www.xbox.com/en-US/xbox-game-pass">Purchase an Xbox Game Pass Ultimate Subscription</a>, navigate to your Game Pass perks, and claim your rewards. It's that simple. Ready for some sweet perks? Let us know how you're using your in-game rewards via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>. </p> 
<p><i>*Note: Items must be claimed within 180 days from in-game mail</i>. <i>Limit one pack per player, per account.</i></p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Community</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/04/683b754a867a6be9f37c32434ca6921d.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Begin Your Elder Scrolls Online Adventure During the April 2024 Free Play Event]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65725</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65725</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Explore Tamriel and realms beyond free of charge during the April 2024 Free Play Event!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/b0d7469f15502abf69180b596e230fd8.jpg" /><p><i>Explore Tamriel and realms beyond free of charge during the April 2024 Free Play Event!</i></p> 
<h2>Adventure Awaits!</h2> 
<p><i>The Elder Scrolls Online</i> April 2024 Free Play Event is now live and continues until Tuesday, April 9, 2024. Throughout this event, you can experience the vast world of Tamriel and its many stories and adventures for<b> FREE</b> on PC/Mac, Xbox consoles, and PlayStation consoles. </p> 
<p>During the Free Play event, you gain access to the <i>ESO</i> base game, including four unique classes (Sorcerer, Nightblade, Templar, and Dragonknight), 24 different zones, and the ability to participate in <i>ESO</i>'s various PvP game modes.</p> 
<p>Ready to begin? Head over to our <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/freeplay">Free Play page</a> and select your platform of choice. Note that if you've already begun your <i>ESO </i>adventure during a prior Free Play event, you can hop back in without any loss of progression!</p><p><br></p><p>Finally, any new accounts created during this period will receive 500 complimentary crowns to spend in the in-game Crown Store.</p><p>Once the Free Play event concludes, you can continue right where you left off by picking up your copy of <i>ESO</i> from the <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/joinus">Buy Now page</a>.</p><h2>Explore Tamriel for Free!</h2><p>Whether you are a new player or a returning adventurer, the April 2024 Free Play Event is the perfect opportunity to dive into the massive world of fantasy that is Tamriel's Second Era!</p><p><i>The Elder Scrolls Online April 2024 Free Play Event runs from Tuesday, April 2, 2024, until Tuesday April 9, 2024.</i></p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Sales</category>
            <category>Free Play</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/b0d7469f15502abf69180b596e230fd8.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Seize Sizable Savings on the ESO Base Game & Necrom During the 2024 April Sale]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65751</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65751</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Whether you're looking to enter Tamriel for the first time or stocking up on Crowns, the 2024 April Sale has a deal for you!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/ec1cf0f733db1f6a58ffa304218ad0e5.jpg" /><p><i>Whether you're looking to enter Tamriel for the first time or stocking up on Crowns, the 2024 April Sale has a deal for you!</i><br></p> <h2>April Savings</h2> <p>Let there be no fooling around—April is great for savings! The 2024 April Sale offers up to 75% off <i>The Elder Scrolls Online Standard Edition</i> and up to 67% off various editions of 2023's <i>Necrom</i> Chapter. The sale is active on all platforms for a limited time, although access to discounts for certain <i>Necrom </i>editions may vary depending on your platform of choice.</p> <p>The <i>Elder Scrolls Online Standard Edition</i> offers the full <i>ESO </i>base game, which includes four of the game's classes (Sorcerer, Nightblade, Templar, and Dragonknight), 24 unique zones to explore, and access to <i>ESO's </i>PvP game modes such as the Battlegrounds and the Alliance War.</p> <p><i>The Elder Scrolls Online: Necrom </i>was 2023's major release, and both the <i>Necrom Collection</i> and <i>Deluxe Necrom Collection</i> provide access to previous Chapters, too. <i>Necrom</i> itself offers two new zones, the mage-ruled Telvanni Peninsula and the eldritch realm of Apocrypha, access to the Arcanist class, and more. For more information on what <i>Necrom </i>has to offer, <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/updates/chapter/necrom">visit this Chapter page</a>.</p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/fa4c62b0445bbd16b982c8899ffd31fc.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center"><i>Discover the weird and wonderful Necrom Chapter</i></p> <h2>Platform Sale Information</h2> <p>Check out the dates listed below to know when the 2024 April Sale will be live on your platform of choice, including specific editions:</p> <p><b>Xbox</b></p> <ul><li>Standard Edition—March 29-April 18</li><li>All <i>Necrom</i> Editions—March 29-April 18</li></ul> <p><b>PlayStation</b></p> <ul><li>Standard Edition—March 27-April 10</li><li>All <i>Necrom</i> Editions—March 27-April 10</li></ul> <p><b>PlayStation Europe</b></p> <ul><li>Standard Edition—March 27-April 10</li><li>All <i>Necrom</i> Editions—March 27-April 10</li></ul> <p><b>PlayStation Asia</b></p> <ul><li>Standard Edition—March 27-April 10</li><li>All <i>Necrom</i> Editions—March 27-April 10</li></ul> <p><b>PlayStation Japan</b></p> <ul><li>Standard Edition—March 27-April 10</li><li>All <i>Necrom</i> Editions—March 27-April 10</li></ul> <p><b><i>Elder Scrolls Online</i> Store</b></p> <ul><li>Standard Edition—April 2-April 16</li><li>All <i>Necrom</i> Editions—April 2-April 16</li></ul> <p><b>Steam Store</b></p> <ul><li>Standard Edition—April 2- 16</li><li>All <i>Necrom</i> Editions—April 2-16</li></ul> <p><b>Epic Games Store</b></p> <ul><li>Standard Edition—April 2-9</li><li>Deluxe <i>Necrom</i> Editions—April 2-9</li></ul> <p>Head over to our <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/joinus">Buy Now page</a> to get ahold of these discounts and set yourself up for savings on your next adventure!</p><h2>Treat Yourself and Save on Select Crown Packs</h2><p>Not only is the game itself on sale, but from <b>April 3-10</b>, you can also save on select Crown Packs. Grab that new in-game pet or mount that caught your eye, or maybe stock up for later! Check out the individual Crown Pack discounts below:</p><ul><li>21,000 Crown Pack—40% off</li><li>14,000 Crown Pack—35% off</li><li>5,500 Crown Pack—30% off</li><li>3,000 Crown Pack—25% off</li><li>1,500 Crown Pack—20% off</li></ul><p> </p><p>You can make use of this sale right now by visiting our <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/crowns">Buy Crowns page</a>. Be sure to peruse the in-game Crown Store to see all the great items you can spend your new bounty on!</p><p><br></p><p><i></i></p> <p>Don't forget, you can try out <i>The Elder Scrolls Online</i> <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65725">for free right now</a> until April 9 and continue your adventures (with no loss of progression) after that by picking up the game during the April Sale—easy! </p> <p>Are you ready to dive into the land of Tamriel? Let us know how your journey begins via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline;">Facebook</a>. </p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Sales</category>
            <category>Necrom</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/ec1cf0f733db1f6a58ffa304218ad0e5.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Crown Store Showcase—April 2024]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65787</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65787</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Preview the new and returning collectibles coming to the in-game Crown Store this April and celebrate ESO's 10th Anniversary with something nice for yourself!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/7bc8c621513901a19927b46903d5fc91.jpg" /><p><i>Preview the new and returning collectibles coming to the in-game Crown Store this April and celebrate ESO's 10th Anniversary with something nice for yourself!</i></p> 
<p>Below, you can preview all the items available in the in-game Crown Store during April 2024. Don't forget to also check out what is currently available on the <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/crownstore">Crown Store page</a>. Fancy any of these goods? Then be sure to head over to the <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/buycrowns">Buy Crowns page</a> to secure however many crowns you need! Certain items and offers will be available for a limited time only, so be sure to read their details below and don't miss out.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>ESO Plus Deals</h2> 
<p>All ESO Plus™ members have access to a monthly selection of exclusive deals and items. You can find more information about them in <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/54825">this article</a>.</p> 
<p><b>Exclusive Free Items</b></p> 
<p><b>Painting: Infinite Archive</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/0acdcaa2fd0d8b91cdd7d0ed199736bf.jpg" />
<p><i>"Those whom Hermaeus Mora calls to the Infinite Archive may serve him—or may choose to leave. But who, upon understanding the limitless knowledge they may access, dares refuse the Lord of Secrets without feeling bereft forever after?"—Mage Allierwen</i></p> 
<p>The Painting: Infinite Archive will be available in the Crown Store FREE, exclusively to ESO Plus Members on all platforms for a limited time, from April 29 to May 30, 2024, at 10AM EDT.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Crown Gem and Seals of Endeavor Items</h2> 
<p><b>Mounts</b></p> 
<p><b>Novelty Stick Dragon</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/2c6c8f6504104b1e909830c543adc594.jpg" />
<p><i>During the Jester's Festival, even the lowliest of commoners can pretend to be a mounted knight with a whimsical Novelty Stick steed. Dragons are popular in the Ebonheart Pact.</i></p> 
<p>The Novelty Stick Dragon mount will be available for Crown Gems and Seals of Endeavor on all platforms for a limited time, from April 1 to April 4, 2024, at 10AM EDT.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Cold-Flame Epidermis</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/288f4ea918bcdc28da553a768e047d87.jpg" />
<p><i>Fancy Cold-Flame Atronachs, do you? Their frozen blue flames? That rock-hard physique? Well, now you can make those elements your own! Perfect for when you need to give someone the cold shoulder.</i></p> 
<p>The Cold Flame Epidermis skin will be available for Crown Gems and Seals of Endeavor on all platforms for a limited time, from April 25 to May 9, 2024, at 10AM EDT.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<h2>Adornments</h2> 
<p><b>Crimson Trickster Face Paint</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/2e2722fad696e55c861898e6e71b834a.jpg" />
<p><i>The Crimson Trickster hides his face with painted smiles and eerie grace. Two-thirds red and one-third white, this comic face is quite a sight! If mischief is what brings you glee, this paint will suit your revelry!</i></p> 
<p>The new Crimson Trickster Face Paint will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from April 1 to April 4, 2024 at 10AM EDT.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Druidic Knotwork Body Tattoos</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/cf9911faa88203d52cc76514ee0070c0.jpg" />
<p><i>To the druids, the repetition of one braid forming three-sided shapes is a symbol that all three druidic circles share the same goals. A reminder that unity eclipses the differences in how they revere Y'ffre.</i></p> 
<p>The Druidic Knotwork Body Tattoos return to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, starting April 22 to April 25, 2024, at 10AM EDT.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Prize-Hunter's Patch</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/47f3ee9b76e123fa8120d4bb188008a6.jpg" />
<p><i>Had your eye on the prize a bit too much, eh? Well, cover up that wound with this stylish patch.</i></p> 
<p>The Prize-Hunter's Patch will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from April 29 to May 2, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<p><br></p><h2>Crafting</h2> 
<p><b>Crown Crafting Motif: Tsaesci Style</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/f80480bbc6ee22c8cce059dbfedda51e.jpg" />
<p><i>Use this motif to craft items in the Tsaesci style.</i></p> 
<p>The Crown Crafting Motif: Tsaesci Style returns to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from April 3, at 1PM EDT to April 11, 2024, at 10AM EDT.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Crown Crafting Motif: Icereach Coven</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/0e5f23d0480e74b01a123e4fd4d9cbce.jpg" />
<p><i>Use to learn the Icereach Coven crafting style. The Icereach Coven motif has a chance to drop by killing the final boss in Icereach.</i></p> 
<p>The Crown Crafting Motif: Icereach Coven Style will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from April 11 to April 15, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item. Icereach Coven Motif chapters, and very rarely the complete book, have a chance to drop from the Icereach Coven in Icereach on at least veteran difficulty.</p><p><br></p><p><b>Crown Crafting Motif: Crimson Oath</b><br></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/2dedee12529d48788730aedd5152a253.jpg" />
<p><i>Use to learn the Crimson Oath crafting style. Also has a chance to drop by defeating the final boss in The Dread Cellar dungeon.</i></p> 
<p>The Crown Crafting Motif: Crimson Oath Style returns to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from April 25 to April 29, 2024, at 10AM EDT. Crimson Oath Motif chapters, and very rarely the complete book, have a chance to drop from the Magma Incarnate in The Dread Cellar on at least veteran difficulty.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Outfit Styles</b></p> 
<p><b>Cadwell's Kitchen Style Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/0e1bd09ab83a8b339971e465b925e554.jpg" />
<p><i>This includes a complete set of Outfit looks for armor in the Cadwell's Kitchen style.</i></p> 
<p>The Cadwell's Kitchen Style Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from April 1 to April 4, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Earthbone Ayleid Arms Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/7938147be43cd82f298d277ae3decaeb.jpg" />
<p><i>Alter your weapon's appearance to match the Earthbone Ayleid Weapons by using this complete set of Outfit styles.</i></p> 
<p>The Earthbone Ayleid Arms Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time during the Anniversary Jubilee. Stay tuned for event details! Matching armor pages will have a small chance to drop from Anniversary Jubilee Gift Boxes. Bound versions of the armor pages can be purchased from the Impresario for 5 Event Tickets each during the event.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Elder Scrolls Artifact: Spellbreaker Shield</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/f7a4b1d269355e95a3e5a0d46bef4da3.jpg" />
<p><i>Alter your shield's Outfit style with a replica of the Spellbreaker Elder Scrolls Artifact, the signature shield of the Daedric Prince Peryite.</i></p> 
<p>The Elder Scrolls Artifact: Spellbreaker Shield will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from April 8 to April 11, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Iceheart Arms Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/ca8b3e9479f1d0f61241f4800cebf23c.jpg" />
<p><i>Alter your weapon's appearance to match the Undaunted Iceheart awards by using this complete set of Outfit styles.</i></p> 
<p>The Iceheart Arms Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from April 11 to April 15, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item. The matching mask page will have a small chance to drop from Drodda of Icereach from Veteran Direfrost Keep. The matching shoulder page can be purchased from Glirion the Redbeard for 50 Undaunted Keys, or has a chance of dropping from Glirion's Mystery Coffer for 1 Key. Having the achievement “A Dish Served Cold” increases the drop chances of both items.</p> 
<p> </p> 
<p><b>Kjalnar's Nightmare Arms Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/b7ad76c63274f12a401c451a4db3f878.jpg" />
<p><i>Alter your weapon's appearance to match the Undaunted Kjalnar's Nightmare awards by using this complete set of Outfit styles.</i></p> 
<p>The Kjalnar's Nightmare Arms Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from April 22 to April 25, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item. The matching mask page will have a small chance to drop from Kjalnar Tombskald from Veteran Unhallowed Grave. The matching shoulder page can be purchased from Urgarlag Chief-bane for 50 Undaunted Keys, or has a chance of dropping from Urgarlag's Mystery Coffer for 1 Key. Having the achievement “Skull Smasher” increases the drop chances of both items.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Zaan Arms Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/7e04597c4561ed13607b206bde4b45e5.jpg" />
<p><i>Alter your weapon's appearance to match the Undaunted Zaan rewards by using this complete set of Outfit styles.</i></p> 
<p>The Zaan Arms Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from April 25 to April 29, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item. The matching mask page will have a small chance to drop from Zaan the Scalecaller from Veteran Scalecaller's Peak. The matching shoulder page can be purchased from Urgarlag Chief-bane for 50 Undaunted Keys, or has a chance of dropping from Urgarlag's Mystery Coffer for 1 Key. Having the achievement “Breaker of Spells” increases the drop chances of both items.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Claw-Dance Acolyte Arms Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/85989b2181b7ec8a903d8c7fe2b755a4.jpg" />
<p><i>Alter your weapon's appearance by using this complete set of Claw-Dance Acolyte Outfit styles.</i></p> 
<p>The Claw-Dance Acolyte Arms Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from April 29 to May 2, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<h2>Crate</h2> 
<p><b>Frost Atronach Crate</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/f2ad1c9727ae498ada023553a42e9afb.jpg" />
<p><i>A mystery collection of Frost Atronach-related items!</i></p> 
<p>Frost Atronach Crates return to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from April 11 to April 25, 2024, at 10AM EDT.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Flame Atronach Crate</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/17805b99c47a5d6abc54a9129546b1a5.jpg" />
<p><i>A mystery collection of Flame Atronach-related items!</i></p> 
<p>Flame Atronach Crates return to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from April 25 to May 9, 2024, at 10AM EDT.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<h2>Wardrobe</h2> 
<p><b>Costumes</b></p> 
<p><b>Sisei Flowering Dress</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/ef05a2a62cf0c5b20c74b07a0ccba58f.jpg" />
<p><i>Early in the year, Argonians don colorful garments and invite Blackwood visitors do the same. Will you join them in their celebration of this season of growth, romance, and renewal?</i></p> 
<p>The new Sisei Flowering Dress costume will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from April 3, at 1PM EDT to April 11, 2024, at 10AM EDT.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Breton Hero Armor</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/f36e2e976ffd0257ea5f349726788eae.jpg" />
<p><i>This costume pays tribute to a legendary Breton hero of the Daggerfall Covenant. Now you can honor this nameless rogue by adopting his intimidating outfit.</i></p> 
<p>The Breton Hero Armor costume will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from April 8 to April 15, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Elven Hero Armor</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/c28d3c0ba891f01167f7a9f55f1771ac.jpg" />
<p><i>This costume pays tribute to a legendary High Elven hero of the Aldmeri Dominion. Now you can honor this nameless Altmer by adopting her epic appearance.</i></p> 
<p>The Elven Hero Armor costume will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from April 8 to April 15, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Nord Hero Armor</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/3f0c9237cbc27f1071838fe4cb12b108.jpg" />
<p><i>This costume pays tribute to a legendary Nord hero of the Ebonheart Pact. Now you can honor this nameless warrior by adopting his savage appearance.</i></p> 
<p>The Nord Hero Armor costume will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from April 8 to April 15, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Song of the Night Ensemble</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/17bc9ec9fe22f9aa45ec40ca043e5e52.jpg" />
<p><i>A Redguard lady's formal wear, like this ensemble by Sar'aq of Sentinel, is made of light fabric designed to be both beautiful and impressive, a constant reminder of the wearer's heritage and grace. As Sar'aq says, "Glamor is for all of us!"</i></p> 
<p>The Song of the Night Ensemble costume will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from April 15 to April 18, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Treasure Hunter</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/f4efd40c80181553ea3afda25a002b78.jpg" />
<p><i>The serious treasure hunter knows it's really all about the gear.</i><i> Whether you're exploring subterranean catacombs, ancient ruins, or a shattered shipwreck, when you run into an obstacle, you want to have the right tool at hand.</i></p> 
<p>The Treasure Hunter costume will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from April 15 to April 29, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Mercymother's Attire</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/a3019943485f033fdb333b6310a3087e.jpg" />
<p><i>This exquisite garb was created in honor of Almalexia's gentle grace and leadership over the centuries since Red Mountain. A devotional surrogate often wears this attire during the days-long observation called the Fast of Forebearance.</i></p> 
<p>The Mercymother's Attire costume returns to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from April 18 to April 25, 2024, at 10AM EDT. </p> 
<p> </p> 
<h2>Events </h2> 
<p><b>Currency</b></p> 
<p><b>Event Tickets</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/33ae7b7ecc92a94706137c214285214f.jpg" />
<p><i> A ticket used to purchase rare goods from The Impresario, Event Merchant. Curious as to what goods? Well, chat with her to see what she has to offer!</i></p> 
<p>Single Event Tickets will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time during the Anniversary Jubilee. Stay tuned for event details! Event Tickets are also giftable to other players from within the Crown Store.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<h2>Furniture </h2> 
<p><b>Furnishing Pack: Dibella's Garden</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/6a6da1ab1dc66e575f82952f93f1bd16.jpg" />
<p><i>The Lady of Love, Art, and Affection teaches us to treasure the gifts of friendship and to open our hearts to the mysteries of love. In her divine words, "No matter the seed, if the shoot is nurtured with love, will not the flower be beautiful?"</i></p> 
<p>The Furnishing Pack: Dibella's Garden will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from April 3, at 1PM EDT to April 11, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p><p><b>Music Box, Mad God's Garden</b><br></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/abd87a0827e9f65529c98e2cf8482765.jpg" />
<p><i>When activated, plays a music box arrangement of the frenetic "Mad God's Garden" composition.</i></p> 
<p>The new Music Box, Mad God's Garden will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from April 3, at 1PM EDT to April 11, 2024, at 10AM EDT.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Statue of Sai Sahan</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/a7ad029e15491d4009ce401324210e81.jpg" />
<p><i>By using an array of vibrant illusionary effects, this impressive statue of Sai Sahan makes for a stunning focal piece within your home. One such effect even puts a sword within the hand of this Redguard swordmaster!</i></p> 
<p>The new Statue of Sai Sahan will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from April 3, at 1PM EDT to April 11, 2024, at 10AM EDT.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Music Box, Y'ffre in Every Leaf</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/7f01973e6ec8c91bd478ab787e104243.jpg" />
<p><i>When activated, plays a music box arrangement of the Aldmeri Dominion "Y'ffre in Every Leaf" composition.</i></p> 
<p>The Music Box, Y'ffre in Every Leaf will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from April 8 to April 11, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Music Box, Sands of the Alik'r</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/8334a7cbb5f423599b8136b8c8468783.jpg" />
<p><i>When activated, plays a music box arrangement of the Daggerfall Covenant "Sands of the Alik'r" composition.</i></p> 
<p>The Music Box, Sands of the Alik'r will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from April 8 to April 11, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Music Box, Hinterlands</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/74c81165efdcfe81530a69a2d4b6fd7e.jpg" />
<p><i>When activated, plays a music box arrangement of the Ebonheart Pact "Hinterlands" composition.</i></p> 
<p>The Music Box, Hinterlands will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from April 8 to April 11, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Furnishing Pack: Hubalajad's Final Treasure</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/df576fb79906243446c88b5b47deb1bb.jpg" />
<p><i>No Prince of the Ra Gada would be caught dead without the appropriate (and extravagant) funerary offerings for his tomb. Not to mention the requisite Mournful Aegis to welcome any unexpected guests!</i></p> 
<p>The Furnishing Pack: Hubalajad's Final Treasure returns to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from April 18 to May 2, 2024, at 10AM EDT.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Music Box, Dreams of Yokuda</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/e9922bda5cf34543c949b7b0dd601376.jpg" />
<p><i>When activated, plays a music box arrangement of the soothing "Dreams of Yokuda" composition.</i></p> 
<p>The Music Box, Dreams of Yokuda returns to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from April 18 to April 22, 2024, at 10AM EDT.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Houses</h2> 
<p><b>Willowpond Haven</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/293327844e785efa8da78d6581097f23.jpg" />
<p><i>Twinkling candleflies and languorous willow trees set a cozy scene for this retreat nestled near a peaceful pond. Waterfalls and scenic views complete this serene living nook on the edge of Blackwood.</i></p> 
<p>The new Willowpond Haven will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from April 3, at 1PM EDT to April 18, 2024, at 10AM EDT. Furnished and unfurnished versions will be available.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Princely Dawnlight Palace</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/540d3894f5f200806ebb68036e33213f.jpg" />
<p><i>Prince Hubalajad, in one of his wilder flights of extravagance, had a second palace built solely to better catch the light of the morning sun. It's a magnificent estate that truly makes one feel like a monarch.</i></p> 
<p>Princely Dawnlight Palace returns to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from April 18 to May 2, 2024, at 10AM EDT. Furnished and unfurnished versions will be available.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Houseguests</h2> 
<p><b>Crafty Lerisa</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/57791395bab62e77d53c60b4bdd4e7e0.jpg" />
<p><i>As her name implies, Crafty Lerisa possesses a cunning that keeps her alive. Right now it's telling her to sit tight—perhaps in your home? After adding Crafty Lerisa to your home, you can set her on a path, plus you and your visitors can speak with her.</i></p> 
<p>Crafty Lerisa will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from April 18 to April 22, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Mounts</h2> 
<p><b>Novelty Stick Horse</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/3d93a12ae84ee5695a5c6818894b9d0d.jpg" />
<p><i>During the Jester's Festival even the lowliest of commoners can pretend to be a mounted knight with a whimsical Novelty Stick steed. Horses are popular in the Daggerfall Covenant.</i></p> 
<p>The Novelty Stick Horse mount returns to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from April 1 to April 4, 2024, at 10AM EDT.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Ashen Fang Lair Courser</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/928bec3a4947cfbd8ba5191e9951a5ea.jpg" />
<p><i>Sometimes, when necromancers reanimate a creature, they overdo it and imbue the undead entity with an excess of dark conjuration. In the case of the Ashen Courser, this residue of mystical power manifests as a cloud of grave dust and ash.</i></p> 
<p>The Ashen Fang Lair Courser mount returns to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from April 3, at 1PM EDT to April 11, 2024, at 10AM EDT.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Evergloam Indrik</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/59e435fa620b43fa205de7b2aa6de6da.jpg" />
<p><i>Woven carefully from shadow wisps of Nocturnal's realm, these noble indriks shy from the light of day until trained by a patient rider to tolerate it. Forever after, they move under Magnus's fierce glow as if to defy it.</i></p> 
<p>The Evergloam Indrik mount will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from April 8 to April 15, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Atmoran Snow Ursauk</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/6942fa0fb587c9b2de2b16568ff3aed7.jpg" />
<p><i>Though fearsome in appearance, these ursauks make staunch companions when properly socialized. Their thick fur and hardy constitutions allow them to thrive even in the harshest environments, especially those in the northern reaches of Tamriel.</i></p> 
<p>The new Atmoran Snow Ursauk will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from April 18 to April 22, 2024, at 10AM EDT.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Emote</h2> 
<p><b>Pop the Cork</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/a02854a16cdda193f9fb3fabb88d4682.jpg" />
<p><i>It's time to celebrate! Pop open that sparkling cider and enjoy the moment.</i></p> 
<p>The Pop the Cork emote returns to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from April 1 to April 4, 2024, at 10AM EDT.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Pets</h2> 
<p><b>Pebble Pal</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/4e3a8a12b0c5223f5eb6937eb092c2dc.jpg" />
<p><i>Tired of pets that follow you everywhere? Fed up with feeding them? Step up to Pebble Pal, the pet that's a … rock.</i></p> 
<p>The Pebble Pal pet will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from April 1 to April 4, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Catwell</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/55d3210b04a0b97096a22940f67cf94a.jpg" />
<p><i>The cat's eyes seem to speak, saying, "Jolly good to see you! We appear to have a small blight of rodents. Dreadful crawling things. Scuttling everywhere. Hmm, skittering blights. I knew a good joke about that. What? Oh, yes. Lovely day for a hunt!"</i></p> 
<p>The Catwell pet will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from April 1 to April 4, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Spotted Snow Senche-Leopard</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/839c1612e48d8a45da02fe9920c3d9c0.jpg" />
<p><i>Even for the elusive senche-leopard, the Spotted Snow is a rare variety. Despite its frosty-looking fur, this adorable companion makes for a great cuddle buddy during long winter nights.</i></p> 
<p>The Spotted Snow Senche-Leopard pet will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from April 11 to April 15, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Fledgling Terror Bird</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/26af633c8f698fa44535276f2a40f542.jpg" />
<p><i>Taming even a young terror bird requires patience, full-coverage armor, and even more patience. The result, however, can put pause to any seeking to cast you in the role of victim. Plus these fledglings cuddle so nicely while making cute sleeping noises!</i></p> 
<p>The Fledgling Terror Bird pet returns to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from April 22 to April 25, 2024, at 10AM EDT.</p><p><br></p> 
<p>Whether you've been playing <i>ESO</i> since the beginning or are arriving just in time to celebrate its 10<sup>th</sup> Anniversary, there's sure to be something for you in the Crown Store this month. Don't forget, if you wish to acquire any of the above items, you will need to stock up on crowns via the <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/crowns">Buy Crowns page</a> first. Do you have your eye on any of April's new or returning items? Let us know via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline" target="_blank">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>. </p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Crown Store</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/7bc8c621513901a19927b46903d5fc91.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Daily Login Rewards—April 2024]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65769</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65769</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Preview some of the in-game items and collectibles you can unlock simply by logging in to ESO this April 2024!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/ce8c1c64521f0aefabd98528354b365d.jpg" /><p><i>Preview some of the in-game items and collectibles you can unlock simply by logging in to ESO this April 2024!</i></p> 
<p><i>ESO</i>'s 10<sup>th</sup> Anniversary Celebration is just about to kick off, and we've got a plethora of amazing rewards you can unlock during its first month (in addition to a <i>sneaky</i> new promotion we're not quite ready to reveal yet). Check out some of the in-game goodies you can claim this April 2024 below and learn more about Daily Login Rewards in <a href="https://help.elderscrollsonline.com/#en/answer/41950">this help article</a>.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Seals of Endeavors—Days 1, 6, 8, 13, 15, and 20 (phew)! </b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/10/cbf054f9fa4122ee9be26996607da8d2.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Seal the deal!</i></p> 
<p>Once again, we've added a bounty of Seals to this month's rewards, helping you get your hands on specific Crown Crate items. April's offerings total 450 Seals, making this another big month, but you'll need to log in multiple days (and at least 20 days in total) to claim them all. Learn more about Seals of Endeavor <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/59925">in this blog</a>.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Dibella's Sweetroll Stack Memento—Day 7</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/58dd0a3ca35cdfc73347500bd64981a1.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Indulge your sweet tooth</i></p> 
<p>What's better than a single sweetroll? A whole stack of them! This tasty memento, which summons a veritable stack of snacks, ensures you can always sweeten the deal.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Ayrenn's Fledgling Gryphon Pet—Day 14</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/728afd0fd6ae05a1d0e8c91b5d8525b8.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Adorably regal!</i></p> 
<p>Talking about sweeties, Ayrenn's Fledgling Gryphon pet is equal parts cute and fierce and is ready to join you in your adventures in Tamriel.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Cumberland Anniversary Attire—Day 21</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/b896db0f95aba09ea92b02703cafd2ef.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Dress to impress (everybody)</i></p> 
<p>Step out and celebrate <i>ESO</i>'s upcoming birthday in style with the Cumberland Anniversary Attire costume. This elegant ensemble is sure to help you turn heads and stand out in a crowd. We'll see you on the ballroom floor! </p> 
<p>These items, of course, are just a taste of what you can claim while logging into <i>ESO</i> this month. To see the full list, hop into Tamriel starting April 1! Keep an eye out for a unique in-game promotion kicking off later this month as well—those of you who live outside the law might enjoy what is to come! </p> 
<p>Are you excited to kick off <i>ESO</i>'s 10<sup>th</sup> Anniversary Celebration in style with these in-game rewards? Let us know via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Daily Rewards</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/ce8c1c64521f0aefabd98528354b365d.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Crown Store Gifting Update – October 2023]]></title>
            <link>https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/644559/crown-store-gifting-update-october-2023</link>
            <guid>https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/644559/crown-store-gifting-update-october-2023</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 20:22:11 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[Following up on Studio Director Matt Firor's message last month about the <a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/643289/update-on-current-and-future-status-of-gifting">current and future status of Crown Store Gifting</a>, we are moving forward with re-enabling this functionality for eligible players at the account level. In this post, we will detail what to expect.<br><br>
In September, we temporarily disabled Crown Store gifting due to a rapidly growing issue of "bad actors" using various fraudulent means to amass crowns without paying for them, then using them in turn to sell Crown Store items to players for real-world cash outside of the game client. That said, we recognize that gifting is a meaningful part of our community, and we are in the process of manually re-enabling Crown Store gifting access for select players who meet our specific criteria. This work will be complete tomorrow, October 11, during the maintenance window from 09:00 AM ET to 12:00 PM ET.<br><br>
Gifting eligibility is determined by an evolving list of factors including but not limited to the account being at least 180 days past its first login and previous engagement with in-game features. You may check if you have access to gifting in-game via the Crown Store as well as via <a href="https://account.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/account/billing/billing-history">your billing history page</a> in the ESO account center. If you have access to Crown Store gifting, you will see "Allow Crown Store Gifting" in your billing history. If you try to send a gift via the in-game Crown Store and do not have access, you will see a "Gifting Locked" pop-up message. Please note that we are exploring better ways to display this information in-game in the future, such as updating the Gifting Tutorial.<br><br>
If you do not have access to Crown Store gifting after it is re-enabled on October 11, 2023, and wish for a review of your account, please visit <a href="https://help.elderscrollsonline.com">https://help.elderscrollsonline.com</a> and submit a Customer Support ticket. Please choose the Billing / Purchase / Code category then Platform &gt; I have a question about a sale / offer &gt; I want to send gift items from this account.<br><br>
We appreciate everyone's understanding and patience while we get this solution up and running. Multiple teams have worked long hours to evaluate the best technical solutions that we could stand up in a reasonably short time, while also prioritizing the Crown Store gifting player experience. We are dedicated to continuing to explore ways to make this better and reduce fraudulent activity in ESO. Thanks again for being a part of our community and for your continued support.]]></content:encoded>
            <category>Forum</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[New Patcher Rollout]]></title>
            <link>https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/642066/new-patcher-rollout</link>
            <guid>https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/642066/new-patcher-rollout</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 20:49:19 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[Hello everyone! After plenty of testing <a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en-gb/discussion/632782/new-eso-launcher-testing-and-launch-plan-pc-and-mac">during the last PTS period</a>, we are pleased to announce the rollout of our new patcher on the live servers for PC/Mac. The rollout of the new patcher will happen in four phases, with new countries being added during each phase. As we give countries access to the new patcher, we will make note of it in the list below by noting next to the country name (has the new patcher.) We will also note what phase we are currently in by specifying whether it has not started, in progress, or complete, next to the phase number. The countries getting the patcher are listed in order below.<br><br>
Thanks for your patience as we roll this out to all countries listed below. A special thanks to everyone who helped test out the launcher during the last PTS and provided feedback.<br><br>
Edit for 3/4/2024: All phases have now been complete.<br><br><b>Phase 1 (Complete) </b>
<ol><li>Netherlands (Has the new patcher)</li>
<li>Sweden (Has the new patcher)</li>
<li>Czech Republic/ Finland (Has the new patcher)</li>
<li>Norway/ Denmark (Has the new patcher)</li>
<li>Hungary/ Switzerland/ Romania (Has the new patcher)</li>
</ol><br><b>Phase 2 (Complete) </b>
<ol><li>Poland (Has the new patcher)</li>
<li>Spain/ Turkey (Has the new patcher)</li>
<li>Italy/ Austria/ Belgium/ Portugal/ Greece/ Ireland (Has the new patcher)</li>
</ol><br><b>Phase 3 (Complete) </b>
<ol><li>United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland/ France (Has the new patcher)</li>
<li>Germany (Has the new patcher)</li>
<li>United States of America (Has the new patcher)</li>
</ol><br><b>Phase 4 (Complete) </b><br>
This phase will encompass all other countries where ESO is available, that are not listed above. (All countries where ESO is available now have access to the launcher.)<br><br><b>Known Issues</b>
<ul><li>Some Czech Republic players may not have their country recognized, thus making them unable to upgrade the patch at this time. We are aware of the issue and working toward a solution.</li>
<li>Audio issues with sound volume and sound effects. We have a bug in for this and are working on a fix for the future.</li>
</ul>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>Forum</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>