<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>ESO Announcements</title>
        <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/</link>
        <description>Combined ESO blog and forum post announcements feed</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>Magic</generator>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Endless Archive & Update 40 Now Live on All Platforms]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/64849</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/64849</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Discover the Update 40 base-game patch, featuring the unending battle of the Endless Archive and more, now live on all platforms!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/10/93b563f90ddef66e9abade33ebe4014a.jpg" /><p><i>Discover the Update 40 base-game patch, featuring the unending battle of the Endless Archive and more, now live on all platforms! </i><br></p> <p><i>The Elder Scrolls Online: Endless Archive</i> and Update 40 are now live on PC/Mac, Xbox One, Xbox Series X|S, PlayStation 4, and PlayStation 5.<br></p> <p>This base-game patch introduces an all-new PvE activity for Tamriel's adventurers and a host of new features and quality-of-life improvements—completely free for all <i>ESO </i>players! This update also fully localizes the game for Japanese players on Xbox and PlayStation consoles. This includes localization for the base game, all previous DLCs and Chapters, <i>The Elder Scrolls Online: Necrom</i>, and this most recent patch. </p>
<a href="https://youtube.com/v/aypqJhUi0eM?autoplay=1&rel=0"><img src="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/aypqJhUi0eM/maxresdefault.jpg" /></a>
<h2>Endless Archive</h2> 
<p>In the Endless Archive, you can discover an unending challenge as you battle your way through the shifting libraries and twisting pathways of one of Hermaeus Mora's most mysterious strongholds.</p> 
<p>A malignant force is causing chaos within the once solemn archive, and its custodian, Master Malkhest, needs brave explorers to investigate and fight back against the corruption. </p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/10/4f5eb2f67d03541aa8697d37debdc896.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Battle through the Archive</i></p> 
<p><b>Unending Challenge</b></p> 
<p>In this all-new PvE activity, you can team up with a trusted ally or go it solo as you contend with randomly generated stages filled with waves of monsters and perilous boss encounters. </p> 
<p>The further you progress into this eternal arena, the more dangerous and numerous your foes become. Fall to the Archive's dangers three times, and your run ends, plus you have to start over. But don't let that phase you, as there's always another expedition into the Endless Archive waiting, and the greater the dangers, the greater the rewards are in turn! </p>
<img src="https://esossl-a.akamaihd.net/uploads/Community/Article/Achievement_ELAR_ThoatReplicanum_GlassMantikoraCombat%20%201%20.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Survive twisted maligraphies</i></p> 
<p>Helping you survive these encounters are two types of boons you can choose along the way: Verses (temporary buffs that last until the end of the next Stage), and Visions (more permanent buffs that last your entire run). The Verses and Visions you choose can have a major impact on your run, so choose wisely! </p> 
<p><b>Infinite Rewards</b></p> 
<p>As you continue your expedition into the Endless Archive, you can discover and unlock a host of specials rewards, including unique collectibles, item sets, and more—all granted by the Prince of Knowledge himself! </p> 
<p>These rewards include class set items, the first of their kind, which provide powerful boons to select Class Skill Lines. </p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/5e802a1ba276c8d61c4afe1758e10e1a.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Empower class skills with new item sets</i></p> 
<p>However, that's not all. As you complete expeditions, you also earn a new currency called Archival Fortunes. With Archival Fortunes, you can purchase all manner of helpful items from the vendors within the Endless Archive's central hub. This includes one-time use buffs, individual item set items, fragments of collectibles, and even permanent account unlocks that provide boons for future runs! </p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/10/8e6903a91a99738393994927036ff658.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Endless Archive collectible rewards</i></p> 
<p>Finally, the Endless Archive also features a host of unique in-game collectibles that you can't earn anywhere else in Tamriel or Oblivion, including the Maligraphic Mount, Maligraphic Skeever pet, a unique Tales of Tribute deck, and much more. Check out <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/64891">our preview</a> for more information on the Endless Archive's rewards.</p> 
<h2>Getting Started</h2> 
<p>The Endless Archive is a <b>free</b> base-game addition to <i>The Elder Scrolls Online</i> and is part of the Update 40 patch. There is no additional purchase necessary, although ESO Plus members will enjoy a bonus to Archival Fortune gains during their expeditions. </p> 
<p>You can access the Endless Archive via two methods:</p> 
<ul><li>If you own the Necrom Chapter, you can find the entrance to the Endless Archive northeast of Cipher's Midden in Apocrypha.</li><li>If you don't own the Chapter, select the Endless Archive icon on your map of Apocrypha to teleport directly there.</li></ul>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/10/8900c6e9c570f3ec8db144c6e6fce32c.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center"><i>Prepare for adventure</i></p> <p>Brave adventurers may wish to dive right in to the archive's myriad mazelike passages, but you may wish to review these <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/64837;">developer tips</a> before you begin your expedition. Preparation is key—good luck!</p> <h2>Update 40 </h2> <p>In addition to the new PvE activity, Update 40 also includes a host of new features and quality-of-life improvements that all of Tamriel's adventurers can enjoy.</p><p><b>Japanese Console Text Localization</b></p><p> </p><p>Update 40 is fully localized for Japanese players on both Xbox and PlayStation consoles. These new translations have been added for both past and all future releases, including the base game, previous DLCs and Chapters, and the most-recent <i>Necrom</i> Chapter. To enable Japanese localization for your console, download the Update 40 patch and check your console's language settings. </p><p> </p> <p><b>Group Finder</b></p> <p>The new Group Finder tool makes it easier than ever to find likeminded players to join you for practically any in-game activity, including typical group challenges such as Trials or Dungeon runs, but also more social activities such as zone explorations, roleplay sessions, or fashion contests! </p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/10/0f2f8e781eacee9f7a7a165c6b2e4019.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Group Finder UI</i></p> 
<p>There are a host of categories you can choose from when finding a group, but the Custom category allows you to create or find fellow players for any unique activity you can dream up! </p> 
<p>In addition, the Group Finder allows you to set up requirements for your groups, including roles, CP levels, voice chat, and many more. </p> 
<p><b>Grand Master Crafting Stations</b></p> 
<p>Update 40 also introduces a new type of end-game furnishing for Tamriel's master crafters: Grand Master Crafting Stations. These special items allow you to consolidate your home's (likely many) attuned crafting stations into one, severely reducing the amount of housing slots your crafting stations take up AND freeing up space in general. The more attuned crafting stations you “feed” to your Grand Master station, the more visually distinct that specific furnishing will appear as it evolves over time. </p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/10/ed2a0be2d781a7eb96a51f70e780978c.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center"><i>Grand Master Crafting Stations</i></p> <p>You can acquire Grand Master Crafting Stations using Writ Vouchers from the Achievement Mediator, Faustina Curio, with a unique furnishing available for each of Blacksmithing, Jewelry Crafting, Clothing, and Woodworking. </p> <p>You can dive deeper into both the Group Finder and Grand Master Crafting Stations in <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/64897">this preview blog</a>. </p> <p><b>Jewelry Crafting Rebalance</b></p> <p>This patch also establishes a broad rebalancing of Jewelry Crafting to help align its costs with the game's other crafting disciplines. This includes the removal of Jewelry Crafting grains and conversion into platings in addition to increasing the total boosters needed to upgrade your jewelry. As a result, upgrading rings and amulets is now easier and cheaper than ever before.</p> <p><b>Quest XP &amp; Gold Standardization</b></p> <p>Finally, Update 40 also standardizes the Experience Point and Gold rewards for many of the game's quests, including those associated with zones, main storylines, prologues, dailies, guild storylines, and more. This will result in more consistent rewards for the game's various quests based on their complexity or length. </p> <p>Of course, these are just some of the changes implemented with the base-game patch. Be sure to visit our <a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/categories/patch-notes">Patch Notes forum</a> to review everything coming with this massive update. </p> <h2>Endless Challenges</h2> <p>In the Update 40 base-game patch, you can discover an all-new challenge for you and your fiercest allies as you delve ever-deeper into the dynamic galleries of a corrupted library. How far will your expedition into the Endless Archive get? The only limits are your preparation and skills! Tell us if you'll be venturing into the free Endless Archive PvE activity via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, or <a href="https://www.facebook.com/ElderScrollsOnline;">Facebook</a>—good luck!</p> <p><i>The Update 40 base-game patch and Endless Archive are now live on PC/Mac, Xbox One, Xbox Series X|S, PlayStation 4, and PlayStation 5.</i><br></p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Endless Archive</category>
            <category>Update 40</category>
            <category>Shadow Over Morrowind</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/10/93b563f90ddef66e9abade33ebe4014a.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Defend Tamriel from Destruction during the Gates of Oblivion Celebration Event]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65005</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65005</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Defeat the agents of Mehrunes Dagon and earn bonus rewards during this new in-game event!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/11/06f512f6c40b4e0859d8d5b805c8ead1.jpg" /><p><i>Defeat the agents of Mehrunes Dagon and earn bonus rewards during this new in-game event!</i></p> 
<p></p><h2>Unravel Dagon's Schemes</h2>
<p></p><p> The Gates of Oblivion Celebration begins Thursday, November 16 at 10AM EST, and runs until Tuesday, November 28 at 10AM EST. During the festivities, players will enjoy an assortment of goodies including special Reward Boxes, Event Tickets, and increased drops to Daily Quests, Dungeons, Resource Nodes, as well as World Bosses and Delves throughout the Blackwood and the Deadlands zones. </p> 
<p>To participate, you'll need access to <i>Blackwood, Flames of Ambition</i>, <i>Waking Flame</i>, or <i>Deadlands</i>, all of which are obtainable through <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/esoplus">ESO Plus™</a> or available for purchase from the in-game Crown Store. </p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/11/a87df9628c7f71a7f102fcbf2ec0c30b.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Find Plokun in Gideon to begin! </i></p> 
<p>You can then kick things off by picking up the introductory quest “Burdensome Beasts,” available for free within the in-game Crown Store or from Plokun, a Dremora found northwest of Gideon in the Blackwood zone.</p> 
<h2>Amass Incredible Rewards</h2> 
<p>Throughout the event, you can earn a Glorious Reward Box once per day each time you complete your first Daily Quest in either the Blackwood or Deadlands zones, or from the first Rockgrove Weekly Quest completed. You can also obtain a second Glorious Reward Box once per day by looting the final boss of any <i>Flames of Ambition</i> and <i>Waking Flame</i> dungeons.</p> 
<p>Glorious Reward Boxes may contain the following items:</p> 
<ul><li>Random crafting materials </li><li>A Fine or Superior rarity sellable treasure </li><li>One of the following <i>Blackwood</i>/<i>Deadlands</i> motif style items: </li><ul><li>If the reward box was obtained in the Overland:</li><ul><li>Sul-Xan</li><li>Black Fin</li><li>Ivory Brigade</li><li>House Hexos</li><li>Fargrave Guardian</li><li>Annihilarch's Chosen</li></ul><li>If the reward box was obtained in a Dungeon:</li><ul><li>True-Sworn</li><li>Waking Flame</li><li>Knights of the Silver Rose</li><li>Crimson Oath</li></ul></ul><li>A Fine, Superior, or Epic rarity <i>Blackwood</i> or <i>Deadlands</i> overland set item</li><ul><li>A Dungeon set item will be given instead if you obtained the Reward Box in a Dungeon </li></ul><li>Companion Gear </li><li>One of the following drops </li><ul><li><i>Blackwood</i> or <i>Deadlands</i> furnishing recipes</li><li><i>Blackwood</i> or <i>Deadlands</i> Treasure Maps or Survey Reports</li><li>Motif Chapters</li><ul><li>If the reward box was obtained in the Overland:</li><ul><li>Sul-Xan</li><li>Black Fin</li><li>Ivory Brigade</li><li>House Hexos</li><li>Fargrave Guardian</li><li>Annihilarch's Chosen</li></ul><li>If the reward box was obtained in a Dungeon:</li><ul><li>True-Sworn</li><li>Waking Flame</li><li>Knights of the Silver Rose</li><li>Crimson Oath</li></ul></ul></ul><li>A chance for a style page for the <b>NEW</b> Y'ffre's Fallen-Wood armor</li></ul>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/11/923c2f3e8161930db03f5b02a347a50a.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>The new Y'ffre's Fallen-Wood armor style</i></p> 
<p>In addition, you can collect the more common Regular Reward Boxes by participating in the following activities:</p> 
<ul><li>Slaying Delve and World Bosses in the Blackwood and Deadland zones</li><li>Defeating <i>Flames of Ambition</i> and <i>Waking Flame</i> dungeon bosses</li><li>Opening treasure chests</li><li>Opening safeboxes</li><li>Looting objects such as barrels, crates, etc.</li><li>Looting Psijic portals</li><li>Cracking open Thieves Troves</li><li>Harvesting crafting resource nodes</li></ul> 
<p>These reward boxes may contain the following items:</p> 
<ul><li>Random crafting materials </li><li>A chance for a Fine or Superior rarity sellable treasure </li><li>A chance for one of the following <i>Blackwood</i>/<i>Deadlands</i> motif style items: </li><ul><li>Sul-Xan</li><li>Black Fin</li><li>Ivory Brigade</li><li>House Hexos</li><li>Fargrave Guardian</li><li>Annihilarch's Chosen</li></ul><li>A Fine, Superior, or Epic rarity <i>Blackwood</i> or <i>Deadlands</i> Overland set item </li><ul><li>A Dungeon set item will be given instead if you obtained the reward box in a Dungeon </li></ul><li>A chance for Companion gear </li><li>A chance for one of the following drops </li><ul><li><i>Blackwood</i> or <i>Deadlands</i> furnishing recipes</li><li><i>Blackwood</i> or <i>Deadlands</i> Treasure Maps or Survey Reports</li><li>Motif Chapters</li><ul><li>Sul-Xan</li><li>Black Fin</li><li>Ivory Brigade</li><li>House Hexos</li><li>Fargrave Guardian</li><li>Annihilarch's Chosen</li></ul></ul><li>A small chance for a style page for the <b>NEW</b> Y'ffre's Fallen-Wood armor</li></ul>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/11/9d3803c2d3fec59ceac547ef9e603a24.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Complete daily quests to earn bonus rewards</i></p> 
<h2>Impresario &amp; Event Tickets</h2> 
<p>But that's not all! Throughout the duration of the celebration, players will receive two Event Tickets for the first of the following activities completed each day:</p> 
<ul><li>First Daily Quest completed in the Blackwood zone</li><li>First Daily Quest completed in the Deadlands zone</li><li>Weekly trial quest completed in Rockgrove</li><li>Slaying and looting the final boss in either <i>Flames of Ambition</i> or <i>Waking Flame</i> dungeons</li></ul> 
<p>In total, you can amass a whopping 26 Event Tickets during this event! Don't forget that you can carry only 12 Tickets at one time. </p> 
<p>Here's what the Impresario has in stock:</p> 
<ul><li>All three Passion Dancer Blossom pet fragments </li><ul><li>Chartreuse Lily Petals</li><li>Enchanted Silver Flute</li><li>Mystical Sheet Music</li></ul><li>The first and second Hoardhunter Ursauk mount fragment </li><ul><li>Blessed Honeycomb</li><li><b>NEW</b> Gilded and Dyed Saddle</li></ul><li>Bound style pages for the following:</li><ul><li><b>NEW</b> Y'ffre's Fallen-Wood</li></ul><li>Impresario Group Repair Kits</li><li>Companion Guild Commendations</li></ul> 
<p>The Gates of Oblivion Celebration is your first chance to purchase the Gilded and Dyed Saddle, the second of three morphing fragments for the Hoardhunter Ursauk mount! </p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/11/b3a53d6fcf9e1741482c56e2734daf3f.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>The Hoardhunter Ursauk mount</i></p> 
<p>Learn more about morphing collectibles and upgrade fragments by checking out this <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/guides/eventtickets">guide</a>. Be sure to keep your eyes peeled for the reveal of the final morphing fragment later this year!</p> 
<p>Additionally, the Impresario's Assistant, Philius Dormier, is offering these valuable treasures in exchange for your hard-earned tickets:</p> 
<ul><li>Unstable Morpholith Fragments</li><li>Dagonic Quasigriff Fragments</li></ul> 
<p>Finally, Nenulaure the Indrik Vendor is stocking her shop with the following goodies:</p> 
<ul><li>Nascent Indrik Feathers</li><li>Crimson Indrik Berries</li><li>Pure-Snow Indrik Berries</li><li>Frost-Light Indrik Pet</li><li>Rosethorn Indrik Pet</li></ul> 
<h2>Ward Off Destruction</h2> 
<p>Dismantle Daedric schemes while enjoying an assortment of tantalizing rewards and useful bonuses as you explore Blackwood and the Deadlands during the Gates of Oblivion Celebration. Are you prepared to free these lands from the corrupting influence of Mehrunes Dagon? Let us know via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (Formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, or <a href="https://www.facebook.com/ElderScrollsOnline">Facebook</a>!</p> 
<p><i>The Gates of Oblivion Celebration in-game event begins next Thursday, November 16 at 10AM EST, and continues until Tuesday, November 28 at 10AM EST.</i> </p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Events</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/11/06f512f6c40b4e0859d8d5b805c8ead1.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Share your tips for the Endless Archive for our console friends!]]></title>
            <link>https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/646715/share-your-tips-for-the-endless-archive-for-our-console-friends</link>
            <guid>https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/646715/share-your-tips-for-the-endless-archive-for-our-console-friends</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 19:25:23 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[Hi all! Our friends on console will be able to dive into the Endless Archive for the first time starting next Tuesday! With console launch quickly approaching, share some of your tips, tricks, or experience to help set new players for Endless Archive success! We also have some<a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/64999"> community guides available here</a> for everyone to reference.]]></content:encoded>
            <category>Forum</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Crown Store Showcase—November 2023]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/64957</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/64957</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Traverse the Endless Archive in style with November's new and exciting Crown Store offerings.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/10/473ae27aaf95a2ea078e54ecb72bdd86.jpg" /><p><i>Traverse the Endless Archive in style with November's new and exciting Crown Store offerings.</i></p> 
<p>You can review all the new and returning items arriving to the Crown Store in November 2023 below. Remember: you can see absolutely everything available in the Crown Store right now by heading over to the <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/crownstore">Crown Store page</a>. Additionally, be sure to stop by the <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/buycrowns">Buy Crowns page</a> to pick up whatever number of crowns you may need! Certain items and offers will be time-limited throughout the month, so be sure to read their individual details and don't miss out.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<h2>ESO Plus Deals</h2> 
<p>All ESO Plus™ members have access to a monthly selection of exclusive deals and items. You can find more information about them in <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/54825">this article</a>.</p> 
<p><b>Exclusive Free Items</b></p> 
<p><b>Painting: Sanity's Edge</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/10/5216beb3df74ce7e85eddda4e262da17.jpg" />
<p><i>"As you can see by my attached references, I am one of the foremost experts in vicinage wards, forfending spells, and the art of research. If anyone can deal with the Dreamstone's ire, it is me. I hope you come to the same conclusion."—Warlock Vanton</i></p> 
<p>The Painting: Sanity's Edge will be available in the Crown Store FREE exclusively to ESO Plus Members on all platforms for a limited time, from October 12 at 10AM EDT to November 22, 2023, at 10AM EST.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Painting: The Endless Library</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/10/32bc67b4096e7ec4126a630b7ba31203.jpg" />
<p><i>A painting depicting just one of the innumerable studies within the Endless Library of Hermaeus Mora.</i></p> <p>The Painting: The Endless Library will be available in the Crown Store FREE exclusively to ESO Plus Members on all platforms for a limited time, from November 22, 2023, to January 4, 2024, at 10AM EST.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> <h2>Crown Gem and Seals of Endeavor Items</h2> <p><b>Mounts</b></p> <p><b>Dragonscale Draugr Bear</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/10/72871f88e2eb7511a2222010431d0a22.jpg" />
<p><i>Riders of these draugr bears find the dragonscale barding does an exemplary job. There's exactly as much jouncing as you'd expect riding hard on a skeletal ursine's back. Plus, the frost magic imbued within adds a frisson of chill to keep riders alert.</i></p> 
<p>The Dragonscale Draugr Bear will be available for Crown Gems and Seals of Endeavor on all platforms for a limited time, from November 9 to November 16, 2023, at 10AM EST.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<h2>Adornments</h2> 
<p><b>Hair</b></p> 
<p><b>Short Mussed Wave</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/10/514b2eb6f5fb02406a871a9d461af261.jpg" />
<p><i>With a head of hair this awesome, who needs braids, beads, or wraps? Those curls are strictly au naturel.</i></p> 
<p>The Short Mussed Wave will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from November 20 to November 27, 2023, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Hat</b></p> 
<p><b>Xanmeer Doyen's Feather Tiara</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/10/42cd5d42cae6d1f5fb57bd309ba83771.jpg" />
<p><i>This gorgeous tiara is replicated from the intricate regalia of the Xanmeer Priesthoods. Wow the crowd and stand out with this beautiful plumage waving above your brow.</i></p> 
<p>The Xanmeer Doyen's Feather Tiara will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from November 20 to November 27, 2023, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Skins</h2> 
<p><b>Azure Imp Epidermis</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/10/65877405511b80a407cfb71b6110ac5c.jpg" />
<p><i>"Some, shall we say, ambitious sorts came up with a way to look a bit like those azure imps you sometimes see flitting about. No, you don't gain wings, but you'll very likely frighten most people out of their wits regardless."—Divayth Fyr</i></p> 
<p>The Azure Imp Epidermis will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from November 2, 2023, at 10AM EDT to November 9, 2023, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Crafting</h2> 
<p><b>Motifs</b></p> 
<p><b>Crown Crafting Motif: Sea Giant</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2021/11/4de5ddeaf89aa0901a71bf5bd8e75546.jpg" />
<p><i>Though not much is known of the Sea Giants, as Varcent Eardrey writes, their distinctive armor lends itself well to the fierce foes they hunt. Use to learn the Sea Giant crafting style. Also has a chance to drop by completing "The Fight For Kyne's Aegis" quest.</i></p> 
<p>The Crown Crafting Motif: Sea Giant will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms starting November 13 to November 20, 2023, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item. Sea Giant Motif chapters, and very rarely the complete book, have a chance to drop from Kyne's Coffers, awarded from Thane Ogvar in the Kyne's Aegis trial from completing the weekly quest “The Fight for Kyne's Aegis”.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Outfit Styles</b></p> 
<p><b>Elder Scrolls Artifact: Fearstruck</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/10/aec9c604dcaac94bccaf4fae79bc72c7.jpg" />
<p><i>Alter your shield's Outfit style with a replica of the Fearstruck Elder Scrolls Artifact, a shield crafted by the Daedric Prince Boethiah.</i></p> 
<p>The Elder Scrolls Artifact: Fearstruck will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms starting November 2, 2023, at 10AM EDT to November 6, 2023, at 10PM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Maarselok Arms Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/10/d9423e7097d91a47119c455ac20a6c6e.jpg" />
<p><i> Summon your most stalwart companions to face the Dragon Maarselok in his lair and prevent him from corrupting the Changeling Selene. Then, perhaps, celebrate your victory by altering your weapon's appearance to match the Undaunted Maarselok awards by using this complete set of Outfit styles.</i></p> 
<p>The Maarselok Arms Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms starting November 2, 2023, at 10AM EDT to November 9, 2023, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item. The matching mask page will have a small chance to drop from Maarselok from veteran Lair of Maarselok. The matching shoulder page can be purchased from Urgarlag Chief-bane for 50 undaunted keys, or has a chance of dropping from Urgarlag's Mystery Coffer for 1 key. Having the achievement “Selene's Favor” increases the drop chance of both items.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Anvil of Zenithar Arms Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/10/88ff79e07bf008fee0b9dd8624ef1677.jpg" />
<p><i>The Divine known as Zenithar may not have crafted these glowing weapons himself, but those who did claim the God of Work and Commerce inspired their work! Alter your weapon's appearance by using this complete set of Anvil of Zenithar Outfit styles.</i></p> 
<p>The Anvil of Zenithar Arms Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms starting November 9 to November 22, 2023, at 10AM EST.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Elder Scrolls Artifact: Mehrunes' Razor</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/10/4a9e63f27a9440fcde2faf90892b6b3b.jpg" />
<p><i>Alter your one-handed dagger's Outfit style with a replica of the Mehrunes' Razor Elder Scrolls Artifact, the signature weapon of Daedric Prince Mehrunes Dagon.</i></p> 
<p>The Elder Scrolls Artifact: Mehrunes' Razor will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms starting November 16 to November 22, 2023, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Prior Thierric Arms Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/10/c0661a8cfbf376bb17ff84a13c7d7324.jpg" />
<p><i>Prior Thierrec Sarazen, the knight-commander of the Knights of the Silver Rose, awaits those who brave Red Petal Bastion. Dare you and your fellow Undaunted adventurers face him? Alter your weapon's appearance to match the Undaunted Prior Thierric awards by using this complete set of Outfit styles.</i></p> 
<p>The Prior Thierric Arms Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms starting November 22 to November 30, 2023, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item. The matching mask page will have a small chance to drop from Prior Thierric Sarazen from veteran Red Petal Bastion. The matching shoulder page can be purchased from Urgarlag Chief-bane for 50 Undaunted keys, or has a chance of dropping from Urgarlag's Mystery Coffer for 1 key. Having the achievement “Prior Offenses” increases the drop chance of both items.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Wardrobe</h2> 
<p><b>Costumes</b></p> 
<p><b>Pact Mother Elite Ensemble</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/10/9b44fb56d5db3c962cadb5a2c8d1dfa2.jpg" />
<p><i>"Today I don new robes, a symbol of my vow, my office. Blessed by Almalexia, may the Mother of Morrowind guide my hand. May she lend strength to me in times of conflict. For the Pact!"—Excerpt from Urona Hlaalu's Journal</i></p> 
<p>The Pact Mother Elite Ensemble will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from November 2, 2023, at 10AM EDT, to November 9, 2023, at 10AM EST.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Graht-Climber's Active Wear</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/10/aedf616498f1b9e7d7c840c194cc0024.jpg" />
<p><i>Stitchmaster Moneriel says, "We all have days when we have to climb the graht-oak to clean the house-pod gutters. Does that mean you have to dress like a frump? Of course not! Look trim and stylish in my latest halter-and-skirt outfit from Elden Root!"</i></p> 
<p>The Graht-Climber's Active Wear will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from November 6 to November 9, 2023, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Traveling Merchant</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/10/fc8d7c48bc407b1ce70f3b6245a540f4.jpg" />
<p><i>Merchants need to look presentable, and those who travel require protection from the elements. With this outfit, you can travel through Tamriel and beyond knowing that you have met both requirements!</i></p> 
<p>The Traveling Merchant costume will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from November 6 to November 9, 2023, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Solitude Stevedore's Jerkin</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/10/00c86425603f01b6b7f3cf026f394517.jpg" />
<p><i>"The Nord stevedores who work the docks below the great stone arch of Solitude have a style all their own," says Jork the Tailor-Thane of Windhelm. "They take what they like from travelers of Tamriel and make it their own. Now you can, too!"</i></p> 
<p>The Solitude Stevedore's Jerkin costume will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from November 9 to November 13, 2023, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Dark Shaman</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/10/b44093b43e5b4dafd420cddef8f8d0eb.jpg" />
<p><i>Far from town, temple, and market, those of ill intent meet in secret conclave to importune the forces of darkness for power and mastery. Behold here the dire raiment they don for this fell purpose.</i></p> 
<p>The Dark Shaman costume will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from November 16 to November 22, 2023, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Xanmeer Doyen's Worship Robe</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/10/979cf9a81743eb32b9d62ff1f6c45891.jpg" />
<p><i>"Corset of kagouti-leather, full skirt of dank-cotton, beaded-shell vambraces and bird-skull pauldrons: everything a Xanmeer Doyen needs when welcoming worshipers into the Arboreal Reverie. The Hermit's outdone itself this time," says Jaxa-Kel.</i></p> 
<p>The Xanmeer Doyen's Worship Robe will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from November 20 to November 27, 2023, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Armored Knights Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2022/07/e9ea60adf02c3a00325a727469a6b43d.jpg" />
<p><i>A costume pack that offers three variations of a fully armored battlefield knight.</i></p> 
<p>The Armored Knights Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from November 27 to November 30, 2023, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Crate</h2> 
<p><b>Dragonscale Crate</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/10/a683e0e9ef6e3f21f0ec9a912013593b.jpg" />
<p><i>A mystery collection of Dragonscale related items!</i></p> 
<p>Dragonscale Crate will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from November 9 to November 16, 2023, at 10AM EST.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Baandari Pedlar Crate</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/10/1e4f4af6b38e9c8cc00d452e0a03b3de.jpg" />
<p><i>A mystery collection of Baandari Pedlar items!</i></p> 
<p>Baandari Pedlar Crate will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from November 16 to November 22, 2023, at 10AM EST.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<h2>Events </h2> 
<p><b>Currency</b></p> 
<p><b>Event Tickets</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/74f679e610302be57199309573dd3a29.jpg" />
<p><i>A ticket used to purchase rare goods from The Impresario, Event Merchant. Curious as to what goods? Well, chat with her to see what she has to offer!</i></p> 
<p>Single Event Tickets will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time during the Gates of Oblivion Celebration. Stay tuned for event details!</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Grace of the Green Bundle</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/10/0106797c4767745433e455fce878eb1b.jpg" />
<p><i>As the forces of nature take root, so too do the blessings of Y'ffre. This bundle contains Y'ffre-Bound weapons, which are visibly graced by the God of Song and Forest. It also includes Drinweth, a Valenwood armorer who can advise you on martial matters.</i></p> 
<p>The Grace of the Green Bundle will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time during the Gates of Oblivion Celebration.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<h2>Furniture </h2> 
<p><b>Statue, Vampiric Sovereign</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/10/d41eea0cafcc9f931284723cf8a83b58.jpg" />
<p><i>The vile enchantments placed upon this statue make it a grim reminder of a vampire's power. Whether cloaked in bats, imbued with dark energies, or wreathed in flame, weak-hearted mortals will never forget the sight of it.</i></p> 
<p>The Statue, Vampiric Sovereign will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from November 9 to November 22, 2023, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Furnishing Pack: Mad Alchemist</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/10/48bd3c98247a14826add6709289c4d98.jpg" />
<p><i>At last, you can demonstrate your true genius! Enhance your laboratory with these tanks and specimens then experiment to your heart's content! And, because the simple-minded may fear your work, keep your combat arts well-honed on a sturdy Bloodknight.</i></p> 
<p>The Furnishing Pack: Mad Alchemist will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from November 9 to November 22, 2023, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Furnishing Pack: Daedric Ambitions</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/10/889589fecd6d602d57ac7eb42819317c.jpg" />
<p><i>Build your own imposing edifices with these structural pieces and accessories. Will your enemies—and maybe even friends—quail at the results of your labors? Yes, yes, they will.</i></p> 
<p>The Furnishing Pack: Daedric Ambitions will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from November 13 to November 20, 2023, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Statue, Prince of Ambition</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/10/56e5400149fa2bc1c4bbea420c344bb9.jpg" />
<p><i>Sweltering chaos accompanies this colossal statue of Mehrunes Dagon, the Prince of Destruction. Whether you prefer his smoldering heat, fiery gaze, blazing axe, or the full force of his inferno, this statue will bring sublime terror to any home.</i></p> 
<p>The Statue, Prince of Ambition will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from November 16 to November 22, 2023, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Furnishing Pack: Chapel of Zenithar</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/10/f177da4c6639743a7dd9bc076ef85a60.jpg" />
<p><i>Though Zenithar is known as the God of Work and Commerce, he also represents the peace and prosperity that comes with great effort. Now you can decorate your own place of worship to venerate this industrious Divine.</i></p> 
<p>The Furnishing Pack: Chapel of Zenithar will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from November 22 to December 7, 2023, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Music Box, Silver Rose</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/10/951e33459f840611987033f66f1917eb.jpg" />
<p><i>When activated, plays a music box arrangement of the devotional "Silver Rose" composition.</i></p> 
<p>The Music Box, Silver Rose will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from November 22 to November 30, 2023, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Houses</h2> 
<p><b>Bastion Sanguinaris</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2022/07/fee2bd7a14c8a01fbe7e887ac8f5469e.jpg" />
<p><i>Towering architecture, views to die (or kill) for, and a secret passage number among the many features of this striking Blackreach edifice, which stands within easy reach of Greymoor Keep.</i></p> 
<p>Bastion Sanguinaris will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from November 9 to November 22, 2023, at 10AM EST. Furnished and unfurnished versions will be available.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Kushalit Sanctuary</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/10/4dc8bb9ce3218161a128a0e20f23eed9.jpg" />
<p><i>The recently abandoned Sheogorath shrine that locals call Assalkushalit features a statue to the Mad God within its stony hall. Whether you revere this Daedric Prince or want a home nestled in Red Mountain, this portal-ridden sanctuary can be yours!</i></p> 
<p>Kushalit Sanctuary will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from November 13 to November 20, 2023, at 10AM EST. Furnished and unfurnished versions will be available.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Pantherfang Chapel</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2022/11/91074d21fec55cd27b1ff00b70ff6eb5.jpg" />
<p><i>The embattled clergy of the Quenching Grail established Pantherfang Chapel in the First Era as a bastion of faith. Part cathedral, part citadel, this edifice still stands as an immortal reminder of Aedric strength. Allows use of the Pledge of Mara.</i></p> 
<p>Pantherfang Chapel will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from November 22 to December 7, 2023, at 10AM EST. Furnished and unfurnished versions will be available.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Houseguests</h2> 
<p><b>Rigurt the Brash</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/10/507dd59169e697e02e66caac7c76d2a0.jpg" />
<p><i>The Nord diplomat Rigurt travels around Tamriel to learn about other cultures while demonstrating his own brand of Nord culture. Welcome him home! After adding Rigurt to your home, you can set him on a path, plus you and your visitors can speak with him.</i></p> 
<p>Rigurt the Brash will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from November 9 to November 16, 2023, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Mounts</h2> 
<p><b>Umbral Striped Senche-raht</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/10/4d5773932da2d33f75fad90d9eac2147.jpg" />
<p><i>When this beautiful beast lost their rider while traversing a labyrinth, this banded Senche-raht left to seek mystical help to get back inside. Since their efforts often lead them into peril, Nushaben hopes to find a partner for the long journeys ahead.</i></p> 
<p>The Umbral Striped Senche-raht mount will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from November 2, 2023, at 10AM EDT to November 9, 2023, at 10AM EST.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Autumn Messenger Fox</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/10/b037f0be0cf94284c874cb778e7ef4fa.jpg" />
<p><i>"As kits, these rambunctious little trouble-making furballs keep this one on her toes. But their predilection for trouble when young works in your favor—their ability to sense harm is nearly magical. Perfect for messenger work!"—Tesusah, Stablemaster</i></p> 
<p>The Autumn Messenger Fox mount will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from November 16 to November 22, 2023, at 10AM EST.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Packlord Nightmare Wolf</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/10/358757225f2e9cc0bbbfc16b4fb3aa5a.jpg" />
<p><i>Lord of the Nightmare Pack, this night-black Wolf mount has burning paws and flames hissing from its face and tail; can anyone doubt that its origin must be Mehrunes Dagon's plane of the Deadlands?</i></p> 
<p>The Packlord Nightmare Wolf will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from November 20 to November 27, 2023, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<p><i> </i></p> 
<p><b>Voideater Durzog</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/10/bd09357fb1a1c6b5b4ebf726b2041439.jpg" />
<p><i>No one knows how these beasts found their way into Blackreach, but it didn't take long for them to heed the Dark Heart's call. Drenched in the void's corruption, this mount will chill your enemies to the bone.</i></p> 
<p>The Voideater Durzog mount will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from November 22 to November 30, 2023, at 10AM EST. </p> 
<p><i> </i></p> 
<p><b>Grand Nibenese Stallion</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/10/fb8baa5a22778f51a0f641c455664c4d.jpg" />
<p><i>Though some claim these horses are bred purely for show, the Grand Nibenese Stallion serves as more than just a good luck charm in Leyawiin. They possess a keen intelligence and even temperament—maintaining their composure, even on crowded streets.</i></p> 
<p>The Grand Nibenese Stallion mount will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from November 27 to December 4, 2023, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<p><i> </i></p> 
<h2>Pets</h2> 
<p><b>Sylvan Nixad</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/10/0ca404cb080e14045e03c5ebf9ec497b.jpg" />
<p><i>Once a common sight in Cyrodiil's Great Forest, the Sylvan Nixad is now most often encountered in the glades and meadows of the Gold Coast. Once tamed, they make charming companions, loyal and easy to care for.</i></p> 
<p>The Sylvan Nixad pet will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from November 2, 2023, at 10AM EDT, to November 6, 2023, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Snowsnarl Durzog</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/10/0e02c958ceaa79c445a425a932cedc6a.jpg" />
<p><i>Born with a snarl, these striped durzogs tend to bite the hand that feeds them—but only gently after they get to know you.</i></p> 
<p>The Snowsnarl Durzog pet will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from November 2, 2023, at 10AM EDT to November 6, 2023, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Hallin's Jackal</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/10/1b6286917c73331fcde383174e790a35.jpg" />
<p><i>After news of the Seventh Legion's presence near Hallin's Stand spread, several Evermore citizens moved quickly to protect some at-risk fauna, among them a breed of easily domesticated jackals. Now one of these fierce companions can roam at your side.</i></p> 
<p>The Hallin's Jackal pet will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from November 6 to November 9, 2023, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Daedrat</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/10/d5affcd82065f52286145e342f045ae4.jpg" />
<p><i>This scurrying vermin from Oblivion would be lost in the vastness of Nirn without a loyal companion and guide. Even a Daedric rodent needs a friend.</i></p> 
<p>The Daedrat pet will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from November 13 to November 16, 2023, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Mint Swamp Jelly</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/10/ae1850f3a596f410d6289b371fd571b2.jpg" />
<p><i>Though the Argonians claim that they name each breed of Black Marsh Swamp Jelly for its hue rather than its taste, there's no denying that the Mint Jelly does have a gratifyingly refreshing flavor.</i></p> 
<p>The Mint Swamp Jelly pet will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from November 20 to November 27, 2023, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Deadlands Bantam Guar</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/10/df85daac99b32717e51dbdec50f3cf34.jpg" />
<p><i>It may look cute, but this volcanic little pest comes from Mehrunes Dagon's Oblivion plane of the Deadlands: it's got lava in its blood and fire in its eyes, so keep it away from the curtains.</i></p> 
<p>The Deadlands Bantam Guar pet will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from November 20 to November 27, 2023, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Woodhearth Brown Rabbit</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/10/230d41aedf2a2dede916a96f37771d44.jpg" />
<p><i>Some Wood Elf spinners claim Y'ffre granted these bunnies as part of the Green Pact, scholars contest that Second Empire Imperials brought them when establishing Woodhearth and, well, nature took its course. These hoppy hares make great fuzzy friends!</i></p> 
<p>The Woodhearth Brown Rabbit pet will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from November 27 to November 30, 2023, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<p> </p> 
<h2>Polymorphs</h2> 
<p><b>Shadowsilk Goblin</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/10/345b941f8bc157c7747174a97232eed4.jpg" />
<p><i>Feel left out? Alienated? Alone? Adopt the form of a Shadowsilk Goblin, and you might* find that sense of belonging you crave among these creatures! Fleas not included, but easily attainable. *Might is no guarantee. They may try to eat you instead.</i></p> 
<p>The Shadowsilk Goblin polymorph will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from November 13 to November 20, 2023, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Special Promotions</h2> 
<p><b>Rotating Sales</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/10/e433354b6618467b1c3911f81dde31bd.jpg" />
<p><i>Take advantage of these weekly rotating offers! </i></p> 
<p>In addition, we'll have additional discounts in the Crown Store every weekend in November. Check back in the Crown Store every Thursday for details on these sales!</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Removal of Existing Crown Store Items</h2> 
<p>In addition, the following items will be retired from the Crown Store on all platforms on December 4 at 10am EST, so get them while you can!</p> 
<p><b>Motifs</b></p> 
<ul><li>Crown Crafting Motif: Dreadsails</li><li>Crown Crafting Motif: Ascendant Order</li><li>Crown Crafting Motif: Syrabanic Marine</li><li>Crown Crafting Motif: Systres Guardian</li><li>Crown Crafting Motif: Y'ffre's Will</li><li>Crown Crafting Motif: Drowned Mariner</li></ul><p><br></p> 
<p>From weapons Daedric and divine to a humble hare, this month's Crown Store offerings have something for everyone. You can get the Crowns you'll need for these exciting new acquisitions through visiting the <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/buycrowns">Buy Crowns page</a> to stock up. Are you planning to use any of these items to impress the denizens of the Endless Archive with your fashion sense? Let us know how they react via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, or <a href="https://www.facebook.com/ElderScrollsOnline">Facebook</a>!</p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Crown Store</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/10/473ae27aaf95a2ea078e54ecb72bdd86.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Daily Login Rewards—November 2023]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/64919</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/64919</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Preview some of the free rewards available just by logging in during the month of November 2023!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/10/7f854960c9f8daf83e2ff3a099799301.jpg" /><p><i>Preview some of the free rewards available just by logging in during the month of November 2023!</i></p> 
<p>For those with plans in Tamriel (or the realms of Oblivion!) this November 2023, a wide range of rewards awaits each day you log in. You can find a sampling of what's on offer below, from a refreshing emote to a snappy dresser of a Houseguest. Simply claim them from the Daily Rewards section of the Crown Store—you can find any details you might need in <a href="https://help.bethesda.net/#en/answer/41950">this help article</a>. </p> 
<p><b><br></b></p><p><b>Sit and Drink Emote—Day 7</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/10/7017565bd3c1d77750cb92c9983a8a79.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>That hits the spot!</i></p> 
<p>As 2023 begins to wind down, many people want nothing more than to relax in a comfy seat with a refreshing beverage. Fortunately for you, you can now Sit and Drink in game, perhaps even while you sit and drink at your desk or on your couch!</p> 
<p><b><br></b></p><p><b>Seals of Endeavor ×250—Day 14</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/10/cbf054f9fa4122ee9be26996607da8d2.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Treat yourself with some Seals of Endeavor!</i></p> 
<p>If you have an interest in any of the offerings available in our Crown Crates, these Seals of Endeavor make a great alternative means of acquisition. Also earned by completing Daily and Weekly Endeavors as you play, this special in-game currency allows you to acquire offerings from current Crown Crates or items purchasable with Crown Gems. You can learn more about Seals of Endeavor <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/59925">in this blog</a>.</p> 
<p><b><br></b></p><p><b>Mizzik Thunderboots Houseguest—Day 21</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/10/be683f8349ee07282464477c6ea42990.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Investigate the Daily Login Rewards alongside Mizzik</i></p><p>Even the most stylish of investigators sometimes needs a break from casework, and so Mizzik Thunderboots has found himself in need of a place to hang up his signature hat. If you log in enough throughout November, that place could be your own in-game house, as the clever Khajiit will be available as a Houseguest via Daily Login Rewards!</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p>As handsome as these rewards are, they comprise only a few of the login rewards available in <i>ESO</i> next month. You can view the complete list in the Daily Rewards section of the in-game Crown Store on November 1! Which reward are you most looking forward to? Do you plan to Sit and Drink beside Mizzik Thunderboots, or has one of the items available for Seals of Endeavor caught your eye? Share your plans for this month in <i>ESO </i>with us on <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (Formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>. </p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Daily Rewards</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/10/7f854960c9f8daf83e2ff3a099799301.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Conquer Tamriel's Fears and Earn Special Rewards during the Witches Festival Event]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/64847</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/64847</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Slay Tamriel's most horrific monstrosities to obtain unique in-game rewards during 2023's Witches Festival in-game event!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/10/2a97cd6fcb87cdfc399c1743347f27e5.jpg" /><p><i>Slay Tamriel's most horrific monstrosities to obtain unique in-game rewards during 2023's Witches Festival in-game event!</i></p> 
<h2>The Festival of Frights Returns!</h2> 
<p>This year's Witches Festival in-game event begins next Thursday, October 26 at 10AM EDT, and runs until Tuesday, November 7 at 10AM EST. During this <b>spoopiest</b> of occasions, you can claim terrifyingly awesome event-specific rewards including Plunder Skulls, XP gain boosts, Event Tickets, and more!</p> 
<p>During the Witches Festival, all adventurers can enjoy a passive 100% boost to XP gain at all times. To collect the Witchmother's Whistle and down ladles of hag's brew, simply follow the steps listed below:</p> 
<ul><li>Open the Crown Store and acquire the free quest, “The Witchmother's Bargain.”</li><ul><li>You can also pick up this quest by speaking with the Crow Caller, who you'll find outside of each Olyve's Brewery in Stonefalls, Glenumbra, or Auridon.</li></ul><li>Complete the introductory quest to receive the Witchmother's Whistle tool.</li><ul><li>You won't need to acquire the Witchmother's Whistle if you finished the quest in a previous year's event.</li></ul><li>Blow the whistle to summon the “Witchmother's Cauldron,” which you drink from to polymorph yourself into a spooky scary skeleton.</li><ul><li>You cannot summon the Cauldron in Cyrodiil.</li></ul></ul>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/10/5aeb94e9326505ab14ed6d3167d985f7.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Take a sip from the Witchmother's Cauldron</i></p> 
<h2>Acquire Cursed Rewards</h2> 
<p>During the Witches Festival event period, whenever you defeat a boss monster, you'll be offered a <b>Plunder Skull</b> container in addition to any regular rewards.</p> 
<p>When you open a Plunder Skull, you have the <b>chance </b>to receive the following items:</p> 
<ul><li>Alchemy reagents</li><li>A festival-themed furnishing recipe</li><li>A festival-themed provisioning recipe</li><li>A complete festival-themed furnishing</li><li>A festival-themed treasure</li><li>A small chance for one of the following:</li><ul><li>A Hollowjack style item </li><li>A Dremora style items</li></ul><li>Worms, Crawlers, Guts, Insect Parts</li> </ul> 
<p>What's more, whenever you fell a different unique type of boss for the first time each day, you'll be rewarded with a special <b>Dremora Plunder Skull</b> that contains some of the above items in addition to these:</p> 
<ul><li>Dremora motif chapter</li> <li>A chance for one of the following items:</li> <ul><li>A Witches Festival Writ</li> <li>A Glenmoril Teasure Map or Glenmoril armor outfit style page</li> <li>A Grave Dancer weapon style page</li> <li><b>NEW</b> A Tome of Forbidden Appetites Memento Runebox </li> <li><b>NEW</b> A Witches Festival Ghost Netch pet fragment </li> <li><b>NEW</b> A tradeable style page for the Crowborne Hunter outfit style </li> </ul></ul> 
<p>The different types of bosses that offer these Dremora Plunder Skulls include arena bosses, incursion bosses (from Dark Anchors, Harrowstorms, Volcanic Vents, etc.), delve bosses, final dungeon bosses, Trial bosses, public dungeon bosses, and world bosses. </p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/10/585589416bb9e049ce19a73b2eb8525e.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Reap a host of haunted rewards</i></p> 
<p>Monsters of all shapes and sizes lurk throughout Tamriel this time of year, but there is one creepy beastie that is feared above all: <b>The Crowborne Horror</b>. To locate and slay this living nightmare, acquire the daily quest “Plucking the Crow” by speaking with the Witchmother Taerma, located inside of Olyve's Brewery and at every Impresario tent found throughout Tamriel. </p> 
<p>For your courage, you'll be rewarded with a Dremora Plunder Skull that has a <b>small chance </b>to grant you an incredible offering of tradeable<i> </i>Witches Festival valuables <b>instead </b>of regular Dremora Plunder Skull items, including: </p> 
<ul><li>10 Witch-Tamed Bear Dog fragments</li><li>The FULL style book for the Dremora motif</li><li>A folio of ALL Glenmoril Treasure Maps</li><li>Runebox: Tome of Forbidden Appetites</li><li>A random Crowborne Hunter outfit style page</li></ul> 
<h2>Impresario &amp; Event Tickets</h2> 
<p>During the Witches Festival, you can collect two Event Tickets from the first boss you defeat each day, earning up to 26 tickets by the end of the event. But don't forget: You can hold up to 12 Event Tickets only. </p> 
<p>For this event, the Impresario will stock the following items:</p> 
<ul><li>All three Passion Dancer Blossom pet fragments: </li><ul><li>Chartreuse Lily Petals</li><li>Enchanted Silver Flute</li><li>Mystical Sheet Music</li></ul><li>The first fragment for Hoardhunter Ursauk mount:</li><ul><li>Blessed Honeycomb</li></ul><li>Crowborne Hunter outfit style pages </li><li>Witches Festival Ghost Netch pet fragment </li><li>Tome of Forbidden Appetites memento </li><li>Assorted Spooky Witches festival-themed Furnishings</li><ul><li>Webs, Cone furnishing </li><li>Hollowjack Lantern, Ouroboros furnishing </li><li>Specimen Jar, Spare Brain furnishing </li><li>Ruby Candlefly Gathering furnishing </li><li>Vampiric Lamp, Azure Tall furnishing </li><li>Vampiric Lightpost, Azure Single furnishing </li><li>Vampiric Container, Yellow Liquid furnishing </li></ul><li>Group Repair Kit </li><li>Companion Guild Commendations </li><li>Witches Grab Bag <b>(This is purchasable only if you haven't yet collected all the items contained within)</b></li><ul><li>Skeletal Marionette memento</li><li>Spectre Mask collectible</li><ul><li>There are four variations of this collectible</li></ul><li>Apple-Bobbing Cauldron fragment</li><li>Throw Bones Memento fragment</li><li>Marshmallow Toasty Treat emote</li><li>Witch's Bonfire Dust</li><li>Ghastly Visitation memento</li><li>Witch-Tamed Bear-Dog pet fragment</li><li>Witchmother's Servant outfit style pages</li></ul></ul> 
<p>Of note: The Witches Festival will be your first opportunity to begin gathering the fragments for the final event morphing collectible of 2023, the Hoardhunter Ursauk mount!</p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/10/03b4980cc9b98474c52101a5989b108e.png" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Hoardhunter Ursauk morphing collectible</i></p> 
<p>Additionally, the Impresario's colleague, Nenulaure the Indrik Vendor, has the following items available for purchase using Event Tickets:</p> 
<ul><li>Nascent Indrik Feathers</li><li>Pure Snow Indrik Berries</li><li>Crimson Indrik Berries</li><li>Frost-Light Indrik Pet</li><li>Rosethorn Indrik Pet</li></ul> 
<p>Lastly, the Impresario's Assistant is offering the following, which you can acquire with Event Tickets:</p> 
<ul><li>Unstable Morpholith fragments</li><ul><li>Deadlands Flint</li><li>Rune-Etched Striker</li><li>Smoldering Bloodgrass Tinder</li></ul><li>Dagonic Quasigriff fragments</li><ul><li>Smoke-Wreathed Gryphon Feather </li><li>Black Iron Bit </li><li>Bridle Black Iron Stirrups</li></ul></ul> 
<p>The spooky season has returned, and Nirn need heroes to help bring Tamriel's terrors under control. Will you come to their aid and enjoy the XP boosts, collectibles, and other rewards during the 2023 Witches Festival in-game event? Let us know via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/ElderScrollsOnline">Facebook</a>.</p> 
<p><i>The Witches Festival in-game event begins Thursday, October 26 at 10AM EDT, and runs until Tuesday, November 7 at 10AM EST.</i></p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Events</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/10/2a97cd6fcb87cdfc399c1743347f27e5.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Crown Store Gifting Update – October 2023]]></title>
            <link>https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/644559/crown-store-gifting-update-october-2023</link>
            <guid>https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/644559/crown-store-gifting-update-october-2023</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 20:22:11 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[Following up on Studio Director Matt Firor's message last month about the <a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/643289/update-on-current-and-future-status-of-gifting">current and future status of Crown Store Gifting</a>, we are moving forward with re-enabling this functionality for eligible players at the account level. In this post, we will detail what to expect.<br><br>
In September, we temporarily disabled Crown Store gifting due to a rapidly growing issue of "bad actors" using various fraudulent means to amass crowns without paying for them, then using them in turn to sell Crown Store items to players for real-world cash outside of the game client. That said, we recognize that gifting is a meaningful part of our community, and we are in the process of manually re-enabling Crown Store gifting access for select players who meet our specific criteria. This work will be complete tomorrow, October 11, during the maintenance window from 09:00 AM ET to 12:00 PM ET.<br><br>
Gifting eligibility is determined by an evolving list of factors including but not limited to the account being at least 180 days past its first login and previous engagement with in-game features. You may check if you have access to gifting in-game via the Crown Store as well as via <a href="https://account.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/account/billing/billing-history">your billing history page</a> in the ESO account center. If you have access to Crown Store gifting, you will see "Allow Crown Store Gifting" in your billing history. If you try to send a gift via the in-game Crown Store and do not have access, you will see a "Gifting Locked" pop-up message. Please note that we are exploring better ways to display this information in-game in the future, such as updating the Gifting Tutorial.<br><br>
If you do not have access to Crown Store gifting after it is re-enabled on October 11, 2023, and wish for a review of your account, please visit <a href="https://help.elderscrollsonline.com">https://help.elderscrollsonline.com</a> and submit a Customer Support ticket. Please choose the Billing / Purchase / Code category then Platform &gt; I have a question about a sale / offer &gt; I want to send gift items from this account.<br><br>
We appreciate everyone's understanding and patience while we get this solution up and running. Multiple teams have worked long hours to evaluate the best technical solutions that we could stand up in a reasonably short time, while also prioritizing the Crown Store gifting player experience. We are dedicated to continuing to explore ways to make this better and reduce fraudulent activity in ESO. Thanks again for being a part of our community and for your continued support.]]></content:encoded>
            <category>Forum</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Explore the Necrom Chapter & Unlock Bonus Rewards during the Secrets of the Telvanni In-Game Event]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/64773</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/64773</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Team up with your fellow players within the Telvanni Peninsula and Apocrypha to unlock unique rewards for all Necrom owners.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/ae4b9368b38d467f598a83f8789e07b1.jpg" /><p><i>Team up with your fellow players within the Telvanni Peninsula and Apocrypha to unlock unique rewards for all Necrom owners.</i></p><h2>Challenge complete! </h2><p>Claim your unlocked rewards from the in-game Crown Store from now until Friday, October 20 at 10AM EDT. Don't forget, you need access to the <i>Necrom </i>Chapter to claim all Secrets of the Telvanni rewards—don't miss out! <br></p><p> </p> <h2>Explore the Unknown</h2> <p>The Secrets of the Telvanni in-game event kicks off this Thursday, September 28 at 10AM EDT, and runs until Tuesday, October 10 at 10AM EDT. During the celebration event, you can earn bonus rewards and collectibles as you complete daily quests and adventure within the Telvanni Peninsula and Apocrypha zones. </p> <p>Work together with your fellow players to complete the new event-unique daily quest, titled “Turn the Page” to progress the community meter found on the <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/secretsofthetelvanni">Secrets of the Telvanni event page</a>. By the event's end, <b>all</b> <i>Necrom</i> Chapter owners can claim all unlocked rewards. </p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/465fa8e917cecd80c6133b75bce12ced.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Complete a new daily quest</i></p> 
<p>Every day, we'll update the meter on the event page with the #ESOFam's progress. The more of you who complete the quest each day, the quicker the meter will fill and unlock the rewards.</p> 
<p>You can see the percentage goal for each of the three rewards below: </p> 
<ul><li>33% Ebony Dwarven Scarab pet</li><li>66% Nightmare Nest body and face markings</li><li>100% Kelesan'ruhn house </li></ul>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/7bccc2dcdba8feca0070c0a31a336ff2.jpg" />
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/d07883828451b46064ce7aed1ee404e6.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Unlock these unique rewards (and more)</i></p> 
<p>To get started, acquire the quest titled “The Telvanni Secret” free from the Crown Store or find Master Faras outside the city of Necrom. Don't forget, this event and its rewards are available only for those who own the <i>Necrom</i> Chapter. </p> 
<p>In addition, when turning in the unique event daily quest, you must choose between Tralise and Yensa for one additional end-of-event reward: </p> 
<ul><li>Oath of the Keepers music box (from Tralise)</li><li>Apocryphal Tome furnishing (from Yensa)</li></ul> 
<p>Throughout the event, you can vote for which reward you'd like to unlock by choosing to either favor <b>Tralise</b> (to unlock the music box) or <b>Yensa</b> (to unlock the furnishing) when turning in the “Turn the Page” daily quest. </p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/527f7eb6feaec7a56365cfba209b437f.jpg" />
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/0c8b5839a15c783a7c1a4932c2de4c79.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center"><i>Only one of these two bonus rewards can be unlocked!</i></p> <p>The sister with the most favor by the event's end will determine which bonus reward is unlocked. You can check which of the two sisters is currently favored during the event on the <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/secretsofthetelvanni;">official page</a>.</p><p><b>Update: </b>Yensa is the most favored! You can claim the Apocryphal Tome furnishing from the in-game Crown Store from now until Friday, October 20 at 10AM EDT. </p><p> </p> <h2>(Re)Discover Necrom</h2> <p>During the event period, as you adventure within the Telvanni Peninsula and Apocrypha, you receive event reward boxes, called Secret Telvanni Coffers, each time you complete a daily quest. In addition, you have a <b>chance</b> to receive a coffer when you complete the following activities in either of the two zones: </p> <ul><li>Defeat a Delve or World Boss </li><li>Defeat a Bastion Nymic Herald or Boss</li><li>Defeat any monster</li><li>Opening treasure chests, safeboxes, Psijic Portals, etc.</li><li>Harvesting resource nodes</li><li>Pickpocketing</li><li>…and more! </li></ul> <p>When you open a Secret Telvanni Coffer, you have a <b>chance</b> to receive the following items:</p> <ul><li>Random crafting materials</li><li>Valuables (that can be sold to vendors) or style items</li><li>Zone set items or Companion gear (only while either Azandar or Sharp are active)</li><li>Necrom furnishings, furnishing recipes, Treasure Maps, Survey Reports, or a motif page (Dead Keeper or Clan Dreamcarver)</li><li>A small chance for a tradeable style page of the <b>NEW</b> Apocrypha Expedition armor style</li></ul> <p>Take note, the first time you complete a Telvanni Peninsula or Apocrypha daily quest, you receive a <b>Sublime Secret Telvanni Coffer</b> instead of a standard one. Sublime coffers can contain the same items as regular ones, but also have a <b>much</b> <b>greater</b> <b>chance</b> of containing the rarer rewards (such as pages for the Apocrypha Expedition armor style).</p>
<a href="https://youtube.com/v/5jOUum46eqI?autoplay=1&rel=0"><img src="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/5jOUum46eqI/maxresdefault.jpg" /></a>
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Venture into the Necrom Chapter</i></p> 
<p>Finally, in addition to the reward coffers, during the event period adventurers enjoy these additional bonuses when venturing into the Telvanni Peninsula and Apocrypha:</p> 
<ul><li>ALL zone daily quests and Trial weekly quests have their usual non-event reward boxes doubled.</li><li>Harvest node yields are increased. </li><li>World, Delve, and Trial Bosses all award double loot.</li></ul> 
<h2>Impresario Event Goods</h2> 
<p>During the Secrets of the Telvanni event, you can earn <b>two event tickets per day</b>, awarded by completing <b>any</b> daily quest in either the Telvanni Peninsula or Apocrypha zones.</p> 
<p>The Impresario stocks the following items during the event period:</p> 
<ul><li>All three <b>Passion Dancer Blossom</b> pet fragments:</li><ul><li>Chartreuse Lily Petals</li><li>Enchanted Silver Flute</li><li>Mystical Sheet Music</li></ul><li>All three <b>Passion Dancer's Attire </b>costume fragments:</li><ul><li>Bolt of Indigo Cotton</li><li>Bolt of Silver Silk</li><li>Enchanted Sewing Kit</li></ul><li>Bound style pages for the <b>NEW</b> Apocrypha Expedition style</li><li>Group Repair Kits</li><li>Companion Guild Commendations</li></ul>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/07/72f6c741dec03864b7ae6048f5261b1f.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>The Passion Dancer's Attire costume</i></p> 
<p>Also during the event, the Indrik Vendor Nenulaure stocks: </p> 
<ul><li>Nascent Indrik Feathers</li><li>Onyx Indrik Berries</li><li>Mossheart Indrik Berries</li><li>Ebon-Glow Indrik Pet</li><li>Sapling Indrik Pet</li></ul> 
<p>Finally, the Impresario's Assistant has the following items:</p> 
<ul><li>All three <b>Unstable Morpholith </b>pet fragments</li><ul><li>Deadlands Flint</li><li>Rune-Etched Striker</li><li>Smoldering Bloodgrass Tinder</li></ul><li>ll three <b>Deadlands Firewalker </b>personality fragments</li><ul><li>Vial of Simmering Daedric Brew</li><li>Vial of Bubbling Daedric Brew</li><li>Vial of Scalding Daedric Brew</li></ul></ul> 
<h2>Wonderful Worlds Await </h2> 
<p>Venture into the Telvanni Peninsula and Apocrypha zones, complete daily quests, choose your favored sister, and unlock unique rewards for ALL <i>Necrom</i> Chapter players. Don't forget, the only way you can participate in this event and receive its unique rewards is to first own <i>The Elder Scrolls Online: Necrom</i>. Are you excited to delve into the weird and wonderful worlds of the <i>Necrom </i>Chapter? Let us know via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">Twitter</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, or <a href="https://www.facebook.com/ElderScrollsOnline">Facebook</a> and don't forget to check the community's progress on the <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/secretsofthetelvanni">event's official page</a>—good luck! </p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Events</category>
            <category>Necrom</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/ae4b9368b38d467f598a83f8789e07b1.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Crown Store Showcase—October 2023]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/64775</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/64775</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Try not to scream (in excitement) at the collection of terrifying and terrific new items arriving in the Crown Store this October.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/b6bfa865294a6b4077661f61482968f5.jpg" /><p><i>Try not to scream (in excitement) at the collection of terrifying and terrific new items arriving in the Crown Store this October.</i></p> 
<p>Check out the complete list of contents arriving in the Crown Store in October 2023 below. Don't forget you can always review everything on sale right now by heading over to the <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/crownstore">Crown Store page</a>. Before that, be sure to open the <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/buycrowns">Buy Crowns page</a> to pick up however many crowns you need. Certain items and offers will be time-limited throughout the month, so be sure to read their individual details below and don't miss out.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<h2>ESO Plus Deals</h2> 
<p>All ESO Plus™ members have access to a monthly selection of exclusive deals and items. You can find more information about them in <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/54825">this article</a>.</p> 
<p><b>Exclusive Free Items</b></p> 
<p><b>Painting: Sanity's Edge</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/3e10fbf1a65fb7fd255f65b6f7afde8c.jpg" />
<p><i>"As you can see by my attached references, I am one of the foremost experts in vicinage wards, forfending spells, and the art of research. If anyone can deal with the Dreamstone's ire, it is me. I hope you come to the same conclusion."—Warlock Vanton</i></p> <p>The Painting: Sanity's Edge will be available in the Crown Store FREE exclusively to ESO Plus Members on all platforms for a limited time, from October 12 at 10AM EDT to November 22, 2023, at 10AM EST.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> <h2>Crown Gem and Seals of Endeavor Items</h2> <p><b>Mounts</b></p> <p><b>Bonfire Wicker-Steed</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/9f6ba7679d72c7ec6b46c598e34969f6.jpg" />
<p><i>Woe to any who ride this fiery steed without its consent! Sanctified by ashes from the funeral pyres of venerated witches, this wicker steed blazes a path across Tamriel and beyond, reminding any mortals who see it of their own short lifespans.</i></p> 
<p>The Bonfire Wicker-Steed will be available for Crown Gems and Seals of Endeavor on all platforms for a limited time, from October 2 at 10AM EDT to November 6, 2023, at 10AM EST.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Customized Actions</b></p> 
<p><b>Coldfire Recall</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/1b2b6496295bfd3c683340d5e1cff204.jpg" />
<p><i>"The cold-flames speak to me. Will the flames speak to you, too, calling you to a master? Or perhaps you are a master—of bones? No matter. Go where your path leads, as I do. Perhaps we'll meet next in Coldharbour?"—Ymirra, Master of Bone and Scythe</i></p> 
<p>The Coldfire Recall will be available for Crown Gems and Seals of Endeavor on all platforms for a limited time, from October 19, 2023, to November 2, 2023, at 10AM EDT.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<h2>Adornments</h2> 
<p><b>Hats</b></p> 
<p><b>Jhunal's Owl Mask</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/32861bfeaa2ab07c92f6ac31b8eeff4b.jpg" />
<p><i>Wise-Wing the Owl is associated in northern Tamriel with the god Jhunal or Julianos. During the Witches Festival she is said to warn the unwary away from graveyards and witches' covens where they may come to harm.</i></p> 
<p>The Jhunal's Owl Mask will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 2 to October 5, 2023, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Rajhin's Cat Mask</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/8374cd5c6206c5c07fd1d78124780f34.jpg" />
<p><i>During the Witches Festival, no one perpetrates more cunning and devious tricks than Rajhin the Footpad, the Purring Liar. This mask enables you to adopt one of the many faces of that consummate trickster.</i></p> 
<p>The Rajhin's Cat Mask will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 2 to October 5, 2023, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Nightmare Daemon Mask Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/a17499ac08d8a66de9f5b0b27e8adc27.jpg" />
<p><i>This bundle includes the Nightmare Daemon Mask for Humans and Elves along with the variations for Khajiit and Argonians.</i></p> 
<p>The Nightmare Daemon Mask Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 16 to October 23, 2023, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Daedric Death Mask</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/c5564ee79fea3ae09213bccef47e0a64.jpg" />
<p><i>Daedra Worshiper, do you dare wear a mask that strikes fear into the souls of ordinary mortals? Then the Daedric Death Mask is for you! For as is graven upon its metal horn bands: FEAR ABIDES.</i></p> 
<p>The Daedric Death Mask will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 23 to October 26, 2023, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Flatbrim Mourning Hat Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/52b5c48d992b33ba7a2d68e058f49ade.jpg" />
<p><i>Bundle including three Flatbrim Hats: the Modest Mourning Hat, Deluxe Mourning Hat, and Plumed Mourning Hat.</i></p> 
<p>The Flatbrim Mourning Hat Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 30 to November 2, 2023, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Markings</b></p> 
<p><b>Warrior-Poet Tattoos</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/5ce53a41b68fac41e6adc378cf5d0637.jpg" />
<p><i>This bundle includes the Warrior-Poet tattoo markings for both face and body. Vehk yourself!</i></p> 
<p>The Warrior-Poet Tattoos will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 30 to November 2, 2023, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Warrior-Poet Skull Tattoo</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/04b0761a8ea0a2d696acb1685aab178c.jpg" />
<p><i>"Colorful and intimidating. Truly, these markings bring the fire of the warrior-poet to your spirit as well as to your face."—Artist-Adept Aimira</i></p> 
<p>The Warrior-Poet Skull Tattoo will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 30 to November 2, 2023, at 10AM EDT.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Skull Face Tattoo Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/762d578bb9f96abc1d22c81360e9117e.jpg" />
<p><i>Face marking bundle including the Verdant, Floral, and Spoked Skull Face Tattoos.</i></p> 
<p>The Skull Face Tattoo Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 30 to November 2, 2023, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Skins</h2> 
<p><b>Decayed Zombie</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/299b13f0a1544478287013d427a0c538.jpg" />
<p><i>Decayed Zombie: the skin condition no amount of Lillandril Moisturizing Lotion can cure! Pairs well with Worm Cult style armor.</i></p> 
<p>The Decayed Zombie will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 12 to October 19, 2023, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Crafting</h2> 
<p><b>Motifs</b></p> 
<p><b>Crown Crafting Motifs: Grim Harlequin</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/3620304a22696e3172af0c2c69d8d677.jpg" />
<p><i>As Chamberlain Haskill explains, "My Lord Sheogorath has directed me to compile a guide for those seeking to create 'Grim Harlequin' arms and armor, so that the Mad God's mortal servants may have a way to make all their equipment look the same. Of course, this standardization runs counter to all other cult practices, and is insane on the face of it. What's your point?" Motif book and style items that enable crafting in the Grim Harlequin style.</i></p> 
<p>The Crown Crafting Motifs: Grim Harlequin will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms starting October 5 to October 12, 2023, at 10AM EDT.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Crown Crafting Motif: Kindred's Concord</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/da5c3e5c124fe4784592865b29e704f9.jpg" />
<p><i>High Priest Blightcrown writes of those using this style, “Many of you are entrusted with duties that require you to move without notice among the scoffers and persecutors of our world.” Use to learn the Kindred's Concord crafting style. Also has a chance to drop from daily coffers and bosses from Bastion Nymic.</i></p> 
<p>The Crown Crafting Motif: Kindred's Concord will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms starting October 18, 2023, at 10AM EDT. The Kindred's Concord chapters, and very rarely the complete book, have a chance to drop from Bastion Nymic and Bastion Nymic Coffers, awarded from Ordinator Tandasea in Necrom.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Outfit Styles</b></p> 
<p><b>Thurvokun Arms Pack </b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/251608e75ad0dab18611d9a15a96b4ae.jpg" />
<p><i>The long-dead Dragon Thurvokun once inhabited Fang Lair—but a Necromancer seeks to reawaken him! Stop this threat, then alter your weapon's appearance to match the Undaunted Thurvokun awards by using this complete set of Outfit styles.</i></p> 
<p>The Thurvokun Arms Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms starting October 2, 2023, to October 9, 2023, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item. The matching mask page will have a small chance to drop from Thurvokun from veteran Fang Lair. The matching shoulder page can be purchased from Urgarlag Chief-bane for 50 Undaunted Keys, or has a chance of dropping from Urgarlag's Mystery Coffer for 1 Key. Having the achievement “Let Bygones Be Bygones” increases the drop chances of both items.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Elder Scrolls Artifact: Volendrung</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/bfe5cbd9892d8972578f6562dcbe1ea3.jpg" />
<p><i>Alter your two-handed weapon's Outfit style with a replica of the Volendrung Elder Scrolls Artifact, a paradoxical weapon forever torn between its Dwarven origins and Malacath's Daedric influence.</i></p> 
<p>The Elder Scrolls Artifact: Volendrung will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms starting October 5, 2023, to October 9, 2023, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Elder Scrolls Artifact: Ebony Blade</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/fe28f8e4aa4eec9bb91354aff60c3f4c.jpg" />
<p><i>Alter your two-handed weapon's Outfit style with a replica of the Ebony Blade Elder Scrolls Artifact, a weapon forged by the Daedric Prince Mephala</i></p> 
<p>The Elder Scrolls Artifact: Ebony Blade will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms starting October 9, 2023, to October 16, 2023, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Evergloam Champion Armor Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/cb74fb06c8dcc950c97f4ed2ea397e61.jpg" />
<p><i> Adherents of Nocturnal who venture to the Evergloam sometimes come back changed in more ways than one—the armor of that realm may hold greater appeal to the Daedric Prince of Shadow's followers than any mortal gear they initially wore. Alter your armor's appearance by using this complete set of Evergloam Champion Armor Outfit styles.</i></p> 
<p>The Evergloam Champion Armor Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms starting October 23, 2023, to October 30, 2023, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Crowborne Hunter Arms Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/bd5d4d69a0ddc70b597a2e0213ca1430.jpg" />
<p><i>Sergeant Qasim of Evermore notes, “The combination of fastidious detail work and exquisite balance on these weapons make them perfect for any seeking a more shiveringly totemic look as they hunt.” Alter your weapon's appearance by using this complete set of Crowborne Hunter Outfit styles.</i></p> 
<p>The Crowborne Hunter Arms Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms during the Witches Festival event. Matching armor pages will have a small chance to drop from Plunder Skulls. Bound versions of the armor pages can be purchased from the Impresario for 5 Event Tickets each during the event.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Wardrobe</h2> 
<p><b>Costumes</b></p> 
<p><b>High Rock Pioneer Outfit </b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/3dabf656392ab549dffd9bd185be4bc2.jpg" />
<p><i>"Even a rugged pioneer of the borderlands can show some distinctive Breton style," says Lady Eloisse of House Manteau. "Our traditional linen shirt is suitable for any occasion!" </i></p> 
<p>The High Rock Pioneer Outfit will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 2 to October 5, 2023, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Jarl's Deluxe Moot Regalia</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/39a6e4cef72d344879822dc89ef2cb71.jpg" />
<p><i>"Someday East and West Skyrim will be reunited and the Jarls will gather in a Moot to select a new High King," says Jork of Windhelm. "But that day may be a long time coming, so you might as well wear this noble outfit now!"</i></p> 
<p>The Jarl's Deluxe Moot Regalia will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 16 to October 19, 2023, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Cyrod Patrician Formal Gown</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/b148c330c4953eb75bf8e67a37e45c86.jpg" />
<p><i>You'll look every inch the aristocrat in this formal wrap gown from Diocletia of Skingrad, paired with a splendid gorget of hammered gold dripping with Imperial diamonds. Get haughty!</i></p> 
<p>The Cyrod Patrician Formal Gown will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 19 to October 26, 2023, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Grisly Mummy Wrap</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/686fb1a3ee99dba6be7f4ec5f8880707.jpg" />
<p><i>Only you know what lies beneath your enshrouding bandages. Whether hero or horror, your presence imparts an unforgettable chilling dread.</i></p> 
<p>The Grisly Mummy Wrap costume will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 30 to November 2, 2023, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Crate</h2> 
<p><b>Reaper's Harvest Crate</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/d786dbaadff9b092862e8a10484e5505.jpg" />
<p><i>A mystery collection of Grim Reaper-related items!</i></p> 
<p>Reaper's Harvest Crate will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 19 to November 2, 2023, at 10AM EDT.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<h2>Events </h2> 
<p><b>Currency</b></p> 
<p><b>Event Tickets</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/74f679e610302be57199309573dd3a29.jpg" />
<p><i>A ticket used to purchase rare goods from The Impresario, Event Merchant. Curious as to what goods? Well, chat with her to see what she has to offer!</i></p> 
<p>Single Event Tickets will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time during the Secrets of the Telvanni and the Witches Festival. Stay tuned for event details!</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<h2>Furniture </h2> 
<p><b>Furnishing Pack: Sinister Hollowjack Items</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/d43e1e7b9f45ae40dc3ff662fc92880e.jpg" />
<p><i>Lanterns lure and pumpkins trip</i></p> 
<p><i>Webs ensnare and grave hands grip</i></p> 
<p><i>Crows will mock as wraith-scythes hack</i></p> 
<p><i>All in thrall to Hollowjack!</i></p> 
<p>The Furnishing Pack: Sinister Hollowjack Items will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 2 at 10AM EDT to November 6, 2023, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Furnishing Pack: Necrom Garden</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/ef21f4f36e1b72ce289f640844eea1d3.jpg" />
<p><i>When you need a break from the rigors of research or strenuous adventures, enjoy a quiet Necrom-themed nook in your home. Including a gazebo, statuary, fungi, and more, this pack may inspire your inner mycoturge into a great feat of gardening.</i></p> 
<p>The Furnishing Pack: Necrom Garden will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 6 to October 20, 2023, at 10AM EDT.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Statue, The Thirty-Fourth Sermon</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/35169b1e94ba70de726b57cf5b6aea93.jpg" />
<p><i>"When GULGA MOR JIL saw his mother-father, he asked why he should have to die and return to oblivion. Vivec told the eighth monster that to be otherwise was to betray his nature."—The Thirty-Six Lessons of Vivec, Sermon Thirty-Four</i></p> 
<p>The Statue, The Thirty-Fourth Sermon will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 6 to October 20, 2023, at 10AM EDT.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Target Harrowing Reaper, Trial</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/0c1f840b3475ba2a9fc86d912b27d1ff.jpg" />
<p><i>This is a large house item. This may be attacked and, when destroyed, will regenerate. This creature is equivalent to a veteran trial boss. Its abilities include granting a resource-restoring synergy opportunity, performance buffs, and self debuffs.</i></p> 
<p>The Target Harrowing Reaper, Trial will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 6 to October 20, 2023, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Music Box, The Shadows Stir</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/a7dbf0deddc63c654ded337ccbdbf5f1.jpg" />
<p><i>When activated, plays a music box arrangement of the haunting "The Shadows Stir" composition.</i></p> 
<p>The Music Box, The Shadows Stir will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 12 to October 19, 2023, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Music Box, Witchmother's Bubbling Brew</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/3e55454dfe46377a05fddb1bec0eab96.jpg" />
<p><i>"Pulp of pumpkin, dash of guts. Prep your cauldron, make your cuts. Capture death 'cause it's your due. Stir it all and then you're through." When activated, plays a music box arrangement of the macabre "Witchmother's Bubbling Brew" composition. </i></p> 
<p>The Music Box, Witchmother's Bubbling Brew will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms during the Witches Festival event.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Furnishing Pack: Trappings of Mephala Worship</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/9fbf7f46c912a4b44d4f424506787a4f.jpg" />
<p><i>With these furnishings, some from Mephala cultists, some that replicate the bizarre environment of the Spiral Skein, you can adopt the ambience of the realm of the Webspinner.</i></p> 
<p>The Furnishing Pack: Trappings of Mephala Worship will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 26 at 10AM EDT to November 9, 2023, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Furnishing Pack: Witches' Coven</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/1ff738c3e815474a70fc2a3b95cbc148.jpg" />
<p><i>Bring the moody atmosphere of Hag Fen to your home with these tools and trappings of the witch's trade. Whether brewing potent poisons or cooking cauldrons of questionable stew, craft in true coven style with the included alchemy and provisioning stations!</i></p> 
<p>The Furnishing Pack: Witches' Coven will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms during the Witches Festival event. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Houses</h2> 
<p><b>Wraithhome</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/ebbd5b7ba892fd21150868850622c0ec.jpg" />
<p><i>With its pillars of skulls, stained glass, and ghostly portals, this abode can accommodate even the most tormented soul. Take advantage of its open layout to set up large-scale rituals, and use its vaults and lofty balconies for vile experiments.</i></p> 
<p>Wraithhome will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 12 to October 26, 2023, at 10AM EDT. Furnished and unfurnished versions will be available.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Shadow Queen's Labyrinth</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/76b2bf32530402812a7b5924a14086bc.jpg" />
<p><i>A winding maze dominates the grounds of this twilight-enshrouded estate, creating endless opportunities to perplex visitors. The visceral awe evoked by Nocturnal's Evergloam skies provides an exquisite contrast to the spacious, Summerset-inspired home.</i></p> 
<p>Shadow Queen's Labyrinth will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 26 at 10AM EDT to November 9, 2023, at 10AM EST. Furnished and unfurnished versions will be available.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Exorcised Coven Cottage</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/66167430dc9985d1e338cb6acd62c670.jpg" />
<p><i>Pay no attention to the rumors: this witches hut on the edge of Hag Fen in Glenumbra is guaranteed NOT to be haunted by the dead, the undead, or restless spirits of any kind. It does come with tumbledown walls to keep the crocodiles and wolves out. Spooky!</i></p> 
<p>Exorcised Coven Cottage will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms during the Witches Festival event. Furnished and unfurnished versions will be available.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Houseguests</h2> 
<p><b>Heiruna</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/1b7b3de277d242bdacf5d1dfc4f1be7a.jpg" />
<p><i>Oh, the ignominy of being an agent of justice trapped inside a small floating doll! Now Heiruna intends to plot vengeance—in your retreat. After adding Heiruna to your home, you can set her on a path, plus you and your visitors can speak with her.</i></p> 
<p>Heiruna will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 12 to October 26, 2023, at 10AM EDT.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Squire Caw</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/27f6d537a7a8a93f93b1c5a10aab689b.jpg" />
<p><i>Is your home bedecked in shiny treasures? Did you leave carrion out in the sun? Regardless, Blackfeather Court's most nettlesome squire noticed! After adding Squire Caw to your home, you can set him on a path, plus you and your visitors can speak with him.</i></p> 
<p>Squire Caw will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 26 at 10AM EDT to November 9, 2023, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Mounts</h2> 
<p><b>Great Dark Ram</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/03a63b1be306b89d15c6cbf8f93a8b42.jpg" />
<p><i>"The mythic texts of discredited scholars are right, the Great Dark Ram lives! Hircine appears in this form only during Rain's Hand in the Great Forest. Soon, there will be the trials of virility. I hope my strength endures."—Lost Journal of Bekelva</i></p> 
<p>The Great Dark Ram mount will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 5 to October 16, 2023, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Zombie Horse</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/767da834a0078403fd6bb3e9c824f37d.jpg" />
<p><i>Mannimarco's Order of the Black Worm must be responsible for the re-animated Zombie Horse, as it was first seen in Cyrodiil as a Worm Anchorite's mount.</i></p> 
<p>The Zombie Horse mount will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 12 to October 19, 2023, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Hollowjack Indrik</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/6ae905fc2b3fc6b67d3ff477ea38e33c.jpg" />
<p><i>"Twisted twigs, a scent of death, a dance amid the briars. A dash of howls and drip of gore starts sinister fires. Stir round with haunted bone, then call me with your screams. If I approve, a mount you gain to torment your foes' dreams."—Lord Hollowjack</i></p> <p>The Hollowjack Indrik mount will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 26 to November 2, 2023, at 10AM EDT. </p> <p><i> </i></p> <h2>Pets</h2> <p><b>Black Cat</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/45c6e54dffbf3c11650a33026bfadd18.jpg" />
<p><i>This black cat knows things you cannot know, and sees things you cannot see. But that is the nature of all black cats, is it not?</i></p> 
<p>The Black Cat pet will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 2 to October 9, 2023, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Dire Pony</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/fccc5921188fb97a6ebb51e84ad94eab.jpg" />
<p><i>When you always wanted a pony as a child and your parents wouldn't let you have one so you grew up bitter and tormented and became a dark cultist but now you can finally afford a pony.</i></p> 
<p>The Dire Pony pet will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 5 to October 16, 2023, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Amber Ash Hopper</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/f6f44802b36a042a2415fe4ec478309d.jpg" />
<p><i>Native to the upper Ashlands and the slopes of Red Mountain, the perky Amber Ash Hopper is a favorite pet of Dunmer expatriates, as it's relatively low maintenance (it digs its own hole in the ground), and it reminds the Dark Elves of home.</i></p> 
<p>The Amber Ash Hopper pet will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 16 to October 23, 2023, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Skeletal Senche-Leopard</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/f14739616aabafd9dae5f72da2392891.jpg" />
<p><i>Is Necromancy always wrong? Not even death can stop this loyal senche-leopard from stalking to adventure at your side!</i></p> 
<p>The Skeletal Senche-Leopard pet will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 19 to October 23, 2023, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Skeletal Pack Wolf</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/337427490b4fe382f1d4ea80457d4f93.jpg" />
<p><i>When the Two Moons are full, the undead wolf pack rises from the grave, point their canine craniums at the sky, and try to howl—but the only sound is a dismal rattling in their bony throats.</i></p> 
<p>The Skeletal Pack Wolf pet will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 19 to October 23, 2023, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Rihad Coffee Scorpion</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/f08191df1d9754a82371caf3f71dd61c.jpg" />
<p><i>The Coffee Scorpion gets its name from the way they like their kaveh in Rihad: strong, dark, and sweet. (Well, I guess two out of three isn't bad.)</i></p> 
<p>The Rihad Coffee Scorpion pet will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 23 to October 26, 2023, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Witch's Infernal Familiar</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/7044b24ec52d510e7146ccf0e087bab2.jpg" />
<p><i>Equipped with a hat, this black cat makes its way in the world at your side, leaving little fiery pawprints behind as it goes.</i></p> 
<p>The Witch's Infernal Familiar pet will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 23 to October 30, 2023, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Volkihar Death Hound</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/19e12bb8678c9c6241f128fdf3893cf0.jpg" />
<p><i>“Rarely do these inky black death hounds venture beyond Castle Volkihar—most serve their master's purpose at home better than abroad. The ones wandering after folk are probably some form of spy for the Volkihar vampires.”—Nalana, Advisor to House Tamrith</i></p> 
<p>The Volkihar Death Hound pet will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 30 to November 2, 2023, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Personalities</h2> 
<p><b>Zombie</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/099a9c1af51eda3dcff341fc9e846def.jpg" />
<p><i>Graargh URR agg rhhh HAAAGH gug gug gug. RrrrrRRrrrrawww! GHORF blafffft urgl! Sneg?</i></p> 
<p>The Zombie personality will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 12 to October 19, 2023, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<p> </p> 
<h2>Polymorphs</h2> 
<p><b>Werewolf Lord</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/49fe24cf3c06ae1c0bd781c51957d5f6.jpg" />
<p><i>Wear Hircine's Gift with pride as the leader of the lycanthrope pack with the Werewolf Lord polymorph. Time to howl!</i></p> 
<p>The Werewolf Lord polymorph will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 5 to October 12, 2023, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Pumpkin Spectre</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/c5fbad4ebd32d1e52c853ed252d6f362.jpg" />
<p><i>A Pumpkin Spectre is like a horrific figure from a skooma-induced nightmare! And with this costume, the wearer can take on the semblance of these dread monsters.</i></p> 
<p>The Pumpkin Spectre polymorph will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from October 23 to October 30, 2023, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p>Haunted homesteads, accursed arms, and terrifying beasts both big and small await you in the Crown Store this month. Don't forget, before you can acquire any of these creepy collectibles, you'll need to visit the <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/buycrowns">Buy Crowns page</a> to stock up on crowns. Are you planning to spook friends and foes alike with any of the above items this October? Let us know via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">Twitter</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/ElderScrollsOnline">Facebook</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Crown Store</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/b6bfa865294a6b4077661f61482968f5.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ESO Live: September 29 @4PM EDT—Exploring the Secrets of the Telvanni]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/64789</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/64789</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Join us this Friday as we delve into the Secrets of the Telvanni event and complete some daily quests!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/61f0175038087ebd377d3ccb429c605e.jpg" /><p><i>Join us this Friday as we delve into the Secrets of the Telvanni event and complete some daily quests! </i></p> 
<p>Tune in to <a href="https://www.twitch.tv/bethesda">Twitch.tv/Bethesda</a> this Friday, September 29 at 4PM EDT as Senior Community Managers Gina Bruno and Amy Schlueter will be joined by Stream Team member <a href="https://www.twitch.tv/neliserendipity" target="_blank">NeliSerendipity</a> to delve back into the <i>Necrom</i> Chapter and participate in the Secrets of the Telvanni in-game event. </p> 
<p>Together, they'll complete the new event-specific daily quest and do their part to help the community unlock its unique rewards. Which sister will they support during the livestream? You can help them decide by sharing whether you're #TeamYensa or #TeamTralise via a Twitch poll they'll post towards the end of the show!</p> 
<p>Twitch Drops will be enabled for those watching (<a href="https://help.elderscrollsonline.com/#en/answer/41809" target="_blank">link your <i>ESO</i> and Twitch accounts here</a>), so be sure to join us on <a href="https://www.twitch.tv/Bethesda">Twitch.tv/Bethesda</a> this Friday, September 29 at 4PM EDT as the team returns to the Telvanni Peninsula and Apocrypha. See you there!</p> 
<p><i>ESO Live is your official Elder Scrolls Online stream, hosted on Twitch.tv/Bethesda by ESO's Community Team.</i></p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>ESO Live</category>
            <category>Community</category>
            <category>Necrom</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/61f0175038087ebd377d3ccb429c605e.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Begin Your Necrom Adventure & Save Up To 50% on the New Chapter During the Secrets of the Telvanni Sale]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/64783</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/64783</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[You can save up to 50% on the Necrom Chapter and explore both the Telvanni Peninsula and Apocrypha during this special event sale.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/ff531054ba1001d150ef08b6b760f359.jpg" /><p><i>You can save up to 50% on the Necrom Chapter and explore both the Telvanni Peninsula and Apocrypha during this special event sale.</i></p><p>The Secrets of the Telvanni Sale is now live on all platforms, including Xbox (Xbox One, Xbox Series X|S), PlayStation (PlayStation 4, PlayStation 5), and PC/Mac (<i>Elder Scrolls Online</i> Store, Steam, Epic Games Store). During the sale period, you can save up to 50% on <i>The Elder Scrolls Online: Necrom</i> as well as up to 70% on <i>The Elder Scrolls Online: Standard Edition</i>. Note that on Xbox and PlayStation consoles, this discount is available only for <i>Necrom Deluxe Editions</i>.</p><p>Want to take advantage of these great deals? Visit our <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/joinus">Buy Now page</a> and select your edition!</p> <p>If you're new to <i>ESO</i>, the <i>Necrom</i> <i>Collection</i> (Deluxe Edition and Standard) includes the <i>ESO</i> base game, <i>Necrom</i> Chapter, and ALL previous Chapters. However, if you're a seasoned Tamrielic adventurer, you might prefer the <i>Necrom</i> <i>Upgrade</i> (Collector's Edition and Standard), which grants access to the new Chapter content (including zones, Arcanist class, and storyline).</p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/ba48125ad19837108d994758ba406278.png" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Explore ESO's Latest Chapter</i></p> <p>These sale prices are available for a limited time only and may end on different dates depending on your platform and territory. Check your preferred retailer to confirm.</p> <p><b>Elder Scrolls Online Store</b></p> <ul><li><i>Standard Edition</i>—September 28-October 10</li><li><i>Necrom</i>—September 28-October 10</li></ul> <p><b>Steam Store</b></p> <ul><li><i>Standard Edition</i>—September 28-October 10</li><li><i>Necrom</i>—September 28-October 10</li></ul><p><b>Epic Games Store</b></p><ul><li><i>Standard Edition</i>—September 28-October 10</li><li><i>Necrom</i>—September 28-October 10</li></ul> <p><b>Xbox </b>(<i>Necrom Deluxe Edition</i> only)</p> <ul><li><i>Standard Edition</i>—September 27-October 11</li><li><i>Necrom Deluxe Edition</i>—September 27-October 11 </li></ul> <p><b>PlayStation </b>(<i>Necrom Deluxe Edition</i> only)</p> <ul><li><i>Standard Edition</i>—September 27-October 11 </li><li><i>Necrom Deluxe Edition</i>—September 27-October 11 </li></ul> <h2>Uncover the Secrets of the Telvanni</h2> <p>Running alongside this sale is the Secrets of the Telvanni in-game event, giving you and your fellow adventurers a chance to earn bonus rewards while completing daily quests in the Telvanni Peninsula and Apocrypha. These bonus rewards include unique collectibles and an in-game house. </p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/05a8700ac7da03df37efc97293803ff8.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center"><i>Delve into Apocrypha during the Secrets of the Telvanni </i></p><p>Be sure to check out the event <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/64773">announcement article</a> for details on how you can participate and visit <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/secretsofthetelvanni;">the official event page</a> regularly to see which in-game rewards have been unlocked for you and your fellow <i>Necrom</i> players. Don't forget, you need access to the <i>Necrom</i> Chapter to participate—don't miss out. </p> <p>Are you excited to save big on <i>ESO</i>'s latest Chapter and unlock bonus rewards simply by questing within the Telvanni Peninsula and Apocrypha? If you've been waiting, now is the perfect time to begin your <i>Shadow Over Morrowind</i> adventure—we'll see you in Tamriel! </p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Sales</category>
            <category>Necrom</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/ff531054ba1001d150ef08b6b760f359.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Daily Login Rewards–October 2023]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/64777</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/64777</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[See what goodies you can claim simply by logging in to ESO during the month of October 2023.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/d2d3225127ae571fb135794c229b528c.jpg" /><p><i>See what goodies you can claim simply by logging in to ESO during the month of October 2023.</i></p> 
<p>If you're planning to spend some time in Tamriel this October, there's 31 great reasons why you should log in to <i>The Elder Scrolls Online</i>. You can see just some of the daily rewards you can claim next month below, but if you'd like to find out more about Daily Login Rewards in general, <a href="https://help.bethesda.net/#en/answer/41950">check out this help article</a>. </p> 
<p><b>Grand Gold Coast Experience Scroll ×2—Day 7</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/06/1f7bf97587039a52547d3df74a2632bc.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Level up quick!</i></p> 
<p>Get ready to dive into the Endless Archive by leveling up fast with two EXP Scrolls, each granting a 150% boost to experience gains.</p> 
<p><b>Seals of Endeavor ×250—Day 14</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/1cfb418981bec3aee26d7c3a05265b75.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Claim 250 of these on day 14!</i></p> 
<p>Got your eye on any Crown Crate items? In its first appearance for the Daily Rewards system, Seals of Endeavor were previously earned only by completing daily and weekly Endeavors. You can learn more about <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/59925">Seals of Endeavor in this blog</a>. </p> 
<p><b>Ash Hopper Chomp Emote—Day 21</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/1ca7df6e7625fb74256b02576b86cdec.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>A Green Pact-approved meal</i></p> 
<p>Ash hoppers are typically native to Vvardenfell (but certainly found in other equally inhospitable locations), so it is perhaps unsurprising that the Dark Elves have incorporated these creatures into their <i>already</i> <i>formidable</i> local cuisine. This emote proves once more that there's no accounting for taste.</p> 
<p>These are just some of the rewards you can claim during October, so be sure to log in to the game on the first day of the month to see the complete list. You can find it within the Daily Rewards section of the in-game Crown Store. Do any of these items tickle your fancy? Will you be taking a big bite out of some giant insect legs? Let us know via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">Twitter</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/ElderScrollsOnline">Facebook</a>! </p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Daily Rewards</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/d2d3225127ae571fb135794c229b528c.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Japanese Localization Arrives on Consoles with ESO's Update 40]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/64685</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/64685</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[ESO's console players will be able to enjoy Japanese localization with the Update 40 base-game patch!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/51ab9eb9f1b49a864a47722743e809b8.jpg" /><p><i>ESO's console players will be able to enjoy Japanese localization with the Update 40 base-game patch! </i></p> 
<p>We are very excited to share that <i>The Elder Scrolls Online</i> will launch fully localized in Japanese for Xbox One, Xbox Series X|S, PlayStation 4, and PlayStation 5 consoles with the release of Update 40 on November 14, 2023 (November 15 local Tokyo time). </p> 
<p>During last night's <a href="https://news.xbox.com/en-us/2023/09/19/xbox-digital-broadcast-tokyo-game-show-how-to-watch/">Xbox Digital Broadcast</a> from the Tokyo Game Show, Creative Director Rich Lambert thanked the Japanese community and highlighted the game's most recent Chapter, <i>The Elder Scrolls Online: Necrom</i>, which players will be able to play translated into Japanese this November. </p> 
<p>As shared during the recent preview livestream, the Update 40 base-game patch arrives November 14 (November 15 local Tokyo time) on console and includes the new <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/64687">Endless Archive PvE activity</a> and a host of <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/64689">quality-of-life additions and fixes</a>. As a base-game update, Update 40 is free for all existing <i>ESO</i> players, with no additional purchases required. </p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Update 40</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/51ab9eb9f1b49a864a47722743e809b8.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Defend the Warrior Poet with Items from the New Buoyant Armiger Crown Crates]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/64619</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/64619</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Stand sentinel over the Tribunal Temple and Lord Vivec with the items and collectibles found within the new Buoyant Armiger Crown Crates.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/6e5c77410c51ee82b600b929b34b7ba4.jpg" /><p><i>Stand sentinel over the Tribunal Temple and Lord Vivec with the items and collectibles found within the new Buoyant Armiger Crown Crates.</i></p> 
<p>***</p> 
<p><i>“Poetry is the sharpest blade a warrior can wield. Do you have the wherewithal to stand your ground, as does a proud kwama queen? Or do you offer your throat as the gentle guar? Take up the glassine armor of the Buoyant Armiger in service to Lord Vivec!</i></p> 
<p><i>And in return for your service and artistry? Ride forth with treasures from the Telvanni Peninsula. Arm yourself with flair and panache, or seek the best the mycoturges have to offer. This is your moment, Armiger. In Vehk's name!”</i></p> 
<p>*** </p> 
<p>The new Buoyant Armiger Crown Crates arrive in the Crown Store this Thursday, September 21 at 10AM EDT. When claiming one of these new crates, Vivec's finest have a chance to acquire a selection of new and returning collectibles and items, fit for Vehk himself. </p> 
<p>These goods include unique mounts, pets, furnishings, and much more. You can see just some of the items available within Buoyant Armiger Crown Crates below. </p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/223ffeb70686bdcc71b0062150d7cb42.jpg" />
<img src="https://esossl-a.akamaihd.net/uploads/Community/Article/headers/Costumes_NecromEveningAttire2.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Necrom Armiger body markings &amp; Necrom Evening Attire costume</i></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/b023c5e2e4bd60ec86ed61617272d4bd.jpg" />
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/ff56803f84c0da246ae89208ddeb8157.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Armiger Axing customized action &amp; Chaotic Creatia Cub pet</i></p> 
<p>Should Vivec's own fortune find you when opening a Buoyant Armiger crate, you might even unlock one of the below extremely rare Radiant Apex mounts. </p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/1f5369f3b06b483993339db80cf19510.jpg" />
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/0da955a207790553cacd704f7be06d18.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Necrom Armiger Senche &amp; Harrowstorm Destrier mounts</i></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/b7d8684e2bb5a5aa03c04d76185b201f.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Spellscar Quasigriff mount</i></p> 
<p>Buoyant Armiger Crown Crates will be available in one-, four-, and 15-crate bundles in addition to two unique bundles that include Spellscar items. </p> 
<ul><li>The Spellscar's Kiss Crate Bundle</li><ul><li>Including 25 Buoyant Armiger crates and the Spellscar Sheathe skin</li></ul><li>The Spellscar's Hiss Crate Bundle</li><ul><li>Including five Buoyant Armiger crates and the Spellscar Salamander pet </li></ul></ul>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/343b60dc6af3f130d5b6e3b6a1a59fab.jpg" />
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/d3d616a141dc8394310e29496c39de95.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>The Spellscar's Kiss and Spellscar's Hiss bundles</i></p> 
<p>Upon purchase of either one of these special bundles, the skin or pet will be unlocked automatically and added to your collectibles. These bundles can be purchased only once each. </p> 
<p>Of course, the above are just some of the blessings Vivec can bestow upon his most-trusted guardians. If you wish to see the full list of items you have a chance to receive when opening a Buoyant Armiger Crown Crate, check out <a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/643357/official-discussion-thread-for-buoyant-armiger-crown-crates" target="_blank" style="">this thread on our official forums</a>. </p> 
<p>Be warned, when the new crates go live, the currently available <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/crownstore/category/38">Unfeathered Crown Crates</a> will be removed from the Crown Store in turn, so don't forget to pick them up while they're still available! </p> 
<p>Buoyant Armiger Crown Crates arrive this Thursday, September 21 at 10AM EDT, and can be acquired from the Crown Crate section of the in-game Crown Store. Are you ready and willing to stand sentinel and protect the Warrior Poet himself? Let us know if you're excited to become one of Vivec's chosen via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">Twitter</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Crown Store</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/6e5c77410c51ee82b600b929b34b7ba4.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Endless Archive & Update 40 Now Available on the PC/Mac Public Test Server!]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/64751</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/64751</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Join us on the Public Test Server to try out the new Endless Archive PvE activity and Update 40 base-game patch!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/a85f011cf8fca96a3dd263db0a34d73c.jpg" /><p><i>Join us on the Public Test Server to try out the new Endless Archive PvE activity and Update 40 base-game patch!</i></p> 
<p>The Update 40 base-game patch is now live on the Public Test Server (PTS) and is accessible via the PC/Mac ESO launcher. This base-game update, free to all players, includes the <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/64689">Endless Archive PvE activity</a>. Want to help us test Update 40 and this new dungeon-like challenge? Log in to the PTS!</p> 
<p>To access the PTS, open the Settings menu located within the PC/Mac ESO launcher and click on the “Show Public Test Environment.” Once you've downloaded everything, you'll be able to access the testing server. While you're exploring the PTS, don't forget to leave feedback and report any bugs you come across by typing “/feedback” or “/bug” through the in-game chat.</p> 
<p>If you want to learn more about the new challenges that await you in within the infinite halls of the Endless Archive or anything else arriving with the Update 40 patch, be sure to check out our recent preview <a href="https://www.twitch.tv/videos/1925408444">livestream</a> and <a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/643287/pts-patch-notes-v9-2-0" target="_blank">PTS Patch Notes</a> on the <i>ESO</i> forums.</p> 
<p>Are you ready to take your first steps into the Endless Archive? Let us know via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">Twitter</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, or <a href="https://www.facebook.com/ElderScrollsOnline">Facebook</a>!</p> 
<p><i>Update 40 base-game patch, including the Endless Archive, arrives on October 30 for PC/Mac and November 14 for Xbox and PlayStation consoles. </i></p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Community</category>
            <category>Update 40</category>
            <category>Endless Archive</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/a85f011cf8fca96a3dd263db0a34d73c.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Don't Miss the Endless Archive & Update 40 Preview Livestream]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/64679</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/64679</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Tune in to Twitch.tv/Bethesda this Thursday as we unveil the new Endless Archive and Update 40 in a special livestream preview show.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/c8b8140f7b9eb2781b4630adc616a1ec.jpg" /><p><i>Tune in to Twitch.tv/Bethesda this Thursday as we unveil the new Endless Archive and Update 40 in a special livestream preview show. </i></p> 
<p>Join us this Thursday, September 14 at 3PM EDT, on <a href="https://www.twitch.tv/bethesda">Twitch.tv/Bethesda</a> as we reveal the all-new Endless Archive and Update 40 base-game patch. Watch as Senior Community Manager Gina Bruno is joined by Creative Director Rich Lambert, Lead Encounter Designer Mike Finnigan, and Associate Encounter Designer Lauren Kaiser to dive deep into this exciting new in-game activity with live gameplay. </p> 
<p>Watch the show with a <a href="https://help.elderscrollsonline.com/app/answers/detail/a_id/41809/">linked<i> ESO</i> and Twitch account</a> and you'll also earn the Tentacular Tome emote and an Ouroboros Crown Crate as Twitch Drops rewards. </p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/f0e09a027a7f96a995a7f1660cdbe707.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Tentacular Tome emote</i></p> 
<p>Stick around after the show as <i>ESO </i>Stream Team member <a href="https://www.twitch.tv/deltiasgaming">Deltias</a> recaps all the latest reveals and interviews Lead Encounter Designer Mike Finnigan on <a href="https://www.twitch.tv/Deltiasgaming">Twitch.tv/Deltiasgaming</a>. </p> 
<h2>Global ESO Livestreams</h2> 
<p>Both during and following the preview, there'll also be a series of livestreams hosted by members of the global <i>ESO </i>Community Team and special friends. Check out the full schedule below!</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>New Feature &amp; Update Preview: Endless Archive (FR) </b></p> 
<p>Join French Community Manager Geoffrey as he translates and comments the Endless Archive preview show live on Twitch.tv/Bethesda_FR! </p> 
<p><b>When:</b> Thursday, September 14 at 3PM EDT/9PM CEST</p> 
<p><b>Where:</b> <a href="https://www.twitch.tv/bethesda_FR">Twitch.tv/Bethesda_FR</a></p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Luisanc Live Reacts to Preview Stream (ES-Mx)</b></p> 
<p>Stream Team member Luisanc reacts live to the preview show and hunts down Tamriel's monsters. Join him!</p> 
<p><b>When:</b> Thursday, September 14 at 3PM EDT/9PM CEST</p> 
<p><b>Where:</b> <a href="https://www.twitch.tv/luisanc">Twitch.tv/luisanc</a></p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>ESO: Q4 &amp; Endless Archive Preview (PL)</b></p> 
<p>Polish Community Manager Łukasz hosts the preview show live and discusses it with members of the <i>ESO </i>Stream Team. </p> 
<p><b>When:</b> Thursday, September 14 at 3PM EDT/9PM CEST</p> 
<p><b>Where:</b> <a href="https://www.twitch.tv/bethesda_PL">Twitch.tv/Bethesda_PL</a></p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Eurogamer Spain &amp; Community Discuss the Latest ESO News (ES)</b></p> 
<p>Eurogamer Spain and well-known community guests discuss the latest news and reveals concerning what to expect from <i>ESO</i> in the following months. </p> 
<p><b>When:</b> Friday, September 15 at 3PM EDT/9PM CEST</p> 
<p><b>Where:</b> <a href="https://www.twitch.tv/eurogamer_es">Twitch.tv/Eurogamer_ES</a></p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Mestre Frooke Dives Deep into ESO's Q4 and the Latest Reveals (PT-BR) </b></p> 
<p><i>ESO</i> fan and livestreamer Mestre Frooke discusses the latest reveals with guests and what to expect in Q4.</p> 
<p><b>When:</b> Sunday, September 17 at 8PM BRT/7PM EDT/1AM CEST </p> 
<p><b>Where:</b> <a href="https://www.twitch.tv/mestrefrooke">Twitch.tv/mestrefrooke</a></p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Endless Archive &amp; Update 40 Discussion (EN)</b></p> 
<p>UK Community Manager Ophelia and special guests discuss the latest Update 40 reveals and what to expect from the rest of 2023. </p> 
<p><b>When:</b> Tuesday, September 19 at 9AM EDT/2PM BST</p> 
<p><b>Where:</b> <a href="https://www.twitch.tv/bethesda">Twitch.tv/Bethesda</a></p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>The Elder Scrolls Online: What to Expect from the Endless Archive &amp; Update 40 (DE)</b></p> 
<p>German Senior Community Manager Kai Schober and special guests (including Lead Encounter Designer Mike Finnigan*) talk about what you can expect in Q4.</p> 
<p><b>When:</b> Tuesday, September 19 at 1PM EDT/7PM CEST</p> 
<p><b>Where:</b> <a href="https://www.twitch.tv/bethesda_DE">Twitch.tv/Bethesda_DE</a></p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>ESO Italia Delves into the Latest ESO News (IT)</b></p> 
<p><i>ESO </i>Italia and Community Manager Stefania discuss the latest reveals and what to expect from Q4. </p> 
<p><b>When:</b> Monday, September 25 at 3PM EDT/9PM CEST</p> 
<p><b>Where:</b> <a href="https://www.twitch.tv/arvendirita">Twitch.tv/Arvendirita</a></p><p><br></p> 
<p>The New Feature &amp; Update Preview: Endless Archive livestream kicks off this Thursday, September 14 at 3PM EDT, on <a href="https://www.twitch.tv/bethesda">Twitch.tv/Bethesda</a>. Don't forget to <a href="https://help.elderscrollsonline.com/app/answers/detail/a_id/41809/">link those accounts</a> and ensure you claim the new emote while watching—we'll see you there! </p> 
<p><i>*Editor's Note: What a busy guy! </i></p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Previews</category>
            <category>Update 40</category>
            <category>Endless Archive</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/c8b8140f7b9eb2781b4630adc616a1ec.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Update 39 Base-Game Patch Now Live on All Platforms]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/64551</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/64551</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Discover the host of additions and improvements arriving with the free Update 39 base-game patch.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/08/2e966846125f5b8145838f4247202990.jpg" /><p><i>Discover the host of additions and improvements arriving with the free Update 39 base-game patch. </i></p> <p>The Update 39 base-game patch is now live PC/Mac, Xbox One, Xbox Series X|S, PlayStation 4, and PlayStation 5, and introduces a series of long-awaited improvements and additions to <i>The Elder Scrolls Online</i>, completely free of charge for all existing <i>ESO</i> players.<br></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/08/2aae9b31906a3c66e2128b4d1cf5b7d1.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Update 39 Base Game Improvements</i></p> 
<p>As a base-game patch, Update 39 includes a wide array of bug fixes, but also features a series of long-awaited improvements to your in-game experience. </p> 
<p><b>Quest &amp; Content Improvements for New Players</b></p> 
<p>If you're a new player feeling overwhelmed when first entering Tamriel, you can enjoy a series of changes that <b>reduce the volume and frequency of quests </b>offered to your low-level characters. This includes quests from NPCs for the main story, Fighters Guild, Mages Guild, Battlegrounds, Undaunted, and others. Instead, these quests are now delivered more gradually as you level up, helping your journal stay in a manageable state for longer!</p> 
<p>Tamriel's navigator NPCs that can transport your characters between destinations have also received some improvements with this update. Now, these navigators <b>indicate whether they can transport you to a location for one of your tracked quests</b> (active or inactive.) When exploring, you now see the “door” pin above relevant navigator NPCs, indicating that they can help you in your journey. In addition, appropriate dialog lines with those same NPCs have similar pins, ensuring you make the right choice and go where you need to go—happy travels! </p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/08/71d1ea150e994d1d9a33e1959bbe5942.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Taking your first steps into Tamriel is daunting</i></p> 
<p><b>Inventory Management Improvements</b></p> 
<p>If you're struggling with an overburdened Inventory, Update 39 also includes changes to key item types to help improve management and reduce clutter. Some (but not all) similar Crown Store items that came from separate sources (such as Tri-Restoration Potions) can now all be <b>stacked together using the “Stack All Items” option</b>. Also, this patch adds <b>better communication regarding which items in your Inventory can or cannot be sold</b>, helping you identify and clear out unwanted items and make a little gold in the process!</p> 
<p><b>PvP Additions &amp; New Rewards </b></p> 
<p>This update adds new rewards for Tamriel's PvP victors in the form of <b>three new monster mask sets</b>: Jerall Mountains Warchief, Nibenay Bay Battlereeve, and Colovian Highlands General. Each grants unique and powerful boons, and you can trade Alliance Points for these new masks with Cyrodiil Elite Gear Vendors within the Eastern Elsweyr Gate, Southern High Rock Gate, and Northern Morrowind Gate. </p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/07/02adb5389ad204fbd8e6c9ce6240f7d4.png" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Chase down new PvP rewards</i></p> 
<p>In addition, you can now claim <b>new Unfeathered Battle Body and Face Markings</b> from Gladiator's Rucksacks (earned by completing Cyrodiil Conquest Mission Board daily quests), and the Imperial City's hapless <b>Treasure Scamps now</b> <b>drop even better loot </b>when hunted down. In particular, Cunning Scamps drop more Tel Var Stones and Trove Scamps drop tradable pieces of Imperial City gear sets. </p> 
<p>Finally, while battling in Cyrodiil, the Imperial City, and Battlegrounds, you can now see <b>new death notifications</b> that help you plan your next move (or avoid that incoming zerg!).</p> 
<p><b>Home Editor Improvements</b></p> 
<p>With Update 39, this patch gives you the ability to <b>place a furnishing directly from your Inventory or Collectibles UI </b>while in your home. You can now find a “Place” option when viewing the specific furnishings. In addition, you can <b>preview Crown Store furnishings</b> in your home before you buy, helping you determine how a new item might look when placed. </p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/08/1c12c700d99b7f15c2d3bffeba283673.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Place furnishings from Inventory and Collectibles</i></p> 
<p>Of course, these are just some of the changes and additions that arrive with Update 39. To see a complete list of everything this new base-game patch introduces to <i>ESO</i>, visit our <a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/641025/pc-mac-patch-notes-v9-1-5-update-39" target="_blank">Patch Notes forum</a>.</p><br><h2>Getting Started in Update 39</h2><p>As a base-game update, your version of <i>ESO</i> automatically updates on PC/Mac via the <i>ESO </i>Launcher. Note that to run <i>ESO</i> on PC/Mac, your machine needs to meet the game's requirements here: <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/newplayerguide/minspec">PC</a>, <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/newplayerguide/minspec">Mac</a>. Don't forget, Update 39 arrives on consoles September 5.</p><p>As mentioned above, this is a free base-game update for all <i>ESO</i> players. Anybody with access to the game can download and enjoy these new additions and changes. There is no previous purchase required (aside from the game itself).</p><h2>Tamriel Evolves</h2><p>With the free Update 39 base-game patch, you can enjoy the above improvements and more to help you get the most out of your time in Tamriel. Which of the above changes and additions are you most excited to experience? Let us know via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">Twitter</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, or <a href="https://www.facebook.com/ElderScrollsOnline">Facebook</a>.</p><p><i>The Update 39 base-game patch is now live PC/Mac, Xbox One, Xbox Series X|S, PlayStation 4, and PlayStation 5.</i> </p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Update 39</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/08/2e966846125f5b8145838f4247202990.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dungeon Delvers Rejoice! The Undaunted Celebration Event Returns]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/64605</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/64605</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Get bonus rewards when you explore Tamriel's four-player dungeons during the Undaunted Celebration in-game event.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/55b65a6e41b37e0a74eb64b62f71fb9e.jpg" /><p><i>Get bonus rewards when you explore Tamriel's four-player dungeons during the Undaunted Celebration in-game event.</i></p> 
<h2>Group Up for Adventure</h2> 
<p>The Undaunted Celebration begins <b>Thursday, September 7 at 10AM EDT,</b> and runs until <b>Tuesday, September 19 at 10AM EDT</b>. Throughout this PvE in-game event, you and your intrepid band earn special rewards and Event Tickets by delving into any of <i>ESO</i>'s group dungeons. </p> 
<p>Once the event begins, you can head into Tamriel's dungeons via your map, the Activity Finder, or any dungeon entrance. In addition, you can acquire the introductory quest “Glory of the Undaunted” by speaking to Serileth at any Undaunted Enclave, traveling to an Impresario tent, or free from the in-game Crown Store.</p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2022/09/73f5287c12ad2a1ac276c76934e2f4bb.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Look for Serileth!</i></p> 
<h2>Undaunted Rewards</h2> 
<p>Tamriel's dungeons are challenging PvE encounters, but throughout the event, big dangers can also lead to big rewards. The first time you complete a dungeon each day throughout the Undaunted Celebration, you receive a Glorious Undaunted Reward Box as an additional loot drop. You can open this unique container to receive various reward items including gold, consumables, style pages, Undaunted Keys, Opal Weapon styles, and more. </p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/ac97ded8d7b519ef75b9a96bf30e5aa0.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Slay bosses for bonus rewards</i></p> 
<p>After you have defeated your first final dungeon boss each day, keep going! Subsequent final dungeon bosses reward regular Undaunted Reward boxes, which can include the following goods:</p> 
<ul><li>A guaranteed drop of an item set piece from the dungeon in which the box was acquired.</li><li>A guaranteed drop of one of the following items:</li><ul><li>A random motif style page from the following:</li><ul><li>Ascendant Order</li><li>Bloodforge</li><li>Crimson Oath</li><li>Dreadsail</li><li>Fang Lair</li><li>Huntsman</li><li>Hazardous Alchemy</li><li>Icereach</li><li>Mazzatun</li><li>Moongrave Fane</li><li>Pyre Watch</li><li>Silken Ring</li><li>Scalecaller</li><li>Silver Dawn</li><li>Stags of Z'en</li><li>Silver Rose</li><li>Thorn Legion</li><li>True Sworn</li><li>Waking Flame</li></ul></ul><li>1,000 Gold</li><li>An Undaunted Key</li><li>A Crown Repair Kit</li><li>A Riding Lesson</li></ul> 
<p>The daily Glorious Undaunted Reward Box can contain any of the above items, but it also has a chance to drop one of the following: </p> 
<ul><li>Opal monster weapon styles for:</li><ul><li><b>NEW</b> Sentinel of Rkugamz</li><li>Velidreth</li><li>Iceheart</li><li>Lord Warden</li><li>Nightflame</li><li>Swarm Mother</li></ul></ul> 
<p>Regular Undaunted Reward Boxes can also be earned by complete Bolgrul's (found within any Undaunted Enclave) Daily Undaunted Delve quest. </p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/dacc1d3e26f379623682139c009234fc.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Earn Opal style pages</i></p> 
<p><b>Opal Monster Mask Style Pages</b></p> 
<p>During the event, when you defeat and loot a specific dungeon's final boss on <b>veteran hard mode</b>, you'll also enjoy a greater chance to loot its associated Opal Monster Mask style page. This includes the following bosses and dungeons: </p> 
<ul><li>Sentinel of Rkugamz (Darkshade Caverns I)</li><li>Velidreth (Cradle of Shadows)</li><li>Iceheart (Direfrost Keep)</li><li>Lord Warden (Imperial City Prison)</li><li>Nightflame (Elden Hollow II)</li></ul> 
<p><b>Opal Monster Shoulder Outfit Style Pages</b></p> 
<p>If you own a base version of a monster shoulder style, you can also acquire the Opal version of that same style from Undaunted vendors at a cost of Undaunted Keys. Specific Opal style pages cost 50 keys, while special coffers with a random Opal Shoulder style page cost 25. </p> 
<h2>Impresario Stocks Up</h2> 
<p>During the Undaunted Celebration, you can earn <b>two Event Tickets</b> for defeating your first final dungeon boss each day. Note that with the Update 39 base-game patch, should you fail to loot your Event Tickets for whatever reason, you will be granted subsequent opportunities to loot your daily Event Tickets from other sources. Don't forget you can loot only two Event Tickets per day during the event, but now your chances of missing out on your daily allotment are minimized. </p> 
<p>During the event, you can spend your Event Tickets at the Impresario vendor to acquire the following items: </p> 
<ul><li>All three <b>Passion Dancer Blossom </b>pet fragments</li><ul><li><b>Chartreuse Lily Petals</b></li><li><b>Enchanted Silver Flute</b></li><li><b>Mystical Sheet Music</b></li></ul><li>The first TWO <b>Passion Dancer's Garment </b>costume fragments</li><ul><li><b>Bolt of Indigo Cotton</b></li><li><b>Bolt of Silver Silk</b></li></ul><li>Bound style pages for the Sentinel of Rkugamz Opal weapons and Opal masks and shoulders</li><li>Impresario Group Repair Kits</li><li>Companion Guild Commendations</li></ul>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/07/72f6c741dec03864b7ae6048f5261b1f.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Passion Dancer's Garment</i></p> 
<p>In addition, the Impresario's Assistant will stock:</p> 
<ul><li>All three <b>Unstable Morpholith </b>pet fragments</li><ul><li>Deadlands Flint</li><li>Rune-Etched Striker</li><li>Smoldering Bloodgrass Tinder</li></ul><li>All three <b>Deadlands Firewalker </b>personality fragments</li><ul><li>Vial of Simmering Daedric Brew</li><li>Vial of Bubbling Daedric Brew</li><li>Vial of Scalding Daedric Brew</li></ul><li>Finally, the Indrik vendor Nenulaure will have: </li><ul><li>Nascent Indrik Feathers</li><li>Onyx Indrik Berries</li><li>Mossheart Indrik Berries</li><li>Ebon-Glow Indrik Pet</li><li>Sapling Indrik Pet</li></ul></ul> 
<h2>Undaunted, Undaunted! </h2> 
<p>Who knows no fear of beast or blade? Undaunted! Delve into Tamriel's dungeons, defeat final bosses, and collect shiny event-specific rewards during the Undaunted Celebration in-game event. Is your party ready to venture forth into some of <i>ESO</i>'s toughest PvE content? Let us know via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">Twitter</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>.</p> 
<p><i>The Undaunted Celebration begins Thursday, September 7 from 10AM EDT, and runs until Tuesday, September 19 at 10AM EDT.</i></p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Events</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/55b65a6e41b37e0a74eb64b62f71fb9e.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Get Ready for the PC/Mac Launcher Update & Beta]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/64607</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/64607</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[An update to your ESO PC/Mac Launcher is coming soon. Here's everything you need to know about this long-awaited optimization.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/08/f32a5f61dfdc6107aa47055274e5a828.jpg" /><p><i>An update to your ESO PC/Mac Launcher is coming soon. Here's everything you need to know about this long-awaited optimization.</i></p> 
<h2>Your Launcher, Improved</h2> 
<p>Over the last few months, the team has been hard at work implementing a host of new features and improvements to<i> ESO</i>'s PC/Mac Launcher. After a successful series of tests on the Public Test Server, we're almost ready to roll this update out via an open beta. Curious as to what this update brings to the launcher? Check out the full list of the changes and additions below!</p> 
<ul><li>Patching and installing <i>ESO</i> is faster, more efficient, and has fewer patching steps. </li><li>Invalid file issues are more consistently caught for repairs.</li><li>The Launcher window can be scaled, increasing text size.</li><li>The Launcher now supports keyboard and gamepad navigation.</li><li>New options in the Settings Menu:</li><ul><li>Obsolete File Checker (automatically checks your Launcher installation directory for outdated or unneeded files and proposes to remove them to save space and prevent future errors).</li><li>Log File Locator.</li><li>Error messaging presents clearer details on internal launcher issues.</li></ul><li>Visual changes on the loading bar while patching, including the following:</li><ul><li>Display disk speed.</li><li>Display network speed.</li><li>All progress is displayed through a single loading bar.</li></ul><li>Resolution scaling, including 4K support.</li><li>A new Accessibility Settings menu.</li><ul><li>Accessed via a new head-shaped button to the left of the cog-shaped Settings Menu button.</li></ul></ul>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/08/4741117e4445039c9e1087f4d5c8feb9.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>The updated ESO Launcher</i></p> 
<h2>Getting the Update</h2> 
<p>This update will roll out gradually over select territories as part of a public beta period. When your territory's launcher is in beta, you will be able to enable the new version by following these steps:</p> 
<ol><li>Open the Launcher and click on the cog-shaped Settings Menu button</li><li>Select the Launcher Beta option</li><li>Select the Upgrade button, and confirm</li><li>Allow the Launcher to update itself and reload</li><li>Check the “Beta” flag next to the Accessibility icon to confirm it is updated<b> </b></li></ol>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/08/2e1ebaca4688b3912c294eebea1f60c7.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center"><i>Upgrade to the beta</i></p> <p>Note that Epic Games Store players cannot update their launchers at this time. Keep an eye out for more information regarding the Epic Games Store and launcher in the future.</p> <p>The beta's full duration is to be determined, but during this period, you can move back and forth between the old and new version of the launcher at will via the Settings Menu. </p> <p>Once the beta period has ended, ALL PC/Mac <i>ESO</i> players will need to update their launchers. This will occur automatically. To see when your territory is enabling the beta update, keep an eye on this <a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/642066/new-patcher-rollout" target="_blank">forum thread</a>. </p> <p>We're excited to bring the updated <i>ESO</i> PC/Mac Launcher to Tamriel's adventures, and we look forward to receiving your thoughts and feedback on the upcoming changes. Be sure to tell us what you think of these changes via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">Twitter</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/ElderScrollsOnline;">Facebook</a>. </p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/08/f32a5f61dfdc6107aa47055274e5a828.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Crown Store Showcase—September 2023]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/64617</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/64617</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Take a peek at the massive wave of new and returning items arriving in the Crown Store this September.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/08/d7ea1d10c41fff70bab3e144090bb45c.jpg" /><p><i>Take a peek at the massive wave of new and returning items arriving in the Crown Store this September.</i></p> 
<p>This September's Crown Store additions are featured below, but you can always review all the items currently on sale by checking out the <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/crownstore">Crown Store page</a>. Be sure to visit the <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/buycrowns">Buy Crowns page</a> beforehand to pick up however many crowns you need. Certain items and offers will be time-limited throughout the month, so be sure to read their individual details below to ensure you don't miss out.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<h2>ESO Plus Deals</h2><p><br></p> 
<p>All ESO Plus™ members have access to a monthly selection of exclusive deals and items. You can find more information about them in <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/54825">this article</a>.</p> 
<p><b>Exclusive Free Items</b></p> 
<p><b>Statuette: Mora, Lord of Secrets</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/08/b3d6de7611fe86d457a0a57f0e0f7e1b.jpg" />
<p><i>All statues of the Inevitable Knower are, after a fashion, access points from Apocrypha to Nirn. Given that, go carefully as you invite Hermaeus Mora into your home.</i></p> <p>The Statuette: Mora, Lord of Secrets will be available in the Crown Store FREE exclusively to ESO Plus Members on all platforms for a limited time, from September 7 to October 12, 2023, at 10AM EDT. </p> <p><br></p><h2>Crown Gem and Seals of Endeavor Items</h2> <p><b>Pet</b></p> <p><b>Amaranthine Pocket Watcher</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/08/c6d6685f2cc6f26324a3bc467d49588c.jpg" />
<p><i>"My notes indicate these vibrantly hued watchers once inhabited the ruins of Zaintiraris until an unfortunate explorer set them free. Given their color and origin, I suspect Sheogorath holds some sway over them. Also unfortunate."—Warlock Aldaale</i></p> 
<p>The Amaranthine Pocket Watcher<b> </b>pet will be available for Crown Gems and Seals of Endeavor on all platforms for a limited time, from September 5 to October 2, 2023, at 10AM EDT.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<h2>Crafting</h2> 
<p><b>Motifs</b></p> 
<p><b>Crown Crafting Motif: Clan Dreamcarver</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/08/c2cb8f445d0409d8bde07b68e38ba45a.jpg" />
<p><i>Flaminius Auctor of the Fighters Guild writes, “Since the Dreamcarvers delight in turning our own fears against us, it's only fair to turn their weapons against them....” Use to learn the Clan Dreamcarver crafting style. Also has a chance to drop by completing weekly coffers from Sanity's Edge.</i></p> 
<p>The Crown Crafting Motif: Clan Dreamcarver will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms starting September 13, 2023 at 10AM EDT. The Clan Dreamcarvers chapters, and very rarely the complete book, have a chance to drop from Sanity's Edge Treasure Coffers, awarded from Wizard Twelvane in the Sanity's Edge trial from completing the weekly quest “War Within”.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Crown Crafting Motif: Order of the Hour Style</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/08/c7d2329406f91a559b0c40c3aadf8514.jpg" />
<p><i>Amminus Entius, First Quartermaster of the Hour, writes, “The Order of the Hour is the defensive arm of the Chantry of Akatosh, and as well-disciplined knights of the Order, you must at all times properly represent the dignity and glory of the ancient Imperial worship of the Dragon God of Time.” Use to learn the Order of the Hour crafting style.</i></p> 
<p>The Crown Crafting Motif: Order Hour Style will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms starting September 25, 2023 to October 2, 2023 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item. The Order Hour chapters, and very rarely the complete book, have a chance to drop from Gold Coast Daily Contract Recompenses, awarded from Codus ap Dugal in the Kvatch Arena.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Outfit Styles</b></p> 
<p><b>Elder Scrolls Artifact: Bow of Shadows</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/08/cdc8230c86a2b1454a4a3d366944005c.jpg" />
<p><i>Alter your bow's Outfit style with a replica of the Bow of Shadows Elder Scrolls Artifact, a weapon created by the Daedric Prince Nocturnal.</i></p> 
<p>The Elder Scrolls Artifact: Bow of Shadows will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms starting September 5, 2023, to September 11, 2023, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Vinedusk Assassin Armor Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/08/76bcc16bb834a1dbdd7271ec8369d6a8.jpg" />
<p><i>Hailing from Reaper's March, these members of the Vinedusk Rangers specialize in using an assassin's techniques to keep the peace for the High King of Valenwood. Alter your armor's appearance by using this complete set of Vinedusk Assassin Outfit styles.</i></p> 
<p>The Vinedusk Assassin Armor Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms starting September 7, 2023, to September 14, 2023, at 10AM EDT.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Slimecraw Arms Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/08/d85a32d50b3257102235ce723f10df69.jpg" />
<p><i>Declare your intent to deal with the legendary crocodile of the Wayrest Sewers and you may just find the Undaunted cheering you on! Alter your weapon's appearance to match the Undaunted Slimecraw awards by using this complete set of Outfit styles.</i></p> 
<p>The Slimecraw Arms Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms starting September 7, 2023, to September 11, 2023, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item. The matching mask page will have a small chance to drop from Allene Pellingare from Veteran Wayrest Sewers I. The matching shoulder page can be purchased from Maj al-Ragath for 50 undaunted keys, or has a chance of dropping from Maj's Mystery Coffer for 1 key. Having the achievement “Down the Gutter” increases the drop chances of both items.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Tremorscale Arms Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/08/e2bcf4a009d4ee19f5418a8000ff5c09.jpg" />
<p><i>Brazzideh of Wayrest claims that Volenfell's giant duneripper earned its name after it nearly wiped out a group of Undaunted hopefuls by rupturing the ground under their very feet! Alter your weapon's appearance to match the Undaunted Tremorscale awards by using this complete set of Outfit styles.</i></p> 
<p>The Tremorscale Arms Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms starting September 7, 2023, to September 11, 2023, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item. The matching mask page will have a small chance to drop from the Guardian Constructs from Veteran Volenfell. The matching shoulder page can be purchased from Glirion the Redbeard for 50 undaunted keys, or has a chance of dropping from Glirion's Mystery Coffer for 1 key. Having the achievement “They Were Just Rusty” increases the drop chances of both items.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Kra'gh Arms Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/08/177c5b2d1ffea2ec8b628322143c3267.jpg" />
<p><i>Nessa Inkskin of Elden Root warns, “Enter Fungal Grotto with care, friends. Pay special mind to the dreugh king named Kra'gh, who uses mudcrabs to help tear foes apart.” Alter your weapon's appearance to match the Undaunted Kra'gh awards by using this set of Outfit styles.</i></p> 
<p>The Kra'gh Arms Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms starting September 11, 2023, to September 14, 2023, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item. The matching mask page will have a small chance to drop from the Dreugh King from Veteran Fungal Grotto I. The matching shoulder page can be purchased from Maj al-Ragath for 50 undaunted keys, or has a chance of dropping from Maj's Mystery Coffer for 1 key. Having the achievement “Catch of the Day” increases the drop chances of both items.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Velidreth Arms Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/08/893b9ea2f865d1e60addec2dc005d0c5.jpg" />
<p><i>Also known as the Lady of Lace, the hoarvor Daedroth named Velidreth lurks in the Cradle of Shadows and uses the darkness to her advantage—or so says Roaring Ramavel of the Undaunted. Alter your weapon's appearance to match the Undaunted Velidreth awards by using this set of Outfit styles.</i></p> 
<p>The Velidreth Arms Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms starting September 11, 2023, to September 14, 2023, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item. The matching mask page will have a small chance to drop from the eponymous boss from Veteran Cradle of Shadows. The matching shoulder page can be purchased from Urgarlag Chief-bane for 50 undaunted keys, or has a chance of dropping from Urgarlag's Mystery Coffer for 1 key. Having the achievement “Velidreth's Vengence” increases the drop chances of both items.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Bloodspawn Arms Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/08/a0c304e2fe93a46da2487864017fe2c2.jpg" />
<p><i>Spindleclutch's deadly gargoyle Bloodspawn continues to add to its tally of victories, making it one of several foes the Undaunted seek to challenge. Alter your weapon's appearance to match the Undaunted Bloodspawn awards by using this complete set of Outfit styles.</i></p> 
<p>The Bloodspawn Arms Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms starting September 14, 2023, to September 19, 2023, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item. The matching mask page will have a small chance to drop from Vorenor Winterbourne from veteran Spindleclutch II. The matching shoulder page can be purchased from Maj al-Ragath. for 50 undaunted keys, or has a chance of dropping from Maj's Mystery Coffer for 1 key. Having the achievement “Compassionate Hero” increases the drop chances of both items.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Infernal Guardian Arms Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/08/38d1f0256cf2dafdcb95b726bde64356.jpg" />
<p><i>Akgruhl gra-Bol of the Undaunted writes, “Scholars want to study how the Infernal Guardian, the fire-hardened lurcher within the City of Ash, came about. I would rather study how it comes undone.” Alter your weapon's appearance to match the Undaunted Infernal Guardian awards by using this set of Outfit styles.</i></p> 
<p>The Infernal Guardian Arms Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms starting September 14, 2023, to September 19, 2023, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item. The matching mask page will have a small chance to drop from Razor Master Erthas from veteran City of Ash I. The matching shoulder page can be purchased from Glirion the Redbeard for 50 undaunted keys, or has a chance of dropping from Glirion's Mystery Coffer for 1 key. Having the achievement “Fire Brigade” increases the drop chances of both items.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Apocrypha Expedition Arms Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/08/22aeafdc2f25f5564de88190d13f0bd8.jpg" />
<p><i>The key to adventuring within Apocrypha, Hermaeus Mora's realm, is to prepare properly. Gear up, and pay special attention to your armaments. Alter your weapon's appearance by using this complete set of Apocrypha Expedition Outfit styles.</i></p> 
<p>The Apocrypha Expedition Arms Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms during the Secrets of the Telvanni event. During the event, matching armor pages will have a small chance to drop from Secret Telvanni Coffers (regular and sublime). Bound versions of the armor pages can be purchased from the Impresario for 5 Event Tickets each during the event.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Wardrobe</h2> 
<p><b>Costumes</b></p> 
<p><b>Magnifica's Sundas Wear</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/08/d917fee95275576decfdbe82c99f860a.jpg" />
<p><i>"In Hammerfell, our Crown nobility prefer clothing simple and traditional in cut, but rich and varied in material," says designer Sar'aq of Sentinel. "This ensemble is appropriate for both receiving noble guests and visiting others."</i></p> 
<p>The Magnifica's Sundas Wear will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from September 5 to September 11, 2023, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Treasure Hunter</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/08/83ada2a0da1ddd2c046d18b7259cb352.jpg" />
<p><i>The serious treasure hunter knows it's really all about the gear. Whether you're exploring subterranean catacombs, ancient ruins, or a shattered shipwreck, when you run into an obstacle, you want to have the right tool at hand.</i></p> 
<p>The Treasure Hunter costume will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from September 7 to September 14, 2023, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Eternity Tunic with Pants</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/08/cb15e23481a795735ba2e79139b16050.jpg" />
<p><i>In Orsinium these days, even the busiest tusker likes some flair in his clothing—and nothing says "modern Orc" like a bias-cut-placket tunic from Borzighu at Coldsnap Clothiers. "This outfit," he says, "is one for the ages!"</i></p> 
<p>The Eternity Tunic with Pants will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from September 11 to September 14, 2023, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Dungeon Explorer</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/08/fa8d344fa025884c636a3eb5ca0e83bd.jpg" />
<p><i>Ready to adventure in places filled with hideous monsters, traps, and other surprises? Dress appropriately with the Dungeon Explorer costume!</i></p> 
<p>The Dungeon Explorer costume will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from September 14 to September 21, 2023, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Treethane's Mosaic Jerkin</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/08/fc08698a3ebdffc3e007911eb393703b.jpg" />
<p><i>The thousands of small shiny particles that decorate the Treethane's Mosaic Jerkin may appear at first glance to be of turquoise or other precious stones, but they are actually the iridescent carapaces of deep forest beetles.</i></p> 
<p>The Treethane's Mosaic Jerkin will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from September 18 to September 21, 2023, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Ashlander Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/08/667543f48ead4705144c62c6432767d3.jpg" />
<p><i>The costumes in this pack replicate the garb of the nomadic Ashlander tribes of Morrowind, including the travel and hunting clothes of the Mabrigash tribe, and the armor of the Kagesh.</i></p> 
<p>The Ashlander Pack costume will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from September 28 to October 5, 2023, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Events </h2> 
<p><b>Currency</b></p> 
<p><b>Event Tickets</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/08/768b6021cd2641a3e560cdb5ba9efc68.jpg" />
<p><i>A ticket used to purchase rare goods from The Impresario, Event Merchant. Curious as to what goods? Well, chat with her to see what she has to offer!</i></p> 
<p>Single Event Tickets will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time during the Undaunted Celebration and Secrets of the Telvanni. Stay tuned for event details! </p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<h2>Furniture </h2> 
<p><b>Music Box, High Isle Duel</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/08/7795f01ace9ff77bcc68719758fd8a61.jpg" />
<p><i>When activated, plays a music box arrangement of the dramatic "High Isle Duel" composition.</i></p> 
<p>The Music Box, High Isle Duel will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from September 7 to September 14, 2023, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Furnishing Pack: Moons-Blessed Oasis</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/08/463a234b3ecc9b27571429bcbca47ddd.jpg" />
<p><i>Bring the stark beauty of an Anequine oasis to your courtyard with this bundle of Elsweyr plants and statuary, complete with a luminous fountain blessed by Jone and Jode.</i></p> 
<p>The Furnishing Pack: Moons-Blessed Oasis will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from September 28 to October 12, 2023, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Statue, Kaalgrontiid's Ascent</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/08/9aa02db5b4b190424c5ce3c5fbff9dc2.jpg" />
<p><i>This statue of the mighty Dragon Kaalgrontiid shows him ascending majestically and breathing flame, frost, lightning, and even aeonfire from his position of dominance.</i></p> 
<p>The Statue, Kaalgrontiid's Ascent will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from September 28 to October 12, 2023, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Houses</h2> 
<p><b>Highhallow Hold</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/08/21737c0251779c6b1c8a21deca2d4e39.jpg" />
<p><i>Variously held by both House Dufort and Mornard, this stately manor near the edge of Gonfalon Bay is now available to the adventurer-about-town. It commands a majestic view of the water and provides easy access to the jewel of High Isle.</i></p> 
<p>Highhallow Hold will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from September 7 to September 21, 2023, at 10AM EDT. Furnished and unfurnished versions will be available.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Hunter's Glade</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/08/ee555de5520a52c431bb46c02019feb9.jpg" />
<p><i>The underground entrance way leads through a portal to an expansive forested glade in Hircine's Oblivion realm of The Hunting Grounds. Those "blessed" with lycanthropy can maintain werewolf form indefinitely in this otherworldly wilderness.</i></p> 
<p>Hunter's Glade will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from September 18 to October 2, 2023, at 10AM EDT. Furnished and unfurnished versions will be available.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Jode's Embrace</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/08/ee23d894dc6526984b40f723af11e263.jpg" />
<p><i>Few adeptoriums can match the hallowed majesty of Jode's Embrace. Rumor has it that the temple's worthiest occupants can peer into the sacred realm of Jode itself. Just keep an eye out for Dragons overhead!</i></p> 
<p>Jode's Embrace will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from September 28 to October 12, 2023, at 10AM EDT. Furnished and unfurnished versions will be available.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Houseguests</h2> 
<p><b>Skordo the Knife</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/08/b269b523a9de22ef8ab9d31610a0c2ee.jpg" />
<p><i>This Orc mercenary usually keeps busy, but now he wants some actual quiet time. Not to reflect, though—his well-used gear needs some attention. After adding Skordo to your home, you can set him on a path, plus you and your visitors can speak with him.</i></p> 
<p>Skordo the Knife will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from September 7 to September 21, 2023, at 10AM EDT.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Sereyne</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/08/1de534a9ad997a7bb6f09906daa69103.jpg" />
<p><i>An outlaw with a talent for magic but a thirst for alcohol, Sereyne wants a cozy place to drink her troubles away. Perhaps you can provide? After adding Sereyne to your home, you can set her on a path, plus you and your visitors can speak with her.</i></p> 
<p>Sereyne will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from September 28 to October 12, 2023, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Mounts</h2> 
<p><b>Treasure Hunter's Horse</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/08/63935d1a53df78546d31cc4dd5f92d6b.jpg" />
<p><i>Stolid, careful, sturdy, and long-suffering, the Treasure Hunter's Horse is resigned to a life of being ridden into crumbling ruins by a reckless master who's searching for wealth but often finds only danger.</i></p> 
<p>The Treasure Hunter's Horse will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from September 7 to September 14, 2023, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Iron Orc Welwa</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/08/6dc96031cfdc101c5e97ec2ec23032c1.jpg" />
<p><i>Iron Orcs labor hard and long, fight until their dying breath, and train mounts to do the same. So, if you're lucky enough to ride one of their welwas, expect to be pushed to your own limits as your mount keeps going despite all obstacles in its path.</i></p> 
<p>The Iron Orc Welwa mount will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from September 14 to September 21, 2023, at 10AM EDT.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Hew's Bane Pillion Palfrey</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/08/00e198e4530d909c9ddbdf9541355b80.jpg" />
<p><i>Smuggler crews in Hew's Bane first trained these palfreys to bear two riders. Originally, the training was just a cover story to hide their illicit work. But they quickly found having a mount that could hold two extremely useful for heists.</i></p> 
<p>The Hew's Bane Pillion Palfrey mount will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from September 28 to October 5, 2023, at 10AM EDT.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<h2>Customized Action</h2> 
<p><b>Recall of the Crusader</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/08/dcdb3073cf39f47e6dce3e80216725e7.jpg" />
<p><i>Let the fire of righteousness kindle within your heart. Let that flame carry you to your next worthy endeavor.</i></p> 
<p>The Recall of the Crusader will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms starting September 14, 2023 at 10AM EDT.</p> 
<p><i> </i></p> 
<h2>Pets</h2> 
<p><b>Badger Ruff Echalette</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/08/50ae6cf739b35f996c076d87ebe2c596.jpg" />
<p><i>Most Echalettes are docile and fawn-like, but not the Badger Ruff breed, which are strangely fierce and irritable. They're so ornery they've been known to chase away inquisitive Sabre Cats.</i></p> 
<p>The Badger Ruff Echalette pet<b> </b>will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from September 5 to September 11, 2023, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Pocket Mammoth</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/08/b38588256e9db808794fc2aa5395f4a2.jpg" />
<p><i>Pocket Mammoths were originally bred small in order to make them more manageable as livestock, but in Wrothgar some escaped and began breeding in the wild. However, they're easily domesticated, especially if you get one when it's young.</i></p> 
<p>The Pocket Mammoth pet will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from September 11 to September 14, 2023, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Albinoscript Fangtome</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/08/800f5f1e451c7fd7766d16294976c2fd.jpg" />
<p><i>Fangtomes know not the importance or content of the books they inhabit. In the event that your rare first editions or vital academic texts have gained a tenant, simply befriend the tome via ample spine massages and a gentle ruffling of its pages.</i></p> 
<p>The Albinoscript Fangtome pet will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from September 14 to September 21, 2023, at 10AM EDT.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Clockwork Skeevaton</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/08/f15911d1e31e58a4ee327338fa6dbaac.jpg" />
<p><i>Originally designed for probing tiny, inaccessible areas of the Clockwork City, the mechanical Skeevaton can be set to recognize and follow an individual mortal, replicating pet behavior on the surface of Nirn.</i></p> 
<p>The Clockwork Skeevaton pet will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from September 25 to September 28, 2023, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Personalities</h2> 
<p><b>Treasure Hunter</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/08/fdc11af395bc5389d78eb156f0e9a79f.jpg" />
<p><i>As a Treasure Hunter, forever poking around in shadowy nooks and crannies for loose gems, lost journals, and hidden levers, what could be more important to you than your trusty ever-burning torch? Never again be lost in the dark without it!</i></p> 
<p>The Treasure Hunter personality will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from September 7 to September 14, 2023, at 10AM EDT.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p>All-new and unending challenges are on the horizon for Tamriel's adventurers, and the above goods may come in handy for when you delve into the infinite unknown. Don't forget, before making a move to acquire any of these items, you should head over to the <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/buycrowns">Buy Crowns page</a>. Are you eager to pick up any of the above items this September? Let us know via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">Twitter</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/ElderScrollsOnline">Facebook</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Crown Store</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/08/d7ea1d10c41fff70bab3e144090bb45c.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[New Patcher Rollout]]></title>
            <link>https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/642066/new-patcher-rollout</link>
            <guid>https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/642066/new-patcher-rollout</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 20:49:19 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[Hello everyone! After plenty of testing <a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en-gb/discussion/632782/new-eso-launcher-testing-and-launch-plan-pc-and-mac">during the last PTS period</a>, we are pleased to announce the rollout of our new patcher on the live servers for PC/Mac. The rollout of the new patcher will happen in four phases, with new countries being added during each phase. As we give countries access to the new patcher, we will make note of it in the list below by noting next to the country name (has the new patcher.) We will also note what phase we are currently in by specifying whether it has not started, in progress, or complete, next to the phase number. The countries getting the patcher are listed in order below.<br><br>
Thanks for your patience as we roll this out to all countries listed below. A special thanks to everyone who helped test out the launcher during the last PTS and provided feedback.<br><br><b>Phase 1 (Complete) </b>
<ol><li>Netherlands (Has the new patcher)</li>
<li>Sweden (Has the new patcher)</li>
<li>Czech Republic/ Finland (Has the new patcher)</li>
<li>Norway/ Denmark (Has the new patcher)</li>
<li>Hungary/ Switzerland/ Romania (Has the new patcher)</li>
</ol><br><b>Phase 2 (Complete) </b>
<ol><li>Poland (Has the new patcher)</li>
<li>Spain/ Turkey (Has the new patcher)</li>
<li>Italy/ Austria/ Belgium/ Portugal/ Greece/ Ireland (Has the new patcher)</li>
</ol><br><b>Phase 3 (Not Started) </b>
<ol><li>United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland/ France</li>
<li>Germany</li>
<li>United States of America</li>
</ol><br><b>Phase 4 (Not Started) </b><br>
This phase will encompass all other countries where ESO is available, that are not listed above.<br><br><b>Known Issues</b>
<ul><li>Some Czech Republic players may not have their country recognized, thus making them unable to upgrade the patch at this time. We are aware of the issue and working toward a solution.</li>
</ul>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>Forum</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Delve into the Endless Archive & Update 40 during a Special Livestream Preview]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/64615</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/64615</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Get ready to tune in to Twitch.tv/Bethesda as we reveal the new challenges and base-game additions coming soon to The Elder Scrolls Online.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/08/a79856cb8f5452e3ee64d1b355c60970.jpg" /><p><i>Get ready to tune in to Twitch.tv/Bethesda as we reveal the new challenges and base-game additions coming soon to The Elder Scrolls Online.</i></p> 
<p>Looking to learn more about the Endless Archive and upcoming base-game updates? The New Feature &amp; Update Preview: Endless Archive stream will go live on <a href="http://www.twitch.tv/Bethesda">Twitch.tv/Bethesda</a> on Thursday, September 14 at 3PM EDT. </p><p>During the show, Senior Community Manager Gina Bruno will be joined by Creative Director Rich Lambert and Lead Encounter Designer Mike Finnigan to dive deep into the new Endless Archive PvE activity and reveal some of the major changes arriving with the Update 40 base-game patch. This will be your first opportunity to see Endless Archive gameplay, so don't miss out!</p> 
<p>Twitch Drops will be enabled for those watching, so be sure to <a href="https://help.elderscrollsonline.com/app/answers/detail/a_id/41809/">link your <i>ESO</i> and Twitch accounts</a> to be able to earn the new Tentacular Tome emote!</p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/08/40e000679157a312a2e2d20eaa42b528.png" />
<p>That's not all! Keep an eye on this blog closer to September 14 for details on additional livestreams and recap shows from members of the <i>ESO</i> global community team.</p> 
<p>Be sure to join us on <a href="https://www.twitch.tv/Bethesda">Twitch.tv/Bethesda</a> Thursday, September 14 at 3PM EDT, to get a first look at what challenges and rewards await you within the Endless Archive—we'll see you there!</p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Update 40</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/08/a79856cb8f5452e3ee64d1b355c60970.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Daily Login Rewards–September 2023]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/64609</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/64609</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Discover some of the items you can claim by logging into The Elder Scrolls Online this September 2023!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/08/7ad8342a3ccfffae05bff15d306cbe9f.jpg" /><p><i>Discover some of the items you can claim by logging into The Elder Scrolls Online this September 2023! </i></p> 
<p>Venturing into Tamriel this coming September? There's a broad selection of in-game goodies you can claim simply by logging into the game and visiting the Daily Rewards screen. Find everything you need to know about Daily Login Rewards in <a href="https://help.bethesda.net/#en/answer/41950">this help article</a>, and check out <b>just some</b> of the upcoming items you can claim below!</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Gold ×25,000—Day 7</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/06/cfd7739fad8fa3484c8509c1a47941dc.jpg" />
<p>Whether you're in the market for materials, gear, or provisions, a little bit of extra gold for Tamriel's many Guild Traders is always welcome!</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Akaviri Potentate Crates ×2—Day 14 </b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/08/f855b53f259536ac1befed8d3b261f4b.jpg" />
<p>Herald the return of the Second Empire with Akaviri Potentate Crown Crates, first introduced way back in 2020. Check out our <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/59277">preview blog</a> (published in December 2020) for insight into some of the items you can find in these crates.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Chaurus Egg Ear Studs Adornment—Day 21 </b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/08/c81aa18a5999b3b48e65988b0e5b6919.jpg" />
<p>While exploring the dark depths of Blackreach, you wouldn't want to meet a chaurus in the wild, but their eggs do appear to make for exceptionally fetching earrings!*</p><p><br></p> 
<p>Don't forget, this is just a small sample of some of the useful in-game items you can unlock and claim when logging into <i>ESO</i> next month. If you'd like to see the complete list, be sure to visit the Daily Rewards section of the in-game Crown Store on September 1! Do any of these items catch your eye? Will you be logging in frequently this month to claim them? Let us know via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">Twitter</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/ElderScrollsOnline">Facebook</a>.</p> 
<p><i>*We are reliably informed that the eggs are miniature replicas and pose no danger of hatching.</i></p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Daily Rewards</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/08/7ad8342a3ccfffae05bff15d306cbe9f.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dungeon Finder Known Issues]]></title>
            <link>https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/636122/dungeon-finder-known-issues</link>
            <guid>https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/636122/dungeon-finder-known-issues</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 15:54:08 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[Hi all,<br><br>
We wanted to give everyone some visibility into a couple of issues we are currently tracking involving the Dungeon Finder.<br><br>
The first is a recurring issue where some group members appear to be offline after you port into a dungeon or are not ported at all. We've been working on a fix for this that will hopefully make it into U39.<br><br>
The other issue relates to queueing as a group for a dungeon, specifically as a Tank or Healer. We've seen reports where these roles take longer than intended to get matched into a group, and after some investigating, we found there is indeed a problem here when certain conditions are met. While we work on addressing this, we want to offer some additional information that you can leverage as a workaround in the meantime:<br><ul><li>In 3-person groups:
<ul><li>Tank, Healer and Direct Damage (DD) combination: If the Tank or Healer is the group lead, the LFG queue times will be significantly longer than if the DD is the group lead.</li>
<li>2 DD and a Healer, or 2 DD and a Tank: If the Tank or Healer is group lead, the LFG queue times will be slightly longer than if the DD is the group lead, but to a much lesser extent than the Tank/Healer/DD combo above.</li>
</ul></li>
<li>4-person groups do not appear to be impacted by this issue in any way.</li>
</ul>
Until we can get a fix for this, we suggest <b>queuing up with the DD as group leader for any 3 person groups</b> so you get through the queues much quicker.<br>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>Forum</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>