<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>ESO Announcements</title>
        <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/</link>
        <description>Combined ESO blog and forum post announcements feed</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>Magic</generator>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ESO 2024 Global Reveal—Introducing Scribing]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65361</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65361</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Discover new ways to play with Scribing, arriving as part of The Elder Scrolls Online: Gold Road.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/01/e616bdb61ba3bb4e6bd6d96fbf82ea12.jpg" /><p><i>Discover new ways to play with Scribing, arriving as part of The Elder Scrolls Online: Gold Road. </i></p> 
<p>In <i>The Elder Scrolls Online: Gold Road </i>(arriving June 3 on PC/Mac and June 18 on Xbox and PlayStation consoles), you can unlock access to an all-new game system: Scribing. With Scribing, you can manipulate the nature of magic itself by collecting and customizing special skills, granting you even more ways to tailor specific builds and play your way. </p> 
<h2>Customize New Skills</h2> 
<p>When designing this new system, the team focused on improving opportunities for roleplay and choice for <i>ESO</i>'s adventurers by providing greater agency when it comes to selecting and adapting the skills that are right for them. What exactly does this mean for you and your characters? Scribing introduces Grimoires, which are new types of skills for your existing skill lines. You can customize these Grimoires beyond their basic functions, transforming them into exactly what you want on your action bar. </p> 
<p>For example, one new Grimoire, called Soul Touch, allows you to pull soul magic from the core of your being and cast it at a nearby enemy or ally. You can customize Soul Touch by choosing its Primary, Secondary, and Tertiary Scripts. You could use the Primary to create a Damage Shield for an ally, pull an enemy to you, or even change it to Magic, Shock, or Physical Damage. In addition, you could use the Soul Infusion Secondary to enable the ability to consume a soul gem and gain Ultimate, or you can use a Recovery Secondary to regain resources for a targeted ally.</p>
<img src="https://esossl-a.akamaihd.net/uploads/website/Q3ZeOwb7aw/s41bng_preview.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Customize your Grimoires with Scripts</i></p> 
<p>The above is just one example, but the Scribing system will give you a ton of new ways to change your build and playstyle, since you can unlock a host of Grimoires and Scripts at launch. </p> 
<h2>Explore the Origins of Magic</h2> 
<p>To master the art of Scribing you'll need the <i>Gold Road </i>Chapter, which grants access to a brand-new questline. In this unique story, ancient magic arising in the world attracts the attention of the Mages Guild, who send one of their best to investigate. </p> 
<p>Working alongside a brave Knight of the Lamp, you'll discover a mysterious new location and altar and discover the secrets of the mage who built it. Throughout the questline, you'll learn how to scribe, gain a Grimoire or two, and meet new friends along the way.</p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/01/862d82507bb6a5d566ac10fc40af81d1.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Ally with the Luminaries of magic</i></p> 
<p>Fantastic untold lore awaits those willing to delve into the esoteric mysteries of magic, but those who commit to unraveling its secrets will find new power and freedom as they do. </p> 
<h2>Style Your Existing Skills, Too! </h2> 
<p>With the ability to mix and match a wide variety of classes, races, skills, and gear sets, <i>ESO</i> has always striven to provide you with the freedom and power to customize your characters' unique playstyles. </p> 
<p>In the spirit of this core pillar, <i>Gold Road</i> also introduces a new type of collectible, called Skill Styles. Skill Styles are color variation of popular abilities from various weapon, guild, and world skill lines, helping you further stand out on the battlefield. </p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/01/995744a34de5715f92ef734cc8d5ed38.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Customize existing abilities with Skill Styles</i></p> 
<p>At the launch of <i>Gold Road</i>, you can unlock these Skill Styles as in-game rewards, but there's a lot more planned for them beyond the Chapter, too.</p> 
<h2>Play Your Way</h2> 
<p><i>The Elder Scrolls Online: Gold Road</i>'s new Scribing system will be a powerful and flexible new tool for Tamriel's adventurers, and we can't wait to see how the community reacts to it. Are you ready and willing to explore the mysteries of magic? Are you excited to experiment with Grimoires and Scripts to create a playstyle uniquely your own? Tell us via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (Formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>. </p> 
<p><i>The Elder Scrolls Online: Gold Road arrives for PC/Mac on June 3, 2024, and for Xbox and PlayStation consoles on June 18, 2024. Pre-purchase Gold Road now to receive unique bonus rewards at launch and immediate access to Welkyndstone Ruins Wolf mount and Welkyndstone Ruins Pup pet*. Don't miss out!</i></p> 
<p><i>*The Welkyndstone Ruins Pup pet is available only until March 18, 2024.</i></p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Gold Road</category>
            <category>Update 42</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/01/e616bdb61ba3bb4e6bd6d96fbf82ea12.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ESO 2024 Global Reveal—Gold Road's West Weald Zone]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65363</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65363</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Discover West Weald, ESO's newest zone just announced as part of The Elder Scrolls Online: Gold Road!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/01/0b177a588e1c2d830a4408eb434f3ad9.jpg" /><p><i>Discover West Weald, ESO's newest zone just announced as part of The Elder Scrolls Online: Gold Road!</i></p><h2>Explore West Weald</h2> <p>In <i>ESO</i>'s upcoming <i>Gold Road</i> Chapter (arriving June 3 for PC/Mac and June 18 for Xbox and PlayStation consoles) you can explore and quest within the West Weald zone, which introduces brand-new locations, characters, challenges, rewards, and stories. If you're already familiar with southeast Cyrodiil, this Chapter allows you to explore this bountiful part of Tamriel for the first time since 2006's <i>The Elder Scrolls IV: Oblivion. </i></p> <p>Recently, strange happenings have thrown the region into turmoil, changing the landscape in bizarre ways and introducing new threats you'll have to contend with. In the southeast lies the Gold Road, a temperate environment similar to that found on the Gold Coast. It's home to the region's capital city, Skingrad, the bustling center of the zone and lynchpin for the Colovian Imperials who call the province home. </p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/01/6c423bf1ee34492fa4f12665295066b6.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Discover (or rediscover) Skingrad</i></p> 
<p>Toward the southwest, you will find Dawnwood. Formerly under Imperial control, this area is now home to the encroaching jungles of nearby Valenwood. There, you'll discover a dense wilderness and the Wood Elf settlement of Vashabar. Even more alarming is the Wildburn, a dangerous area that separates Dawnwood from the Colovian Highlands and Gold Road, comprised of sickened, magically twisted land and even more warped beasts. </p> 
<p>In the north of West Weald lies the Colovian Highlands, a mountainous region that is home to an Imperial settlement and numerous ruins. </p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/01/0132c96d607b2c17834eff2d9e101c41.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Venture into ancient Ayleid ruins</i></p> 
<p>Classic Colovian architecture inspired many of the zone's structures, although as you explore its varied terrain you'll also encounter many Ayleid ruins that speak to an older heritage. These ruins are less “spoiled” than many other similar locations and show off structures and architectural pieces of Ayleid culture never seen before.</p> 
<h2>New Challenges and Rewards</h2> 
<p>While the land itself is changing, it is also under attack from a host of new, unfamiliar foes, bringing all-new dangers to West Weald's adventurers. </p> 
<p>These challenges include new delves and public dungeons to explore, world bosses to face, and a bevy of stand-alone quests that tell stories unique to this zone. In addition, new world events, called Mirrormoor Incursions, set you and your fellow adventurers against waves of invading Daedra. </p> 
<p><i>Gold Road</i> also introduces a 12-player Trial, the Lucent Citadel, which has you and your band venture into a long-forgotten Daedric vault—new bosses, mysteries, and rewards await! </p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/01/b3f88397b7ef3c74acc22192a8210d3d.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Prepare for a new Trial</i></p> 
<p>Speaking of rewards, if you venture into the zone, you'll find that West Weald is home to no shortage of new riches. This includes 10 item sets to wear, more Antiquities to dig up, fun collectibles to unlock, and a host of Achievements and Titles to earn. </p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/01/476564f980c157efe4fb816337f842de.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Seize the treasures of West Weald</i></p> 
<p>Finally, <i>Gold Road</i> also introduces an entirely new type of reward collectible called Skill Styles, which provide visual changes to popular abilities, with more planned for future updates!</p> 
<h2>Wonders Old and New Await</h2> 
<p>The return of Ithelia and the Wildburn introduces threats both old and new in West Weald. Will you meet these rising dangers? Or perhaps you're excited to return to Skingrad and discover the Colovian Highlands of Tamriel's Second Era? Let us know via <a href="https://twitter.com/Bethesda_jpn">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>. </p> 
<p><i>The Elder Scrolls Online: Gold Road arrives for PC/Mac on June 3, 2024, and for Xbox and PlayStation consoles on June 18, 2024. Pre-purchase Gold Road now to receive unique bonus rewards at launch and immediate access to the Welkyndstone Ruins Wolf mount and Welkyndstone Ruins Pup pet*. Don't miss out!</i></p> 
<p><i>*The Welkyndstone Ruins Pup pet is available only until March 18, 2024.</i></p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Gold Road</category>
            <category>Update 42</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/01/0b177a588e1c2d830a4408eb434f3ad9.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ESO 2024 Global Reveal—The Elder Scrolls Online: Gold Road & Scions of Ithelia]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65359</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65359</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Discover new adventures and revelations in The Elder Scrolls Online: Gold Road Chapter and Scions of Ithelia dungeon DLC, announced during the ESO 2024 Global Reveal.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/01/ab8ecfcda37467c57e92e21d9640df68140488.jpg" /><p><i>Discover new adventures and revelations in The Elder Scrolls Online: Gold Road Chapter and Scions of Ithelia dungeon DLC, announced during the ESO 2024 Global Reveal.</i><br></p>
<a href="https://youtube.com/v/zt-ZIb2dKIw?autoplay=1&rel=0"><img src="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/zt-ZIb2dKIw/maxresdefault.jpg" /></a>
<h2>The Forgotten Prince</h2> 
<p>A secret long held by Hermaeus Mora has been uncovered and the existence of the Forgotten Prince has come to light. Now, Ithelia's return puts reality itself at risk.</p> 
<p>Arriving March 11 for PC/Mac and March 26 for Xbox and Playstation consoles, the <i>Scions of Ithelia </i>dungeon DLC pack continues the story from last year's <i>Necrom</i> Chapter. Learn more about the spreading threat via the two dungeons featured in this pack, then experience its stunning conclusion in the upcoming Chapter, <i>The Elder Scrolls Online: Gold Road</i> (arriving June 3 for PC/Mac and June 18 for consoles).</p> 
<h2>Scions of Ithelia</h2> 
<p>Begin 2024's adventures with the <i>Scions of Ithelia</i> dungeon DLC pack in March, which introduces two new 4-player dungeons, <b>Oathsworn Pit</b> and <b>Bedlam Veil</b>. </p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/01/0f8e293fb7357fbc6fb495ff3d1fe216.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Scions of Ithelia</i></p> 
<p>These dungeons allow you to explore a training ground for the followers of Malacath and a secret vault within the Oblivion demi-realm of Maelstrom. Both dungeons help set the stage for the upcoming Chapter in their own way, but their storylines can be enjoyed individually, too.</p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/01/8d3598bca482bc066b10f4d0ba031dcf.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Battle the followers of the Forgotten Prince</i></p> 
<p>These two new dungeons are set to challenge you and your team with Normal and Veteran difficulties (including Hard Mode) and each feature their own Achievements and rewards (including unique collectibles and item sets).</p> 
<h2>Gold Road Chapter</h2> 
<p>Featuring a new zone, storyline, Scribing system, rewards, and more, The<i> Elder Scrolls Online: Gold Road</i> is <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/joinus">now available for pre-purchase on all platforms</a>. This new Chapter takes you to West Weald, a region situated on the borders of Cyrodiil, the Gold Coast, and Valenwood. Those <i>Elder Scroll</i>s fans who played 2006's <i>The Elder Scrolls IV: Oblivion</i> might be familiar with this part of Tamriel, including its capital city of Skingrad. </p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/01/f2cd8a3b84c6f30e3f4845e3871d9ec8.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>The Elder Scrolls Online: Gold Road</i></p> 
<p>Ruled by the Colovian Count Calantius, this province is an independent nation allied to the Imperial forces occupying nearby Cyrodiil. However, seemingly overnight, the sweltering jungles of Valenwood have replaced a third of the region, and the Count seeks answers to avoid losing any more of his realm.</p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/01/57157de818d13beccec9405bffeefba9.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>The unraveling of reality is everyone's problem</i></p> 
<p>That said, the new forest (that the Wood Elves call Dawnwood) may not be the most pressing concern for you and your allies, as you must also investigate the reappearance of Ithelia, the Forgotten Prince.</p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/01/5328189025afe0c9fdaea85b654c8a59.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Beware the Scions of Ithelia</i></p> 
<p>While her followers cause chaos in her name, many mysteries remain. Why does she now walk West Weald, and what are her Scions' plans for her return? Reality itself hangs in the balance! While it continues a narrative that began in 2023, like <i>Scions of Ithelia</i>, <i>Gold Road</i> tells its own stand-alone tale and does not require having played the <i>Necrom </i>Chapter.</p> 
<h2>A Clash of Fates</h2> 
<p>The Forgotten Prince may soon return to power, and fate itself trembles in anticipation. What impact will you, a mortal adventurer, have on West Weald and its myriad threats? You'll have to play <i>Gold Road</i> to find out!</p> 
<p>In the meantime, let us know your hopes and predictions for how this conflict will play out via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>. Keep an eye out for more information about both the new Chapter and dungeon DLC in the future, too!</p> 
<p><i>The Elder Scrolls Online: Gold Road arrives for PC/Mac on June 3, 2024, and for Xbox and PlayStation consoles on June 18, 2024. Pre-purchase Gold Road now to receive unique bonus rewards at launch and immediate access to the Welkyndstone Ruins Wolf mount and Welkyndstone Ruins Pup pet*. Don't miss out!</i></p> 
<p><i>*The Welkyndstone Ruins Pup pet is available only until March 18, 2024.</i></p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Gold Road</category>
            <category>Scions of Ithelia</category>
            <category>Update 41</category>
            <category>Update 42</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/01/ab8ecfcda37467c57e92e21d9640df68140488.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Elder Scrolls Online: Gold Road Editions & Pre-Purchase Rewards]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65365</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65365</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn more about the various editions of The Elder Scrolls Online: Gold Road and discover which version is best for you!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/01/14fa2268b5b4572eef0f0d5f0dbc2c60.jpg" /><p><i>Learn more about the various editions of The Elder Scrolls Online: Gold Road and discover which version is best for you! </i></p> 
<h2>The Elder Scrolls Online: Gold Road</h2> 
<p><i>The Elder Scrolls Online: Gold Road</i> Chapter launches June 3 for PC/Mac and June 18 for Xbox and PlayStation consoles. In this exciting new Chapter of the <i>ESO </i>saga, you must investigate the schemes of the followers of the Forgotten Prince Ithelia, explore the new West Weald zone (including the city of Skingrad), and customize unique skills to your liking with Scribing, an all-new game system.</p> 
<p>Are you excited to begin your adventure and experience a multitude of stories from across all of Tamriel before <i>Gold Road</i>'s launch in June? Pre-purchase either <i>The Elder Scrolls Online</i> <i>Collection: Gold Road </i>or its <i>Deluxe </i>edition to get <b>immediate access</b> to the <i>ESO</i> base game and <b>all </b>previous Chapters as well as a bounty of in-game collectibles.</p><br><h2>Pre-Purchase and Pre-Purchase Rewards</h2><p>When you pre-purchase <i>The Elder Scrolls Online: Gold Road</i>, you will immediately receive the Welkyndstone Ruins Wolf mount and Welkyndstone Ruins Pup pet*. In addition, you will gain access to the following bonus content at launch:</p><ul><li>Eyebright Raven pet</li><li>Strid River Fisherfolk costume</li><li>x1 Diamond Anniversary Crate</li><li>Gold Road Treasure Maps</li><li>×2 Experience scrolls (+100% for 1 hour)</li></ul>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/01/0c212799a57b494daca841f37cc41950.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Gold Road pre-purchase rewards</i></p> 
<p>Please be aware that the Welkyndstone Ruins Pup pet is available as a pre-purchase reward only from <b>now until March 18, 2024</b>, so don't miss out! </p> 
<h2>Choose Which Edition Best Fits You </h2> 
<p>When pre-purchasing <i>The Elder Scrolls Online: Gold Road</i>, you can select from two main editions: </p> 
<ul><li><i>The Elder Scrolls Online Collection: Gold Road</i></li><ul><li>This includes the <i>Gold Road</i> Chapter (available at launch in June) and <b>immediate access</b> to both the base game and all seven previous Chapters (<i>Necrom, High Isle</i>, <i>Blackwood</i>, <i>Greymoor</i>, <i>Elsweyr</i>, <i>Summerset</i>, and <i>Morrowind</i>)</li></ul><li><i>The Elder Scrolls Online Upgrade: Gold Road </i></li><ul><li>Includes the <i>Gold Road</i> Chapter (available at launch in June)</li></ul></ul> 
<p>If you're a fresh-faced adventurer and new to the grand world of Tamriel, or if you've missed some of the previous Chapters and want access to them all, then the <i>Collection</i> edition may be just what you need! In addition to receiving access to the base game and <i>Gold Road</i>, you can also experience each of the seven previous <i>ESO</i> Chapters in whichever order you deem fit. Hundreds of hours of exciting exploration, daring quests, and thrilling adventure await! </p> 
<p>For our veteran players who already own the previous Chapters, we recommend the <i>Upgrade</i>, which will unlock the latest Chapter when it arrives in June.</p> 
<p>In addition to the basic <i>Collection</i> and <i>Upgrade</i> versions of <i>Gold Road</i>, you can also get a Deluxe edition for either, which includes the following <b>exclusive in-game rewards</b> that you can access at launch:</p> 
<ul><li>West Weald Tharriker mount </li><li>Skingrad Guard Mastiff pet</li><li>Skingrad Vedette Armor Pack </li><li>Ulfsild's Tome of Legends memento</li><li>Colovian Emote Pack</li></ul>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/01/be77a18cfe66c3cfa77b66b9c1e021ca.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Deluxe Edition items</i></p> 
<p>Even better, if you purchase the <i>Deluxe Collection</i> version of <i>Gold Road</i>, you'll also receive the <i>Collector's/Deluxe</i> edition rewards from <b>all previous <i>ESO</i> Chapters</b> (this <b>does not </b>include the previous pre-purchase rewards). It's a bargain so enticing, you'd think Clavicus Vile came up with it!</p> 
<p>You can see a complete list of each <i>Gold Road</i> edition and what they contain below. </p> 
<h3>The Elder Scrolls Online Deluxe Collection: Gold Road</h3> 
<p><i>The Elder Scrolls Online Deluxe Collection: Gold Road</i> includes <b>immediate access</b> to the base game and all seven previous Chapters (<i>Necrom, High</i> <i>Isle</i>, <i>Blackwood</i>, <i>Greymoor</i>, <i>Elsweyr</i>, <i>Summerset</i>, and <i>Morrowind</i>) in addition to the <i>Gold Road</i> Chapter in June.</p> 
<p>This edition also includes these <i>Deluxe </i>rewards at launch: </p> 
<ul><li>West Weald Tharriker mount </li><li>Skingrad Guard Mastiff pet</li><li>Skingrad Vedette Armor Pack </li><li>Ulfsild's Tome of Legends memento</li><li>Colovian Emote Pack</li></ul> 
<p>Additionally, you'll gain access to the <i>Collector's/Deluxe</i> edition digital items for all previous Chapters.</p> 
<p>Pre-purchase now to gain <b>instant access</b> to the Welkyndstone Ruins Wolf mount and the Welkyndstone Ruins Pup pet* as well as even more awesome pre-purchase items at launch.</p> 
<h3>The Elder Scrolls Online Collection: Gold Road</h3> 
<p><i>The Elder Scrolls Online Collection: Gold Road</i> includes <b>immediate access</b> to the base game and all seven previous Chapters (<i>Necrom, High</i> <i>Isle</i>, <i>Blackwood</i>, <i>Greymoor</i>, <i>Elsweyr</i>, <i>Summerset</i>, and <i>Morrowind</i>) in addition to the <i>Gold Road</i> Chapter in June.</p> 
<p>Pre-purchase now to gain <b>instant access</b> to the Welkyndstone Ruins Wolf mount and the Welkyndstone Ruins Pup pet* as well as even more awesome pre-purchase items at launch.</p> 
<h3>The Elder Scrolls Online Deluxe Upgrade: Gold Road</h3> 
<p><i>The Elder Scrolls Online Deluxe Upgrade: Gold Road</i> includes access to the <i>Gold Road</i> Chapter at launch in June.</p> 
<p>This edition also includes these <i>Deluxe </i>rewards at launch: </p> 
<ul><li>West Weald Tharriker mount </li><li>Skingrad Guard Mastiff pet</li><li>Skingrad Vedette Armor Pack </li><li>Ulfsild's Tome of Legends memento</li><li>Colovian Emote Pack</li></ul> 
<p>Pre-purchase now to gain <b>instant access</b> to the Welkyndstone Ruins Wolf mount as well as the Welkyndstone Ruins Pup pet* plus additional pre-purchase items available at launch.</p> 
<h3>The Elder Scrolls Online Upgrade: Gold Road </h3> 
<p><i>The Elder Scrolls Online Upgrade: Gold Road</i> includes access to the <i>Gold Road</i> Chapter at launch in June. </p> 
<p>Pre-purchase your copy now to gain <b>instant access</b> to the Welkyndstone Ruins Wolf mount as well as the Welkyndstone Ruins Pup pet* plus additional pre-purchase items available at launch.</p> 
<h2>Confront the Forgotten Prince</h2> 
<p><i>The Elder Scrolls Online: Gold Road</i> arrives June 3 for PC/Mac and June 18 for Xbox and PlayStation consoles. If you can't wait to begin, pick up one of the <i>Collection</i> editions to gain immediate access to the base game and all previous Chapters. Don't forget, all <i>Gold Road</i> pre-purchases will also instantly grant you access to the Welkyndstone Ruins Wolf mount and the Welkyndstone Ruins Pup pet*!</p><br><p>Are you ready to confront a never-before-seen Daedric Prince, venture across the chaotic West Weald, and delve into the mysteries of Scribing? Let us know via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline" target="_blank">X (Formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>.</p><p><i>The Elder Scrolls Online: Gold Road arrives for PC/Mac on June 3, 2024, and for Xbox and PlayStation consoles on June 18, 2024. Pre-purchase Gold Road now to receive unique bonus rewards at launch and immediate access to Welkyndstone Ruins Wolf mount and Welkyndstone Ruins Pup pet*. Don't miss out!</i> </p><p><i>*The Welkyndstone Ruins Pup pet is available only until March 18, 2024.</i> </p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Gold Road</category>
            <category>Update 42</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/01/14fa2268b5b4572eef0f0d5f0dbc2c60.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Try ESO Plus for Free and Get Access to DLCs, Unlimited Crafting Space, and More]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65385</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65385</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Enjoy all that's on offer with ESO Plus™ membership by claiming your free trial now available in the Crown Store until January 25.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2022/07/aafe98e3d2e6d688422e6becdef8fa88.jpg" /><p><i>Enjoy all that's on offer with ESO Plus™ membership by claiming your free trial now available in the Crown Store until January 25.</i></p> 
<h2>Get More From ESO</h2> 
<p>The ESO Plus Free Trial is live from now until January 25, at 10AM EST. During the trial period, you can enjoy the following ESO Plus benefits with no credit card required and no strings attached:</p> 
<ul><li>Full access to over 20 DLC game packs—new zones, quests, dungeons, and more</li><ul><li>Includes 26 group dungeons, new systems like Antiquities and Tales of Tribute, and more!</li></ul><li>A Craft Bag providing unlimited storage for all your crafting materials </li><li>Double Bank space for all characters on your account </li><li>10% increase to experience, gold, and Archival Fortune acquisition, crafting inspiration, and trait research rates </li><li>Double furnishings and collectibles space in player housing </li><li>Exclusive ability to dye costumes </li><li>Double Transmute Crystal storage </li></ul> 
<p>Eager to check out ESO Plus for free? Here's what you need to do:</p> 
<ol><li>Log into <i>The Elder Scrolls Online</i></li><li>Navigate to the Crown Store</li><li>Select the ESO Plus tab</li><li>Select “Free Trial!”</li></ol> 
<p>Once you've activated your trial, all the benefits listed above are available to you until January 25. Note that this free trial does <b>not</b> grant access to the Companions from the <i>Blackwood </i>or <i>High Isle</i> Chapters.</p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/01/65b198080ab0b6122e0f7b5a7605cf41.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Get access to great DLC stories with ESO Plus</i></p> 
<p>If you'd like to continue to enjoy the benefits of ESO Plus beyond the trial, including monthly crown stipends and exclusive in-game deals, you can get full membership via our ESO Plus page! Want to learn more? Check out our <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/guides/esoplusguide">ESO Plus guide</a>.</p> 
<h2>ESO Plus, Without the Cost</h2> 
<p>Boosts to XP and gold gains, additional bag space, DLC access, and more await those with ESO Plus membership, and you can get a taste of these boons with no credit card required and no strings attached during the free trial period. </p> 
<p>Don't forget, the Guilds and Glory in-game event is now live, too, enabling you to earn <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65367">increased rewards in certain DLC zones</a>! Are you excited to enjoy the benefits of membership at no cost? Let us know via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (Formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>. </p> 
<p><i>The ESO Plus Free Trial is now live and will run until Thursday, January 25, at 10AM EST.</i></p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>ESO Plus</category>
            <category>Crown Store</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2022/07/aafe98e3d2e6d688422e6becdef8fa88.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Get a Glimpse of Tamriel's Chaotic Future with this New Teaser]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65357</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65357</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Watch a new trailer and get ready to learn more about the future of The Elder Scrolls Online during the upcoming 2024 Global Reveal.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/01/57789f0e26fe7ad4f328a976056d6c9f.jpg" /><p><i>Watch a new trailer and get ready to learn more about the future of The Elder Scrolls Online during the upcoming 2024 Global Reveal. </i></p> 
<p><i>The Elder Scrolls Online</i> 2024 Global Reveal livestream kicks off this Thursday, January 18 at 4PM EST, on <a href="https://www.twitch.tv/Bethesda">Twitch.tv/Bethesda</a>, and it promises to reveal what kind of adventures and challenges are coming soon to Tamriel's heroes. However, you can enjoy a sneak peek at what is to come with this new teaser trailer. </p>
<a href="https://youtube.com/v/TH9Z9IloYS0?autoplay=1&rel=0"><img src="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/TH9Z9IloYS0/maxresdefault.jpg" /></a>
<p>The <i>ESO</i> 2024 Global Reveal follows directly after the <a href="https://news.xbox.com/en-us/2024/01/09/xbox-developer-direct-2024/">Xbox Developer_Direct</a> (so check out all the big reveals there, too!) and will dive deep into this year's major releases, including everything you need to know about the game's next Chapter. </p> 
<p>In addition, tune in to the show and you'll also receive the Pyromancer's Quandary emote (after watching for 15 minutes) and a 50% Gold Coast Experience Scroll (after watching for 30 minutes) as Twitch Drops. Don't forget <a href="https://help.elderscrollsonline.com/app/answers/detail/a_id/41809/~/how-do-i-link-my-eso-account-to-twitch">to link your <i>ESO</i> and Twitch accounts</a> prior.</p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/01/057efe5d5451f00bb3679229ce652591.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>The Pyromancer's Quandary emote</i></p> 
<h2>Post Show Livestreams</h2> 
<p>The excitement doesn't end there. Be sure to tune in after the Global Reveal livestream as members of the <i>ESO </i>Community Team from all over the world host various post-show recaps with members of the <i>ESO </i>Development Team, Stream Team, and the #ESOFam. You can see a complete list of supporting shows below!</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>The Elder Scrolls Online in 2024 Recap—FR</b></p> 
<p>French Community Manager Geoffrey Chapron and local Stream Team members discuss what is coming to <i>ESO</i> in 2024. </p> 
<p><b>When:</b> Friday, January 19 at 12PM EST/6PM CET</p> 
<p><b>Where: </b><a href="https://www.twitch.tv/Bethesda_FR">Twitch.tv/Bethesda_FR</a></p> 
<p> </p> 
<p><b>ESO Global Reveal 2024 with Community Guests—ES</b></p> 
<p>Eurogamer España and community members break down all the latest news related to <i>ESO</i> in 2024.</p> 
<p><b>When:</b> Friday, January 19 at 3PM EST/9PM CET</p> 
<p><b>Where: </b><a href="https://www.Twitch.tv/Eurogamer_ES">Twitch.tv/Eurogamer_ES</a></p> 
<p><b><i> </i></b></p> 
<p><b>ESO 2024 Global Reveal Polish Recap—PL </b></p> 
<p>Polish Community Manager Lukasz Lesniewski and members of the local <i>ESO </i>Stream Team will talk about the latest from the 2024 Global Reveal. </p> 
<p><b>When:</b> Monday, January 22 at 3PM EST/9PM CET</p> 
<p><b>Where: </b><a href="https://www.twitch.tv/Bethesda_PL">Twitch.tv/Bethesda_PL</a></p> 
<p><b><br></b></p><p><b>Let's Explore ESO's Newest Adventures—LATAM</b></p> 
<p>LATAM members of the ESO Stream Team recap all the new <i>ESO</i> content reveals.</p> 
<p><b>When:</b> Friday, January 19 at 6PM EST/7PM MX</p> 
<p><b>Where: </b><a href="https://www.Twitch.tv/luisanc">Twitch.tv/luisanc</a></p> 
<p> </p> 
<p><b>The Future of <i>The Elder Scrolls Online—</i>TR</b></p> 
<p>Influencer and <i>ESO </i>fan Emin Çıtak discuss the future of <i>ESO </i>after all the big news from the Global Reveal. </p> 
<p><b>When:</b> Friday, January 19 at 12:30PM EST/20.30 TRT</p> 
<p><b>Where: </b><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@emincitak">YouTube.com/@emincitak</a><b> </b></p> 
<p><b><br></b></p><p><b>ESO 2024 – Recapping the Global Reveal—PT-BR</b></p> 
<p>Join Mestre Frooke and guests to discuss all the announcements and news concerning <i>ESO</i> in 2024.</p> 
<p><b>When:</b> Sunday, January 21 at 6PM EST/8PM BRT</p> 
<p><b>Where: </b><a href="https://www.twitch.tv/mestrefrooke">Twitch.tv/mestrefrooke</a> </p> 
<p><b><br></b></p><p><b>Discussing <i>ESO's </i>Latest News—IT </b></p> 
<p>Italian Community Manager Stefania Fiorese and guests from <i>ESO </i>Italia will discuss all the news announced during <i>ESO</i>'s 2024 Global Reveal.</p> 
<p><b>When:</b> Monday, January 22 at 3PM EST/9PM CET</p> 
<p><b>Where: </b><a href="https://www.twitch.tv/arvendirita">Twitch.tv/arvendirita</a> </p> 
<p><b><br></b></p><p><b>ESO 2024 Global Reveal Recap—EN GB</b></p> 
<p>UK Community Manager Ophelia and Stream Team members will chat about the <i>ESO</i> Global Reveal and what's coming in 2024.</p> 
<p><b>When:</b> Tuesday, January 23 at 9AM EST/2PM GMT</p> 
<p><b>Where: </b><a href="https://www.twitch.tv/Bethesda">Twitch.tv/Bethesda</a> </p> 
<p><b><br></b></p><p><b>Global Reveal Information with Special Guests—DE</b></p> 
<p>German Community Manage Kai Schober and special guests from the <i>ESO </i>Stream Team talk all things related to the recent Global Reveal. </p> 
<p><b>When:</b> Tuesday, January 23 at 1PM EST/7PM CET</p> 
<p><b>Where: </b><a href="https://www.Twitch.tv/Bethesda_DE">Twitch.tv/Bethesda_DE</a> </p> 
<p><b><br></b></p><p><b>Elder Scrolls Online 2024 Global Reveal Recap—BLX</b></p> 
<p>BLX Community Manager Jordy and local Stream Team members discuss everything coming to <i>ESO</i> in 2024. </p> 
<p><b>When:</b> Tuesday, January 23 at 1PM EST/7PM CET</p> 
<p><b>Where: </b><a href="https://www.twitch.tv/Bethesda_NL">Twitch.tv/Bethesda_NL</a> </p> 
<p><b><br></b></p><p><b>ESO Live—Delving into ESO's Next Adventure—EN</b></p> 
<p>Community Managers Gina Bruno and Jessica Folsom are joined by a special guest from the <i>ESO</i> Development Team to dive deep into 2024's first major release. </p> 
<p><b>When:</b> Friday, January 26 at 3PM/9PM CET</p> 
<p><b>Where:</b> <a href="https://www.twitch.tv/Bethesda">Twitch.tv/Bethesda</a></p> 
<p><br></p><p>Don't forget to catch all the big reveals by tuning in to <i>The Elder Scrolls Online</i> 2024 Global Reveal livestream this coming Thursday, January 18 on <a href="https://www.twitch.tv/Bethesda">Twitch.tv/Bethesda</a> at 4PM EST. It's only two days away—see you there!</p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Community</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/01/57789f0e26fe7ad4f328a976056d6c9f.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[One-Stop Shop: Welcome To The Elder Scrolls Online: Gold Road!]]></title>
            <link>https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/650191/one-stop-shop-welcome-to-the-elder-scrolls-online-gold-road</link>
            <guid>https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/650191/one-stop-shop-welcome-to-the-elder-scrolls-online-gold-road</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 20:55:39 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[Welcome to the One-Stop Shop for all things Global Reveal! Welcome to The Elder Scrolls Online: Gold Road!<br><br>
First, we hope everyone had a chance to watch the Global Reveal Streams. If not, no worries. We will have the <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EDZvHNg85Mc">VOD available here</a>. With that, we welcome you to the One-Stop Shop for The Elder Scrolls Online: Gold Road. Here you will find links to Our Feedback Threads and all of the information shared via our Global Reveal Livestream and the associated conversations.<br><br>
Global Reveal General Discussion Thread<br>
This is where you can post your general thoughts around everything Global Reveal. Your likes, dislikes, and everything in-between.<br><a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/650509/official-feedback-thread-for-eso-2024-global-reveal-the-elder-scrolls-online-gold-road">Link To Poll Feedback Thread</a><br><br>
Gold Road Editions and Pre-Purchase Rewards<br><a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65365">Website Article</a><br><a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/650540/official-discussion-thread-for-gold-road-editions-pre-purchase-rewards">Forum Thread Conversation</a><br><br>
The Elder Scrolls Online: Gold Road &amp; Scions of Ithelia<br><a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65359">Website Article</a><br><a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/650538/official-discussion-thread-for-the-elder-scrolls-online-gold-road-scions-of-ithelia">Forum Thread Conversation</a><br><br>
New Feature: Scribing Preview Blog<br><a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65361">Website Article</a><br><a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/650534/official-discussion-thread-for-eso-2024-global-reveal-introducing-scribing">Forum Thread Conversation</a><br><br>
New Zones: Gold Road's West Weald Zone<br><a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65363">Website Article</a><br><a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/650535/official-discussion-thread-for-eso-2024-global-reveal-gold-road-s-west-weald-zone">Forum Thread Conversation</a><br><br>
ESO Plus Free Trial<br><a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65385">Website Article</a><br><a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/650542/official-discussion-thread-for-eso-plus-free-trial">Forum Thread Conversation</a><br><br>
Gold Road Cinematic Trailer<br><span><span data-youtube="youtube-zt-ZIb2dKIw?autoplay=1"><span><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zt-ZIb2dKIw"><img src="https://img.youtube.com/vi/zt-ZIb2dKIw/0.jpg" width="640" height="385" border="0">https://youtu.be/zt-ZIb2dKIw</a></span><span></span></span></span>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>Forum</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Quest, Hunt, Pilfer, and Conquer during the Guilds and Glory Celebration Event]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65367</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65367</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Find adventure and excitement within Wrothgar, Hew's Bane, the Gold Coast, and the Imperial City during the new Guilds & Glory Celebration in-game event.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/01/0f2c8ee823f58f84e37879f9cd4c64f0.jpg" /><p><i>Find adventure and excitement within Wrothgar, Hew's Bane, the Gold Coast, and the Imperial City during the new Guilds &amp; Glory Celebration in-game event.</i></p> 
<h2>(Re)Discover Classic Adventures </h2><p> The Guilds and Glory Celebration begins Thursday, January 18 at 10AM EST, and runs until Tuesday, January 30 at 10AM EST. Throughout the event, as you quest and adventure within Wrothgar, Hew's Bane, the Gold Coast, and the Imperial City, you'll earn an assortment of bonus goodies including Reward Boxes and Event Tickets. </p> 
<p>These bonus rewards include: </p> 
<ul><li>Double reward boxes earned during Daily Quests in Wrothgar, Hew's Bane, the Gold Coast, and Imperial City as well as the Maw of Lorkhaj Weekly Quests</li><li>Double reward boxes earned during Thieves' Guild Heists and Dark Brotherhood Sacraments</li><li>Increased resource node drops </li><ul><li>This does not include fishing holes or crafting materials obtained from animals</li></ul><li>Additional loot from World Bosses in Wrothgar, Hew's Bane, and the Gold Coast as well as Delve Bosses and Public Dungeon Bosses</li><li>Additional loot from Sweepers and Coldharbour Elite Guard inside Imperial City and Imperial Sewers as well as bosses in the Maw of Lorkhaj </li><li>Additional loot from bosses in Maelstrom Arena, Imperial City Prison, and White-Gold Tower dungeons</li></ul>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/01/2eaa11226556c30ed9444d98ca52b67e.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Return to Wrothgar and other classic DLC zones</i></p> 
<p>To participate in every aspect of this new event, you will need access to the <i>Orsinium </i>DLC, the <i>Thieves Guild</i> DLC, and the <i>Dark Brotherhood </i>DLC. Each is available within the Crown Store or can be accessed via an ESO Plus membership. The <i>Imperial City</i> DLC is free for all and can be claimed from the Crown Store at no cost. </p> 
<h2>Claim Glory &amp; Rewards </h2> 
<p>During the Guilds and Glory Celebration, you can earn Glorious Reward Boxes once per day from the first daily quest completed in Wrothgar, Hew's Bane, or the Gold Coast, or by finishing the Maw of Lorkhaj weekly quest. These Reward Boxes may contain the following items:</p> 
<ul><li>Crafting materials </li><li>Saleable treasures </li><li>A style item </li><ul><li>Ancient Orc, Malacath, or Trinimac if the box is dropped in Wrothgar</li><li>Outlaw, Thieves' Guild, or Abah's Watch if the box is dropped in Hew's Bane</li><li>Assassin's League, Minotaur, Dark Brotherhood, or Order of the Hour if the box is dropped in the Gold Coast</li></ul><li>Overland item set </li><li>Companion gear </li><li>A chance for one of the following items </li><ul><li>Crafting recipes (from the zone in which you earn the box)</li><li>Treasure Maps and Survey Reports (from the zone in which you earn the box)</li><li>Motif chapters</li><ul><li>Ancient Orc, Malacath, or Trinimac if the box is dropped in Wrothgar</li><li>Outlaw, Thieves' Guild, or Abah's Watch if the box is dropped in Hew's Bane</li><li>Assassin's League, Minotaur, Dark Brotherhood, or Order of the Hour if the box is dropped in the Gold Coast</li></ul></ul><li>A chance for a Bristleback Hunter outfit style page</li></ul>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/01/8357e4d381fe5ae8af17ac6f505709f2.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Earn a host of rewards including a new style</i></p> 
<p>In addition, you can collect more common Regular Reward Boxes by completing consecutive dailies in the event-related zones. These may contain the following items: </p> 
<ul><li>Crafting materials </li><li>A chance for saleable treasures </li><li>A chance for a style item </li><ul><li>Ancient Orc, Malacath, or Trinimac if the box is dropped in Wrothgar</li><li>Outlaw, Thieves' Guild, or Abah's Watch if the box is dropped in Hew's Bane</li><li>Assassin's League, Minotaur, Dark Brotherhood, or Order of the Hour if the box is dropped in the Gold Coast</li></ul><li>Overland item set </li><li>A chance for Companion gear </li><li>A small chance for one of the following items</li><ul><li>Furnishing recipes (from the zone in which you earn the box)</li><li>Treasure Maps and Survey Reports ( from the zone in which you earn the box)</li><li>Motif chapters</li><ul><li>Ancient Orc, Malacath, or Trinimac if the box is dropped in Wrothgar</li><li>Outlaw, Thieves' Guild, or Abah's Watch if the box is dropped in Hew's Bane</li><li>Assassin's League, Minotaur, Dark Brotherhood, or Order of the Hour if the box is dropped in the Gold Coast.</li></ul></ul><li>A small chance for a Bristleback Hunter outfit style page</li></ul>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/01/142ee222ee424efc254c420573591f11.jpg" />
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/01/f4cc5bf1893cc948603ccf44ce969d71.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Pilfer or slay your way to new riches</i></p> 
<p>You may also receive a second Glorious Reward Box once per day by looting the final boss within the Imperial City Prison, White-Gold Tower, and Maelstrom Arena. These Reward Boxes may contain the following items:</p> 
<ul><li>Crafting materials </li><li>Saleable treasures </li><li>A style item </li><ul><li>Ancient Orc, Malacath, or Trinimac</li><li>Outlaw, Thieves' Guild, or Abah's Watch</li><li>Assassin's League, Minotaur, Dark Brotherhood, or Order of the Hour</li><li>Xivkyn, Aldmeri Dominion, Daggerfall Covenant, or Ebonheart Pact</li></ul><li>Dungeon item set, from Imperial City Prison, White-Gold Tower, or Maelstrom Arena</li><li>Companion gear </li><li>One of the following items </li><ul><li>Furnishing recipes</li><li>Treasure Maps and Survey Reports</li><li>Motif chapters</li><ul><li>Ancient Orc, Malacath, or Trinimac</li><li>Outlaw, Thieves' Guild, or Abah's Watch</li><li>Assassin's League, Minotaur, Dark Brotherhood, or Order of the Hour</li><li>Xivkyn, Aldmeri Dominion, Daggerfall Covenant, or Ebonheart Pact</li></ul></ul><li>A chance for a Bristleback Hunter outfit style page</li></ul> 
<p>You can also earn Regular Reward Boxes by looting the final boss of an event-related dungeon subsequent times. These may contain the following items: </p> 
<ul><li>Crafting materials </li><li>A chance for saleable treasures </li><li>A chance for a style item </li><ul><li>Ancient Orc, Malacath, or Trinimac</li><li>Outlaw, Thieves' Guild, or Abah's Watch</li><li>Assassin's League, Minotaur, Dark Brotherhood, or Order of the Hour</li><li>Xivkyn, Aldmeri Dominion, Daggerfall Covenant, or Ebonheart Pact</li></ul><li>Dungeon item set, from Imperial City Prison, White-Gold Tower, or Maelstrom Arena</li><li>A chance for Companion gear </li><li>A small chance for one of the following items </li><ul><li>Furnishing recipes</li><li>Treasure Maps and Survey Reports</li><li>Motif chapters</li><ul><li>Ancient Orc, Malacath, or Trinimac</li><li>Outlaw, Thieves' Guild, or Abah's Watch</li><li>Assassin's League, Minotaur, Dark Brotherhood, or Order of the Hour</li><li>Xivkyn, Aldmeri Dominion, Daggerfall Covenant, or Ebonheart Pact</li></ul></ul><li>A small chance for a Bristleback Hunter outfit style page</li></ul>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/01/166b7d169eea8771d741688e4d790ba7.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Battle in the heart of the empire</i></p> 
<p>Lastly, you can collect a third Glorious Reward Box once per day after you complete your first Imperial City daily quest or slay your first Sweeper boss. Additionally, there is a chance to receive a Glorious Reward Box after felling a Coldharbour Elite Guard. These Rewards Boxes may contain the following items:</p> 
<ul><li>Crafting materials </li><li>Tel Var Stones </li><li>Imperial City Key Fragments </li><li>Saleable treasures </li><li>A style item</li><ul><li>Xivkyn, Aldmeri Dominion, Daggerfall Covenant, or Ebonheart Pact<br></li></ul><li>Imperial City item set </li><li>One of the following items </li><ul><li>Furnishing Recipes from Wrothgar, Hew's Bane, or the Gold Coast</li><li>Cyrodiil Treasure Maps</li><li>Motif chapters</li><ul><li>Xivkyn, Aldmeri Dominion, Daggerfall Covenant, or Ebonheart Pact</li></ul></ul><li>A chance for a Bristleback Hunter outfit style page </li></ul> 
<p>Regular Reward Boxes may also be earned by finishing subsequent Imperial City dailies, killing additional Sweeper bosses, and defeating additional Coldharbour Elite Guards. These may contain the following items: </p> 
<ul><li>Crafting materials </li><li>Tel Var Stones </li><li>A chance for Imperial City Key Fragments </li><li>A chance for a saleable treasure </li><li>A chance for a style item</li><ul><li>Xivkyn, Aldmeri Dominion, Daggerfall Covenant, or Ebonheart Pact</li></ul><li>Imperial City item set</li><li>A chance for one of the following items </li><ul><li>Furnishing recipes from Wrothgar, Hew's Bane, or the Gold Coast</li><li>Cyrodiil Treasure Maps</li><li>Motif chapters</li><ul><li>Xivkyn, Aldmeri Dominion, Daggerfall Covenant, or Ebonheart Pact</li></ul></ul><li>A small chance for a Bristleback Hunter outfit style page </li></ul> 
<p>Additionally, you can collect further Regular Reward Boxes by participating in the following activities:</p> 
<ul><li>Slaying World Bosses in the Wrothgar, Hew's Bane, or the Gold Coast zones</li> <li>Defeating the final boss in<i> </i>Imperial City Prison, White-Gold Tower, or Maelstrom Arena dungeons</li> <li>Opening treasure chests</li> <li>Opening safeboxes</li> <li>Looting objects such as barrels, crates, etc.</li> <li>Looting Psijic portals</li> <li>Cracking open Thieves Troves</li> <li>Harvesting crafting resource nodes</li></ul> 
<p>Phew! That's a TON of ways to earn a host of bonus rewards during this massive new in-game event. Whether you're stalking your prey on behalf of the Dark Brotherhood, pilfering unsuspecting nobles with your Thieves Guild allies, battling your fellow players in the Imperial City, or delving into the politics and strife of the home of the Orcs, this event has bonus rewards for you! </p> 
<h2>Impresario &amp; Event Tickets</h2> 
<p>Of course, we can't forget about those precious Event Tickets! During the Guilds and Glory Celebration, you will receive two Event Tickets for the first of the following activities completed each day:</p> 
<ul><li>Daily Delve and World Boss quests in Wrothgar</li><li>Daily Delve, World Boss, and Thieves' Guild quests in Hew's Bane</li><li>Daily Delve, World Boss, and Dark Brotherhood quests in the Gold Coast</li><li>Daily Quests in Imperial City</li><li>Weekly Trial Quest for Maw of Lorkhaj</li><li>Killing and looting a Sweeper in Imperial City</li><li>Killing and looting a Coldharbour Elite Guard in Imperial City Sewers</li><li>Killing and looting the final boss of Imperial City Prison and White-Gold Tower</li><li>Killing and looting the final boss of Maelstrom Arena</li></ul> 
<p>By the end of the event, you could have earned an impressive 26 Tickets total! But keep in mind, you can only carry 12 Tickets at one time. To help you lighten the load, here's what the Impresario has in stock during the event:</p> 
<ul><li>All three <b>Molag Bal Illusion Imp </b>pet fragments </li><ul><li>Anchor Chain Fragment</li><li>Dark Anchor Pinion</li><li>Effigy of the Dominator</li></ul><li>The first <b>Planemeld's Master</b> marking fragment </li><ul><li>Crematory Ash</li></ul><li>Bound style pages for the following:</li><ul><li>Bristleback Hunter outfit style</li></ul><li>Stonefire Scamp Pet </li><li>Soul-Shriven Skin </li><li>Impresario Group Repair Kits</li><li>Companion Guild Commendations</li></ul>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/01/677ee127fccca9ad7e770092b8a14e2e.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>The Molag Bal Illusion Imp pet</i></p> 
<p>The Guilds and Glory Celebration is your first chance this year to purchase Crematory Ash, the first of three morphing fragments for the Planemeld's Master markings! </p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/01/2cc73bbf5b381f94f4d8772f0263a57b.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>The Planemeld's Master markings</i></p> 
<p>Additionally, the Impresario's Assistant, Philius Dormier, will gladly take your precious Event Tickets in exchange for some tantalizing treasures:</p> 
<ul><li>Unstable Morpholith Pet Fragments</li><li>Doomchar Plateau House Fragments</li></ul> 
<p>Last but not least, Nenulaure the Indrik Vendor is ready to barter away the following goodies:</p> 
<ul><li>Nascent Indrik Feathers</li><li>Dawnwood Indrik Berries</li><li>Spectral Indrik Berries</li><li>Springtide Indrik Pet</li><li>Haunting Indrik Pet</li></ul> 
<h2>Greatness Waits for No One</h2> 
<p>Adventure across Wrothgar, Hew's Bane, the Gold Coast, and the Imperial City and you'll earn a mountain of bonus rewards during the Guilds and Glory Celebration. Are you ready to find glory, honor, and untold riches during this new in-game event? Share your story with us via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">Twitter</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, or <a href="https://www.facebook.com/ElderScrollsOnline">Facebook</a>!</p> 
<p><i>The Guilds and Glory Celebration in-game event begins next Thursday, January 18 at 10AM EST, and continues until Tuesday, January 30 at 10AM EST.</i> </p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Events</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/01/0f2c8ee823f58f84e37879f9cd4c64f0.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Experience Echoes of the Planemeld with the New 2024 Morphing Event Collectible]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65351</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65351</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Show your defiance of and/or allegiance to the God of Schemes with this year's morphing collectible, the Molag Bal Illusion Imp pet!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/01/eaa278b215232163e12f83bb666f4e1b.jpg" /><p><i>Show your defiance of and/or allegiance to the God of Schemes with this year's morphing collectible, the Molag Bal Illusion Imp pet!</i></p> 
<p>Molag Bal, Daedric Prince of Brutality and Domination, has long been a menace to Tamriel. This year, throughout <i>ESO</i>'s 2024 in-game events, you can exchange your Event Tickets for a semblance of the Daedric Prince via this year's morphing collectible, the <b>Molag Bal Illusion Imp pet!</b></p> 
<p>Morphing collectibles can take many forms over the course of a year. If you're unfamiliar with how they work, you can read more about them in <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/guides/eventtickets">this guide</a>. </p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/01/677ee127fccca9ad7e770092b8a14e2e.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Molag Bal Illusion Imp Pet</i></p> 
<p>As has been the case in past years, you'll need to collect three different fragments to summon this specific collectible:</p> 
<p>· Anchor Chain Fragment</p> 
<p>· Dark Anchor Pinion</p> 
<p>· Effigy of the Dominator</p> 
<p>These three fragments will be available for purchase with Event Tickets during each of 2024's major in-game events. Just visit the Impresario during any of her appearances throughout the year to acquire them. Once you have all three fragments, combine them in your Collections to unlock access to this malevolent mite.</p> 
<p>As a morphing collectible, the Molag Bal Illusion Imp can also be combined with other fragments to summon a different collectible event reward each quarter of this year, starting with the <b>Planemeld's Master Body and Face Markings</b>.</p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/01/2cc73bbf5b381f94f4d8772f0263a57b.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Planemeld's Master Body and Face Markings</i></p> 
<p>Be sure to be on the lookout for more information on upcoming events and their reward fragments, starting with the Guilds and Glory event later this month. Are you excited to show this simulacrum of Molag Bal just who's in charge, or will you pledge your fealty to the Lord of Lies before it? Let us know via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (Formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>. </p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Events</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/01/eaa278b215232163e12f83bb666f4e1b.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Uncover the Future of Tamriel During the ESO 2024 Global Reveal]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65345</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65345</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Discover The Elder Scrolls Online's new adventures, challenges, and lore during the ESO 2024 Global Reveal livestream, hosted on Twitch.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/01/d084308b40c26d652d88fc3b29ecc89a.jpg" /><p><i>Discover The Elder Scrolls Online's new adventures, challenges, and lore during the ESO 2024 Global Reveal livestream, hosted on Twitch.</i></p> 
<p>Are you ready to find out all about what 2024 has in store for <i>ESO</i>? The Global Reveal has you covered! Tune in to <a href="https://www.twitch.tv/bethesda">Twitch.tv/Bethesda</a> for <i>The Elder Scrolls Online</i> 2024 Global Reveal on Thursday, January 18 at 4PM EST (immediately following the <a href="https://news.xbox.com/en-us/2024/01/09/xbox-developer-direct-2024/">Xbox Developer_Direct</a>). During the show, we'll give you a first look at the upcoming Chapter, as well as a glimpse at our plans for the rest of the year. Join us to see a new (yet familiar) region of Tamriel, as well as the continuation of the story that began in last year's <i>Necrom </i>Chapter. </p> 
<p>Watch the show and you'll also receive the brand-new Pyromancer's Quandary emote through Twitch Drops. Don't forget <a href="https://help.elderscrollsonline.com/app/answers/detail/a_id/41809/~/how-do-i-link-my-eso-account-to-twitch">to link your <i>ESO</i> and Twitch accounts</a> before the <i>ESO </i>2024 Global Reveal goes live so you're ready!</p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/01/de580fb5814250550ed06726505441dc.png" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>The Pyromancer's Quandary emote</i></p> 
<p>We're crafting something special this year for <i>The</i> <i>Elder Scrolls Online</i>, so be sure to join the #ESOFam in watching the livestream via <a href="https://www.twitch.tv/bethesda">Twitch.tv/Bethesda</a> starting on Thursday, January 18 at 4PM EST.</p> 
<p>Are you planning to join us for the big show? Let us know what you hope to see via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (Formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>—we'll see you there! </p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/01/d084308b40c26d652d88fc3b29ecc89a.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Crown Store Showcase—January 2024]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65239</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65239</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Start the new year off right by picking up something fun from the Crown Store this January.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/01/bbb9ed722d46779590b96775eb876a4b.jpg" /><p><i>Start the new year off right by picking up something fun from the Crown Store this January.</i></p> 
<p>Check out the complete list of contents of items coming to the Crown Store in January 2024 below. Don't forget, you can head over to the <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/crownstore">Crown Store page</a> right now to view all offers currently available and visit the <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/buycrowns">Buy Crowns page</a> to pick up however many crowns you need. Certain items and offers will only be available for a limited time, so be sure to read their details below and don't miss out.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<h2>ESO Plus Deals</h2> 
<p>All ESO Plus™ members have access to a monthly selection of exclusive deals and items. You can find more information about them in <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/54825">this article</a>.</p> 
<p><b>Exclusive Free Items</b></p> 
<p><b>Statuette: Dwemer Guardian</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/12/0b319ae6a33e1a39a8a74d15c4b385b7.jpg" />
<p><i>A miniature statue of a sentinel found outside many Dwarven ruins in Morrowind.</i></p> 
<p>The Statuette: Dwemer Guardian will be available in the Crown Store FREE exclusively to ESO Plus Members on all platforms for a limited time, from January 4 to February 15, 2024, at 10AM EST.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<h2>Adornments</h2> 
<p><b>Hair</b></p> 
<p><b>The Heroic Poet</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/12/609b0582b3d7203350d1ed0477c276e0.jpg" />
<p><i>Oh, you romantic devil, tossing off quatrains and epigrams as you charge into battle to defend the underdog! You know who you are, and this is your hair.</i></p> 
<p>The Heroic Poet hairstyle will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from January 8 to January 11, 2024, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Hat</b></p> 
<p><b>Deep Elf Executioner's Hood</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/12/bd502df3f0d2e4c6a71ae06086977db1.jpg" />
<p><i>Ancient engravings tell us that a Dwarven executioner, or "Chun Abakch," always concealed his or her features under a hood of black spidersilk, a material that was also used by the Dwemer for funeral shrouds.</i></p> 
<p>The Deep Elf Executioner's Hood Hat returns to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from January 8 to January 11, 2024, at 10AM EST.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Tattoos</b></p> 
<p><b>Meridian Sunburst Face Tattoos</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/12/3867adadae17a40d474d09abc7132ad1.jpg" />
<p><i>Celebrate the brightest light of all the Lady's Infinite Energies with these glowing Meridian Sunburst Tattoos.</i></p> 
<p>The Meridian Sunburst Face Tattoos will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from January 11 to January 18, 2024, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Meridian Sunburst Body Tattoos</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/12/df97c18c01dd8db1f539100511aab0fc.jpg" />
<p><i>Celebrate the brightest light of all the Lady's Infinite Energies with these glowing Meridian Sunburst Tattoos.</i></p> 
<p>The Meridian Sunburst Body Tattoos will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from January 11, 2024, to January 18, 2024, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Skins</h2> 
<p><b>Opalescent Epidermis</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/12/1db81520828c7951a22e935c945bad54.jpg" />
<p><i>Shimmer with a variety of hues, taking on the colors of the famed opals of Yokuda, with this skin. Perfect for star-strewn celebrations in Sentinel and beyond.</i></p> 
<p>The Opalescent Epidermis skin will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms starting January 16 to January 22, 2024, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Wardrobe</h2> 
<p><b>Costumes</b></p> 
<p><b>Toxin Doctor</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/12/c6d43493ef3174f06fc87b818afd56d0.jpg" />
<p><i>When you specialize in venoms and poison-making, you invest in special protective garb to keep from being poisoned by your own experiments—or else! And if your clients are just a little intimidated by your creepy attire, all the better.</i></p> 
<p>The Toxin Doctor costume will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from January 2 to January 8, 2024, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Auroran Knight</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/12/1f5691259d8f9e8ac659d06b87c488ea.jpg" />
<p><i>Aurorans are idealized humanoid Daedra mainly in the service of Meridia, the Lady of Infinite Energies. Their armor usually appears golden in tone, but since they come from the Colored Rooms, they could be of any hue.</i></p> 
<p>The Auroran Knight costume will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from January 11 to January 18, 2024, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Gem Prospector</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/12/d5ed10b6b128b348365cacf114b6d488.jpg" />
<p><i>If you love chipping away at rock until you reveal raw gemstone, garb yourself appropriately. Crafted from sturdy materials, this costume features pockets, pouches, and gear that allow you to better find and remove natural riches.</i></p> 
<p>The Gem Prospector costume paired with the Gemcutter's Spectacles adornment will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from January 16 to January 22, 2024, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Imperial Officer Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/12/1dc828487e8564137b7bba70ff5845e8.jpg" />
<p><i>This pack includes costumes of three different armor sets as worn by Tribunes and Centurions of the Imperial Legions. Hail the Red Diamond!</i></p> 
<p>The Imperial Officer Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from January 22 to January 25, 2024, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Orc Wise Woman's Vestment</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/12/d73f8faf7e13c652df4181dd44cdcd8b.jpg" />
<p><i>"As the Wise Woman of your clan, or the Hunt-Wife on ceremonial days, you must project both grace and authority," says designer Borzighu the Tidy. "Count on my gilt-broidered vestment to provide that, and more!"</i></p> 
<p>The Orc Wise Woman's Vestment costume will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from January 25 to January 29, 2024, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Soul-Shriven Costume Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/12/4b4b8445193cc4c20fdb9236b0750c45.jpg" />
<p><i>When the Soul-Shriven arrive in Coldharbour, they are garbed in cast-off armor taken from the dead. This pack includes costumes in various states of raggedness.</i></p> 
<p>The Soul-Shriven Costume Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from January 29 to February 1, 2024, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Crafting</h2> 
<p><b>Motifs</b></p> 
<p><b>Crown Crafting Motif: Dreadhorn Style</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/12/f972fbe586c37a3f5b2ef04a4aba9ef3.jpg" />
<p><i>Gherig Bullblood proclaims, “Wayward sons and daughters, embrace Domihaus and set to work to outfit our reborn clan—as the Dreadhorn!" Use of this motif enables crafting in the Dreadhorn style.</i></p> 
<p>The Crown Crafting Motifs: Dreadhorn returns to the Crown Store on all platforms starting January 2 to January 8, 2024, at 10AM EST. Dreadhorn Motif chapters, and very rarely the complete book, have a chance to drop from Domihaus the Bloody-Horned in Falkreath Hold.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Crown Crafting Motif: Silver Dawn</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/12/77c5fa680136cb0f76cc4fef306ec12e.jpg" />
<p><i>Hunt for heinous were-creatures with pride wearing and wielding the traditional arms and armor of the Order of the Silver Dawn! By the gleam of silver shall we slay! Use to learn the Silver Dawn crafting style.</i></p> 
<p>The Crown Crafting Motif: Silver Dawn returns to the Crown Store on all platforms starting January 16 to January 22, 2024, at 10AM EST. Silver Dawn Motif chapters, and very rarely the complete book, have a chance to drop from Vykosa the Ascendant in Moon Hunter Keep.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Crown Crafting Motif: New Moon Priest</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/12/c6420d35ef8ce18917427bee398665fa.jpg" />
<p><i>The Arcane Quartermaster of Order of the New Moon states, "Some believe that the order grows too quickly. This one says we should embrace newcomers and provide appropriate priestly garments! Fadai gladly offers guidance on crafting vestments and how best to incorporate aeonstones into them." Use to learn the New Moon Priest crafting style. Also acquired from the Dragonguard Supply Chest in the Dragonguard Santum.</i></p> 
<p>The Crown Crafting Motif: New Moon Priest will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms starting January 25 to January 29, 2024, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item. New Moon Priest Motif chapters can be acquired from the Dragonguard Supply Chest in the Dragonguard Sanctum.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Outfit Styles</b></p> 
<p><b>Elder Scrolls Artifact: Rueful Axe</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/12/539699f448344ec0ea5da162b69eb074.jpg" />
<p><i>Alter your two-handed axe's Outfit style with a replica of the Rueful Axe Elder Scrolls Artifact, a weapon created by the Daedric Prince Clavicus Vile.</i></p> 
<p>The Elder Scrolls Artifact: Rueful Axe will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms starting January 2 to January 11, 2024, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Gloambound Arms Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/12/98e0006a0de4769a8e248832aadb075d.jpg" />
<p><i>Need a weapon in a hurry? Let the Evergloam provide! Alter your weapon's appearance to match the Gloambound Weapons by using this complete set of Outfit styles. Stowing these weapons will hide them when equipped.</i></p> 
<p>The Gloambound Arms Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms starting January 4 to January 11, 2024, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Lord Warden Arms Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/12/f3e0a07a6a0d3b53fc67121ce09557d5.jpg" />
<p><i>Urgarlag Chief-bane notes to Undaunted pledgers, "The Lord Warden obsessively keeps record of every indignity he's inflicted. Wipe the record clean before you turn the tables on him." Alter your weapon's appearance to match the Undaunted Lord Warden awards by using this complete set of Outfit styles.</i></p> 
<p>The Lord Warden Arms Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms starting January 16 to January 22, 2024, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item. The matching mask page will have a small chance to drop from Lord Warden Dusk from Veteran Imperial City Prison. The matching shoulder page can be purchased from Urgarlag Chief-bane for 50 Undaunted keys, or has a chance of dropping from Urgarlag's Mystery Coffer for 1 key. Having the achievement “Lord Warden's Retaliation” increases the drop chances of both items.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Elder Scrolls Artifact: Dawnbreaker</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/12/6e38496cd868af4df734add8c7d98590.jpg" />
<p><i>Alter your one-handed weapon's Outfit style with a replica of the Dawnbreaker Elder Scrolls Artifact, a weapon forged by the Daedric Prince Meridia. </i></p> 
<p>The Elder Scrolls Artifact: Dawnbreaker will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms starting January 11 to January 18, 2024, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Bristleback Hunter Arms Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/12/85a6b61806b4be5dfb5e041d371de324.jpg" />
<p><i>Keama of Markarth says, “When I see someone wearing this gear swagger into the Hunter's Repose, I know we'll have a full night of near-death stories. Bristlebacks take skill and luck to kill.” Alter your weapon's appearance by using this complete set of Bristleback Hunter Outfit styles.</i></p> 
<p>The new Bristleback Hunter Arms Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms during the Guilds and Glory Celebration event. Matching armor pages will have a small chance to drop from Event Reward Boxes. Bound versions of the armor pages can be purchased from the Impresario for 5 Event Tickets each during the event.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Crate</h2> 
<p><b>Psijic Vault Crate </b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/12/6da3926890653f7ebbefd9ec9b6bee11.jpg" />
<p><i>A mystery collection of Psijic Order-related items! </i></p> 
<p>Psijic Vault Crates return to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from January 18 to February 1, 2024, at 10AM EST.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<h2>Events </h2> 
<p><b>Currency</b></p> 
<p><b>Event Tickets</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/74f679e610302be57199309573dd3a29.jpg" />
<p><i>A ticket used to purchase rare goods from The Impresario, Event Merchant. Curious as to what goods? Well, chat with her to see what she has to offer!</i></p> 
<p>Single Event Tickets will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time during the Guilds and Glory Celebration in-game event. Stay tuned for event details!</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<h2>Bundles</h2> 
<p><b>Highland Spotted Lynx Bundle</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/12/42442f097d78510b29f85f3e0e5b110f.jpg" />
<p><i>From curious cub to lithe mount, the spotted lynxes found in the Colovian highlands help keep the area free of vermin and often serve as mounts to worthy souls. This feline bundle allows you to add these two furry friends to your adventures.</i></p> 
<p>The new Highland Spotted Lynx Bundle will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from January 22 to January 29, 2024, at 10AM EST.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<h2>Furniture </h2> 
<p><b>Statue, Ancestor-King Auri-El</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/12/cecc6036940fc62449f7f4011321fa18.jpg" />
<p><i>Ayleid artist-enchanters captured the might of the king of the Aldmer and his avian companion in this commanding statue! Light up this focal piece with the eagle's golden glow, Auri-El's lambent eyes, scintillating sunbeams, or a combination of these.</i></p> 
<p>The Statue, Ancestor-King Auri-El will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from January 4 to January 11, 2024, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Island Assortment Household Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/12/35990c61d7b080072e9db4b2ac493d4e.jpg" />
<p><i>A selection of household necessities drawn from cultures across southern Tamriel, ideal for the Grand Topal Hideaway.</i></p> 
<p>The Island Assortment Household Pack returns to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from January 4 to January 11, 2024, at 10AM EST.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Meridia, Lady of Infinite Energies</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/12/556e305df00cb09d4547ebecc34fe8b9.jpg" />
<p><i>"[…] above all others they did venerate the Lady of Light, building for Merid-Nunda a chapel of colored rays and beams, which was for glory like a piece of Aetherius brought down to the mortal world […]"—The Whithering of Delodiil (Author Unknown)</i></p> 
<p>The Meridia, Lady of Infinite Energies statue will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from January 11, 2024, to January 18, 2024, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Music Box, Dawnbreaker's Forging</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/12/563b5889bd6efcad0278dc76eabebb31.jpg" />
<p><i>When activated, plays a music box arrangement of the exultant "Dawnbreaker's Forging" composition. </i></p> 
<p>The new Music Box, Dawnbreaker's Forging will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from January 11 to January 18, 2024, at 10AM EST.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Furnishing Pack: Malacath's Chosen </b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2022/08/82f7d87a4b590e8b9947815d4b4125a5.jpg" />
<p><i>Honor Malacath and his Orc-children with these furnishings from the ancient mountain strongholds of Wrothgar. </i></p> 
<p>The Furnishing Pack: Malacath's Chosen will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from January 18 to January 25, 2024, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Furnishing Pack: Hubalajad's Final Treasure</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/12/2249c8b4880594736df63dc25727982f.jpg" />
<p><i>No Prince of the Ra Gada would be caught dead without the appropriate (and extravagant) funerary offerings for his tomb. Not to mention the requisite Mournful Aegis to welcome any unexpected guests!</i></p> 
<p>The Furnishing Pack: Hubalajad's Final Treasure returns to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from January 25 to February 1, 2024, at 10AM EST.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<h2>Houses</h2> 
<p><b>Colossal Aldmeri Grotto </b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/12/4b463e5e6e147c67b73335bfa54f5171.jpg" />
<p><i>Once a watering stop for the High Elf navy, this great cavernous grotto on the Summerset coast west of Dusk features shipboard compartments, magnificent Aldmeri ruins, weathered wood from several shipwrecks, and a sparkling subterranean waterfall.</i></p> 
<p>The Colossal Aldmeri Grotto returns to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from January 4 to January 18, 2024, at 10AM EST. Furnished and unfurnished versions will be available.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Pariah's Pinnacle </b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/12/29eea0827e86071816cd875c0eb607eb.jpg" />
<p><i>The grand and majestic mountaintop retreat of Baloth Bloodtusk was sealed off in the First Era by King Joile, but its ancient Orcish halls were recently reopened by order of King Kurog. </i></p> 
<p>The Pariah's Pinnacle returns to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from January 18 to January 25, 2024, at 10AM EST. Furnished and unfurnished versions will be available.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Thieves' Oasis</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/12/a6fab78fee45f5acab54bc17c53a7112.jpg" />
<p><i>With its mix of Redguard architecture, both old and new, Thieves' Oasis features a stunning waterfall, ancient statues, and housing fit for a prince—whether that prince is a scholarly antiquarian or roguish thief.</i></p> 
<p>The Thieves' Oasis returns to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from January 25 to February 8, 2024, at 10AM EST. Furnished and unfurnished versions will be available.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Houseguests</h2> 
<p><b>Captain Isara Davaux</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2022/09/4990e7e4fbb9e6bc244c12a5d4ea9138.jpg" />
<p><i>Ghostly Isara may think she's still part of the All Flags Navy, fighting their ancient foes, but that just makes her a hauntingly novel guest. After adding Isara to your home, you can set her on a path, plus you and your visitors can speak with her.</i></p> 
<p>Captain Isara Davaux returns to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from January 4 to January 11, 2024, at 10AM EST.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>M'aiq the Liar </b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/12/6c495f6e8fe94c0b62f9db0b8ce6a85b.jpg" />
<p><i>The Khajiit called M'aiq the Liar travels widely, speaking foolishly—or wisely, depending on whom you ask. Host him before deciding, yes? After adding M'aiq to your home, you can set him on a path, plus you and your visitors can speak with him. </i></p> 
<p>M'aiq the Liar will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from January 18 to January 25, 2024, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Mounts</h2> 
<p><b>Snow Bear</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/12/3d0c410bf589cd4533118c5f554cd1b9.jpg" />
<p><i>The Snow Bear makes a superior mount for northern climes, as it's undaunted by even the fiercest winter weather.</i></p> 
<p>The Snow Bear mount will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from January 2 to January 8, 2024, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Harpy's Bane Durzog</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/12/cad79414d8be811fab06eebe5e39f616.jpg" />
<p><i>"All durzog are relentless in the pursuit of prey, but this sub-species is particularly vicious, especially when following a harpy's scent. Even experienced handlers sometimes struggle to contain their ferocity on the hunt."—Elsweyr: A Rider's Guide</i></p> 
<p>The Harpy's Bane Durzog mount will be available to ESO Plus Members in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from January 2 to February 1, 2024, at 10AM EST.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Auroran Zenith Warwolf</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/12/763ea0219cb7003e8b9b4d5837c53490.jpg" />
<p><i>Followers of Meridia who assist Aurorans can gain enough favor to earn one of their wolf steeds. Trained for war, these wolves stay the course even in siege situations, making them excellent mounts for all manner of dangerous situations.</i></p> 
<p>The Auroran Zenith Warwolf Mount will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from January 11 to January 18, 2024, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<p><i> </i></p> 
<p><b>Great Elk</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/12/e97674071b7f840bbc2cd52153ecb499.jpg" />
<p><i>Though the Reachmen of Markarth say they were the first to successfully domesticate the Great Elk of Skyrim and break them as mounts, the Nords of Haafingar say it was really all their idea.</i></p> 
<p>The Great Elk Mount returns to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from January 11 to January 18, 2024, at 10AM EST. </p> 
<p><i> </i></p> 
<h2>Pets</h2> 
<p><b>Blue Shock Nixad</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/12/634c4c54134533033d72feb70d5e4444.jpg" />
<p><i>The rare and colorful Shock Nixad looks rather like a tiny, winged Storm Atronach, though without the whirling electric rocks. They make loyal companions—though they may also make your hair stand on end!</i></p> 
<p>The Blue Shock Nixad pet will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from January 2 to January 8, 2024, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<p><b>Seht's Dovah-Fly </b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/12/c1cc88be5ea7658a3f6e096048766a57.jpg" />
<p><i>These are clearly fabricants, clockwork simulations of living creatures, with the distinctive appearance of the handiwork of Sotha Sil. But if so, how did they escape Clockwork City? What powers them? And why do they make such loyal pets? No one knows. </i></p> 
<p>The Seht's Dovah-Fly pet<b> </b>will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from January 8 to January 11, 2024, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Mudcrab of Eternal Doom</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/12/92d21405cef837b7251c5404429a8a78.jpg" />
<p><i>Few can withstand the scorching heat and relentless desolation of the Deadlands. Those unlucky few who find themselves trapped there may encounter one of these scuttling horrors—a hideous reminder of their grim and eternal fate.</i></p> 
<p>The Mudcrab of Eternal Doom pet returns to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from January 16 to January 22, 2024, at 10AM EST. </p> 
<p> </p> 
<p><b>Colovian Badger </b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/12/b7d6a325799cd1e3016632001f8eda05.jpg" />
<p><i>Though Badgers mainly eat burrowing rodents, farmers hate them because they'll take chickens, kwama scribs, and bantam guar if they get the chance. Cranky and irritable, they make terrible pets—which makes them a favorite among the Undaunted. </i></p> 
<p>The Colovian Badger pet will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from January 22 to January 25, 2024, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<p> </p> 
<p><b>Psijic Mascot Bear Cub</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2021/12/3a392d97accc227a717510b0c959a43e.jpg" />
<p><i>By tradition, the Psijic Mascot of the order's Ritemaster is always a Bear Cub—but since there's been only one Ritemaster, Iachesis, for over 3,000 years, the tradition hasn't had much opportunity to change. Fortunately, others can befriend them as well!</i></p> 
<p>The Psijic Mascot Bear Cub pet will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from January 25 to February 1, 2024, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<p> </p> 
<p><b>White River Ice Wolf Pup</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/12/6ab069568909301fbbb802fa5ed5593c.jpg" />
<p><i>The Ice Wolves that lope along the White River of northeast Skyrim are associated with both the goddess Mara and the Wolf Totem of Atmora—but it's mighty hard to think of their mythic stature when you're rolling around in the snow with an Ice Wolf Puppy!</i></p> 
<p>The White River Ice Wolf Pup pet will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from January 29 to February 5, 2024, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<p> </p> 
<h2>Polymorph</h2> 
<p><b>Draugr</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/12/6d10283e253a43e1b091c128ef24a05a.jpg" />
<p><i>This guise makes the wearer appear to have withered flesh beneath ancient Nord armor—perfect for lurking in tombs.</i></p> 
<p>The Draugr polymorph returns to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from January 8 to January 16, 2024, at 10AM EST.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Wraith-of-Crows</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/12/3aa981b3b739614db2b55e1d3633e819.jpg" />
<p><i>Pay homage to Nocturnal the Night Mistress by assuming the appearance of her horrific half-bird servant!</i></p> 
<p>The Wraith-of-Crows polymorph will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from January 25 to February 1, 2024, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p>Whether guided by Meridia or the New Moon, you'll dazzle everyone you meet in 2024 with January's new and returning Crown Store items. Don't forget to visit the <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/buycrowns">Buy Crowns page</a> if you need to stock up on crowns first. Even better, be sure to check out this month's <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65237" target="_blank">Daily Login Rewards</a> and claim that free mount! Do any of the items in this month's Crown Store take your fancy? Tell us via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, or <a href="https://www.facebook.com/ElderScrollsOnline">Facebook</a>!</p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Crown Store</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/01/bbb9ed722d46779590b96775eb876a4b.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Daily Login Rewards—January 2024]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65237</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65237</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Get a swift start to the new year with these in-game rewards available simply by logging in to ESO during January 2024.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/12/7147eded58425c213581c077e7ea53a5.jpg" /><p><i>Get a swift start to the new year with these in-game rewards available simply by logging in to ESO during January 2024.</i></p> 
<p>The new year is coming in hot, and you can expect a variety of exciting rewards each day you log in this January. You can see some examples of what to expect listed below, including a mighty mount, copious stacks of riding lessons, and an abundance of experience scrolls. Just be sure to claim them from the Daily Rewards section of the in-game Crown Store. If you need assistance, you can turn to <a href="https://help.elderscrollsonline.com/#en/answer/41950">this help article</a>.</p> 
<p><b>Gnisis Durzog Mount—Day 2</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/12/b6400a5fe408a7f684af475990c6d9bb.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>A hardy mount on top of which you can take on the new year. </i></p> 
<p>The breeders of House Redoran have outdone themselves with this fine specimen of durzog. Sort of clever, mostly loyal, and largely unlikely to maul passerby without permission. Truly a marvel of the species! Do try not to leave it unsupervised near a kwama mine, though. We have it on good authority it has an appetite for scribs.</p> 
<p><b>Crown Lessons: Riding Speed ×3—Days 3, 6, and 21</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/06/cbe274a5829d962f623d632f5cd9af09.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Go off to the races with these boosts to your riding speed!</i></p> 
<p>We're hitting the ground running—or galloping—with this collection of Riding Lessons to increase your character's mount speed offered on each of three different days. Hurry along and get started in the new year posthaste.</p> 
<p><b>Crown Lessons: Riding Capacity ×3—Day 4</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/11/3ccea04ad2ca7e229b5963807211dc85.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>More space in your saddlebags for whatever the new year brings.</i></p> 
<p>The new year often brings new challenges—and new loot. These Riding Lessons can help you deal with the loot and prevent inventory management from becoming one of the challenges!</p> 
<p><b>Crown Lessons: Riding Stamina ×3—Day 5</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/07/e1badfaedd129de798109b389a22658c.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Hit the trail, take a hike, do whatever you like as these lessons teach your mount to endure.</i></p> 
<p>As you spur your mount on to explore new sights and scenes across Tamriel, teach it to stay at its best with these Riding Lessons that improve mount stamina.</p> 
<p><b>Grand Gold Coast Experience Scroll ×2—Day 7</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/06/1f7bf97587039a52547d3df74a2632bc.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Experience all the new year has to offer!</i></p> 
<p>Your mount isn't the only one who can train up. Earn 150% more experience with these two Grand Gold Coast Experience Scrolls and finish that new year's resolution to get more Champion points early!</p> 
<p><b>Seals of Endeavor ×250—Day 14</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/10/cbf054f9fa4122ee9be26996607da8d2.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Start life's new endeavors with some Seals of Endeavor!</i></p> 
<p>And adding to all the previous rewards, we have some 250 Seals of Endeavor you can claim for use on Crown Crate items. Get your supplies off to an early start in 2024 with these Seals! You can also earn Seals from Daily and Weekly Endeavors in-game and use them to buy goods contained in Crown Crates or normally purchased with Crown Gems. Learn more about Seals of Endeavor <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/59925">in this blog</a>.</p> 
<p>What are you looking forward to most for the new year in Tamriel? Tell us your plans and what you hope to accomplish with these rewards! Share it with us via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (Formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>. </p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Daily Rewards</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/12/7147eded58425c213581c077e7ea53a5.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Happy Holidays! Claim a Free Adornment as a Gift from Us]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65235</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65235</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The Effigy Earrings of Saint Vorys are now available free within the Crown Store until January 2024—don't miss out!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/12/b3cc8320b0486bd447968c49dbc50aec.jpg" /><p><i>The Effigy Earrings of Saint Vorys are now available free within the Crown Store until January 2024—don't miss out!</i></p> 
<p>Across Tamriel as well as lands more mundane, this is the season for holiday cheer and gifts. In the spirit of this season, you can now claim the free Effigy Earrings of Saint Vorys adornment from the Featured page of the in-game Crown Store as a gift from us! Once you claim it from the Crown Store, the adornment can be found in your Collections under the Appearance tab.</p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/12/5791f9d7f747be3e8a95413173e5255f.png" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Claim this free adornment from us!</i></p> 
<p>This stylish adornment is available <b>now until January 4, 2024, at 10 AM EST</b>, so be sure to add it to your collection the next time you visit Tamriel. </p> 
<p>These earrings honor the patron saint of House Telvanni, Saint Vorys the Immolant. Whether you plan to wear them to honor the Telvanni ancestors or simply as a fashion statement, we hope you enjoy this holiday gift from us!</p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Crown Store</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/12/b3cc8320b0486bd447968c49dbc50aec.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Discover Seasonal Savings on Necrom, Base Game, and Select Crown Packs During the 2023 Holiday Sale]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65251</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65251</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Enjoy up to 67% off the Necrom Chapter and up to 40% off select Crown Packs during ESO's end-of-year sale.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/12/2b0ede28c6af4028e3550c2684b9f64c.jpg" /><p><i>Enjoy up to 67% off the Necrom Chapter and up to 40% off select Crown Packs during ESO's end-of-year sale.</i></p> 
<h2>'Tis the Season for Savings!</h2> 
<p>The 2023 <i>ESO</i> Holiday Sale is now live, allowing you to pick up <i>The Elder Scrolls Online: Necrom</i> Chapter at up to 67% off and <i>The Elder Scrolls Online: Standard Edition </i>at up to 70% off<i>.</i> These festive deals are available across all platforms, including Xbox (Xbox One, Xbox Series X|S), PlayStation (PlayStation 4, PlayStation 5), and PC/Mac (The Elder Scrolls Online Store, Steam, Epic Games Store).</p> 
<p>These seasonal savings are available for all versions of the <i>Necrom</i> Chapter (<i>Collection</i>, <i>Deluxe Collection</i>, <i>Upgrade</i>, and <i>Deluxe Upgrade</i>), offering you the opportunity to explore the mushroom forests of the Telvanni Peninsula, navigate through the twisted realm of Apocrypha, and master the power of the new Arcanist class!</p> 
<p>To get started, visit our <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/joinus" target="_blank">Buy Now page</a> and select your edition.</p><p>In addition to savings on the latest Chapter and base game, we're also providing some major discounts on Crown Packs:</p><ul><li>21,000 Crowns—Up to 40% off</li><li>14,000 Crowns—Up to 35% off</li><li>5,500 Crowns—Up to 30% off</li><li>3,000 Crowns—Up to 25% off</li><li>1,500 Crowns—Up to 20% off</li></ul><p>Ready to take advantage of these limited-time savings? Head over to the <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/crowns">Buy Crowns page</a> to grab your bundle of choice. You can use these crowns to purchase all sorts of practical and cosmetic items from the in-game Crown Store such as pets, costumes, houses, skill lines, XP scrolls, and more. Check out what offers are currently available by visiting the <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/crownstore/">Crown Store page</a>.</p><p>Both discounts are available for a limited time and may conclude on different dates depending on your platform and territory. To discover when your platform's sale ends, check out the schedule below:</p><p><b>Xbox</b></p><ul><li><i>Standard Edition</i>—December 14, 2023-January 3, 2024</li><li><i>Necrom</i>—December 14, 2023-January 3, 2024</li><li>Crown Packs—December 14, 2023-January 3, 2024</li></ul><p><b>PlayStation America</b></p><ul><li><i>Standard Edition</i>—December 20, 2023-January 6, 2024</li><li><i>Necrom</i>—December 20, 2023-January 6, 2024</li><li>Crown Packs—December 20, 2023-January 6, 2024</li></ul><p><b>PlayStation Europe</b></p><ul><li><i>Standard Edition</i>—December 19, 2023-January 5, 2024</li><li><i>Necrom</i>—December 19, 2023-January 5, 2024</li><li>Crown Packs—December 19, 2023-January 5, 2024</li></ul><p><b>PlayStation Asia</b></p><ul><li><i>Standard Edition</i>—December 19, 2023-January 5, 2024</li><li><i>Necrom</i>—December 19, 2023-January 5, 2024</li><li>Crown Packs—December 19, 2023-January 5, 2024</li></ul><p><b>Elder Scrolls Online Store</b></p><ul><li><i>Standard Edition</i>—December 21, 2023-January 4, 2024</li><li><i>Necrom</i>—December 21, 2023-January 4, 2024</li><li>Crown Packs—December 21, 2023-January 4, 2024</li></ul><p><b>Steam Store</b></p><ul><li><i>Standard Edition</i>—December 21, 2023-January 4, 2024</li><li><i>Necrom</i>—December 21, 2023-January 4, 2024</li><li>Crown Packs—December 21, 2023-January 4, 2024</li></ul><p><b>Epic Games Store</b></p><ul><li><i>Standard Edition</i>—December 13, 2023-January 10, 2024</li><li><i>Necrom</i>—December 13, 2023-January 10, 2024</li><li>Crown Packs—December 21, 2023-January 4, 2024</li></ul><p>With these discounts on the <i>Necrom</i> Chapter, base game, and Crown Packs, there's a host of new adventures waiting for you this festive season. Which of these deals are you considering taking advantage of during the 2023 <i>ESO</i> Holiday Sale? Let us know via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (Formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Necrom</category>
            <category>Sales</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/12/2b0ede28c6af4028e3550c2684b9f64c.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Complete Merry Quests & Earn Special Rewards During the New Life Festival Event!]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65233</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65233</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Spread holiday cheer while enjoying bonus XP gains and seasonal rewards during this year's New Life Festival.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/12/7fb58ed22b9ed6eb2d51e46ecf196a49.jpg" /><p><i>Spread holiday cheer while enjoying bonus XP gains and seasonal rewards during this year's New Life Festival.</i></p> 
<h2>Warm Wishes for a Happy Holiday</h2> 
<p>The 2023 New Life Festival in-game event begins Thursday, December 21, 2023, at 10AM EST, and continues until Tuesday, January 9, 2024, at 10AM EST. During this year's festivities, you can earn a variety of jolly rewards including New Life Boxes, XP boosts, Event Tickets, and more.</p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2021/12/06a63559559303a3d0f3ec1d0d0e98a8.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Find Breda in Eastmarch to begin</i></p> 
<p>During the New Life Festival, you will automatically enjoy a 100% boost to XP gain whenever you log into the game, with no extra steps required! If you'd like to join the party and toast the passing of another year, complete the New Life Festival's introductory quest and collect Breda's Bottomless Mead Mug memento via the following steps:</p> 
<ol><li>Open the Crown Store and acquire the free quest, “The New Life Festival.”</li><ul><li>You can also pick up this quest by speaking with Breda at the New Life Festival tent in Eastmarch. </li><ul><li>You can instantly transport yourself to Breda by using the portal located at any Impresario tent location.</li></ul></ul><li>Complete the introductory quest to receive the Breda's Bottomless Mead Mug memento.</li><ul><li>You won't need to acquire Breda's Bottomless Mead Mug if you finished the quest during a previous year.</li></ul><li>Enjoy your endless supply of winter spiced mead!</li></ol> 
<p>After wrapping up the event's introductory quest, you'll unlock 10 special New Life Festival daily quests: nine from Breda and one from Petronius Galenus. The pair will task you to travel across the vastness of Tamriel and share seasonal merriment with its denizens.</p> 
<h2>Good Deeds, Great Rewards</h2> 
<p>Whenever you complete one of the 10 daily quests, you'll be rewarded with a New Life Festival Box. Contained inside these seasonal cases is the chance to receive the following rewards:</p> 
<ul><li>Assortments of alchemy crafting materials </li><li>New Life Festival Toys: </li><ul><li>Sword Swallower Kit</li><li>Juggling Knives</li><li>Fire-Breather's Torches</li><li>Mudballs</li></ul><li>Wolfsbane Incense </li><li>One of the following: </li><ul><li>A Skinchanger motif page</li><li>New Life Festival Recipes</li><li>New Life Furnishings</li><li>Deep Winter Charity Writs</li><li>Imperial Charity Writs</li></ul><li>A <i>chance</i> for one of the following:</li><ul><li>An Evergreen outfit style page</li><li><b>NEW</b> A Morningstar Frostwear outfit style page</li><ul><li>If you've already earned a Morningstar Frostwear page that day, an Evergreen outfit style page or a Nord Carved armor outfit style page will be given instead</li></ul></ul></ul>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/12/9564abde54b5b07e0516046e09da2a40.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Earn a new armor style</i></p> 
<h2>Impresario &amp; Event Tickets</h2> 
<p>The first New Life Festival daily quest you complete each day rewards three Event Tickets in addition to the reward box. You can earn up to a colossal <b>60 Event Tickets</b> by the event's end! Don't forget that you can only ever hold up to 12 Event Tickets in your inventory at once.</p> 
<p>During the New Life Festival, the Impresario will update her stock with the following items:</p> 
<ul><li>All three <b>Passion Dancer Blossom </b>pet fragments </li><li>All components for this year's morphing collectibles:</li><ul><li>Passion's Muse personality</li><li>Meadowbreeze Memories skin</li><li>Passion Dancer Garment costume</li></ul><li>All three <b>Hoardhunter Ursauk</b> mount fragments</li><ul><li>Blessed Honeycomb</li><li>Gilded and Dyed Saddle</li><li>Sorcerous Golden Ink</li></ul><li>Bound style pages for the following:</li><ul><li><b>NEW</b> Morningstar Frostwear pages </li></ul><li>New Life Festival Grab Bag </li><ul><li>Mud Ball Pouch memento</li><li>Nordic Bather's Towel costume</li><li>Colovian Fur Hood hat</li><li>Colovian Filigreed Hood hat</li><li>Sword-Swallower's Blade memento</li><li>Juggler's Knives memento</li><li>Fire-Breather's Torches memento</li><li>Snowball Buddy pet</li><li>Powderwhite Coney pet</li></ul><li>Impresario Group Repair Kits</li><li>Companion Guild Commendations</li></ul> 
<p>The New Life Festival is also your last chance to pick up the third fragment needed to construct this year's final event Morphing Collectible, the Hoardhunter Ursauk mount!</p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/11/b3a53d6fcf9e1741482c56e2734daf3f.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>The Hoardhunter Ursauk</i></p> 
<p>Additionally, the Impresario's colleague, Nenulaure the Indrik Vendor, has the following items available for purchase with Event Tickets:</p> 
<ul><li>Nascent Indrik Feathers</li><li>Pure Snow Indrik Berries</li><li>Crimson Indrik Berries</li><li>Frost-Light Indrik Pet</li><li>Rosethorn Indrik Pet</li></ul> 
<p>Lastly, the Impresario's Assistant is offering the following, which you can also acquire with Event Tickets:</p> 
<ul><li>Unstable Morpholith fragments</li><ul><li>Deadlands Flint</li><li>Rune-Etched Striker</li><li>Smoldering Bloodgrass Tinder</li></ul><li>Dagonic Quasigriff fragments</li><ul><li>Smoke-Wreathed Gryphon Feather</li><li>Black Iron Bit</li><li>Bridle Black Iron Stirrups</li></ul></ul> 
<h2>Tamriel Rings in the New Year</h2> 
<p>As this year draws to a close, you can send 2023 off in merry style during the New Life Festival and collect some special event rewards as you do. How do you plan to spend the holidays in <i>ESO</i>? Let us know and be sure to share any fun New Life-themed creations with us via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (Formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, or <a href="https://www.facebook.com/ElderScrollsOnline">Facebook</a>. </p> 
<p><i>The New Life Festival in-game event begins this Thursday, December 21 at 10AM EST, and continues until Wednesday, January 9 at 10AM EST.</i> </p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Events</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/12/7fb58ed22b9ed6eb2d51e46ecf196a49.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Studio Director's Letter: ESO's 2023 Retrospective & the Future]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65265</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65265</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Matt Firor, ZeniMax Online Studio's Studio Director, breaks down a special year for The Elder Scrolls Online and discusses its future.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/12/9c95712685820a8a84b06accc5e026fe.jpg" /><p><i>Matt Firor, ZeniMax Online Studio's Studio Director, breaks down a special year for The Elder Scrolls Online and discusses its future.</i></p><p><i><br></i></p><p> </p> 
<p>Greetings everyone—it's time to look back at <i>ESO</i> in 2023 and look forward to 2024.</p> 
<p>In 2023, our #1 priority—besides shipping <i>Necrom</i> and Infinite Archive—was to make the service more stable. The hardware refresh of all game servers finished in 2023, and even though we have some more non-player-facing hardware swaps to go, we are all reaping the benefits of more modern and powerful servers powering <i>ESO</i>'s infrastructure. We also have refined our processes to ensure that updates launch with fewer issues, and for the great majority of situations, we achieved that. We did have longer downtimes than usual a few times due to the hardware refresh, but looking back, I'm pretty happy with where things are—especially after our Epic Games Store launch in July, where we saw our highest monthly active user numbers since 2015.</p> 
<p><i>Necrom</i> was our highest-rated Chapter (in some ratings, highest since <i>Summerset</i>), and shows our commitment to amazing storytelling. I'm especially happy with how the Apocrypha zone turned out. Adding to the <i>Elder Scrolls</i> lore on Daedric realms is something we take great pride in, and I think we nailed the combination of obsession with knowledge and creepy visuals that are the hallmark of Hermaeus Mora. And for the first time in a few years, the story will continue in 2024, as the 2023 story (no spoilers here!) ended on a cliffhanger.</p> 
<p>And wrapping up 2023, we launched Infinite Archive, adding a challenging, repeatable game mode to <i>ESO</i>. This is a type of content that we want to do more of in the future: really fun, challenging experiences with great rewards that players can enjoy for a long time. <i>ESO</i> is always about great storytelling, so we won't abandon story quests and content, but we will balance it out with more systems like dungeons, trials, and special new content like Infinite Archive.</p> 
<p>Looking forward to 2024, the obvious first thing to note is that April 4, 2024, is <i>ESO</i>'s 10-year anniversary, marking a decade since we launched on PC/Mac. Reaching this milestone with the game in such great shape will be an amazing achievement—and we will celebrate with both in-game and real-life events. You already know about the first two: our 10-Year Anniversary community event in Amsterdam in April and a 10-Year Anniversary-themed <i>ESO </i>Tavern in Germany from July 13-14. Stay tuned for more information about all these events, and I certainly hope to see you in person at one or more of them!</p> 
<p>Also, I remind you that April 4, 2024, is the 10-year anniversary of the PC/Mac launch, but many of you didn't join the community until June 2015, at <i>ESO</i>'s massive console launch. As such, we are considering the entirety of April 2024 through July 2025 as our 10-year anniversary period, and we will fill it as much as we can with special events, retrospectives, and lots of other fun stuff to celebrate you, our community, and the <i>ESO</i> dev team. We can't wait to share all of this with you when we are ready.</p> 
<p>Next year will kick off with a Global Reveal show in January, and we are excited to continue the story from last year but in a different part of Tamriel. It's going to be great, and we have some new systems that I think everyone will want to hear about. I'm not going to spoil it now, but you should definitely look out for the Global Reveal announcement and mark your calendars!</p> 
<p>Finally, I'd like to take a moment to talk about all of us in the <i>ESO</i> community. Now that we are a year or so past the pandemic, it's good to take stock of where we are and where we want to go.</p> 
<p><i>ESO</i> is in a great place—enjoyed by millions. In fact, almost two million of you joined <i>ESO</i> last year, not counting the players enjoying the game for free from the Epic Games Store. We have been massively successful for many years now, and we are very thankful for all of you who have helped make this happen. As we approach the 10th anniversary of this amazing experience, I would just like everyone to acknowledge the path we've been on and appreciate the hard work we have all done to keep <i>ESO</i> amazing. It takes a village to develop and operate a game like this, and that village absolutely includes everyone reading this right now. Thanks so much for everything you do for <i>ESO</i>.</p> 
<p>See you in Tamriel!</p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Community</category>
            <category>Development</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/12/9c95712685820a8a84b06accc5e026fe.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ESO's 10th Anniversary Is Coming- Join Us For A Very Special In-Person Event!]]></title>
            <link>https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/648771/esos-10th-anniversary-is-coming-join-us-for-a-very-special-in-person-event</link>
            <guid>https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/648771/esos-10th-anniversary-is-coming-join-us-for-a-very-special-in-person-event</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 16:07:35 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://us.v-cdn.net/5020507/uploads/editor/pp/q529dlgjjtn3.jpg"><br>
This is the official discussion thread for, "<a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65061">ESO's 10th Anniversary Is Coming- Join Us For A Very Special In-Person Event!</a>"<br><br><i>Join us this April in the Netherlands, as we kickoff a year-long celebration of 10 years of #ESO! Get the details on the event, and the celebration to follow, in our latest article, linked above.<br><br>
Interested in attending the 10-Year Celebration Event next April? There's a ticket package option just right for you. Both grant full access to the event and so much more. <a href="https://www.showclix.com/tickets/ESOTenYearCelebrationNL">Get yours today</a>!<br><br>
We're not stopping in Amsterdam! We'll be going on an in-person World Tour in 2024 and 2025, celebrating 10 years of ESO at local community events and ending in the US for our 2025 ESO Celebration Event. We hope to see you at one of our community events!</i>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>Forum</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ESO's 10th Anniversary Is Coming–Join Us for a Very Special In-Person Event!]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65061</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65061</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Commemorate a decade of The Elder Scrolls Online and our amazing community with a special in-person event that kicks off our massive 10th Anniversary Celebration!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/12/955b1752b1e3849f351554ad8e203a17.jpg" /><p><i>Commemorate a decade of The Elder Scrolls Online and our amazing community with a special in-person event that kicks off our massive 10th Anniversary Celebration!</i></p> 
<h2>Celebrating 10 Amazing Years</h2> 
<p>Next year, <i>The Elder Scrolls Online</i> will reach its 10<sup>th</sup> anniversary since it first launched on PC/Mac in April 2014. To celebrate this incredible milestone, we're kicking off a massive 10<sup>th</sup> Anniversary Celebration in April.</p> 
<p>During the celebration, we'll look back on <i>ESO</i>'s history and celebrate the game itself, its dedicated group of developers, its passionate, ever-growing community, and its bright future. </p> 
<p>Whether you've been a member of the #ESOFam since early beta, have recently begun your journey into Tamriel, or are looking for a new epic online roleplaying game—you won't want to miss this incredible celebration. It all kicks off next year in Amsterdam!</p> 
<h2>Join Us in Amsterdam</h2> 
<p>The fun begins next year with the first <i>ESO</i> 10-Year Celebration Event, a two-day in-person event we're hosting at the <a href="https://www.sugarfactory.nl/en/">SugarFactory</a> just outside of Amsterdam, Netherlands, from Friday, April 5, until Saturday, April 6. You can grab your tickets now by visiting the official signup website below. </p><p><br></p><p>
</p><p>At the event, you can mix and mingle with your fellow <i>ESO</i> adventurers <i>and </i>developers while enjoying two days of fun. This will include developer panels and roundtable discussions (with some livestreamed), hands-on gameplay, food and drink, live music, community activities, and more. In addition, the April 2024 event will host our first-ever <b>in-person <i>ESO</i> cosplay competition</b>, so if you've got an amazing <i>ESO</i> costume in mind that you think the community will love and are planning to attend, get crafting! </p> 
<p>We'll share more specifics on the event with the community in the future, so keep an eye out on <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/" target="_blank">elderscrollsonline.com</a> and our social channels.</p> 
<h2>Celebrate ESO with Us!</h2> 
<p>We're planning to make this the biggest in-person community event we've ever had, but it's not the only one we plan to host during this massive anniversary celebration. There's going to be a ton of special 10<sup>th</sup> Anniversary in-person events all over the globe throughout, including a big one in the United States in 2025. </p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/12/c96164c1534c5cb313f541b93c8a14c0.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Celebrate ESO's anniversary with us!</i></p> 
<p>Stay tuned for additional announcements in April 2024 when we unveil more. </p> 
<p>Are you excited to celebrate 10 years of adventure in Tamriel's Second Era with us? Let us know if you're planning to make your way to the Netherlands for this initial event via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (Formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>—we hope to see you there!</p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Community</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/12/955b1752b1e3849f351554ad8e203a17.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ESO Live: December 15 @2PM EST—Cooking December Delights with Matygon!]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65241</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65241</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Tune in this Friday as we celebrate the winter season with some tasty treats!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/12/f375d331bf824aef30c3d96791c3f49d.jpg" /><p><i>Tune in this Friday as we celebrate the winter season with some tasty treats!</i></p> 
<p>Join us on <a href="https://www.twitch.tv/bethesda">Twitch.tv/Bethesda</a> this Friday, December 15 at 2PM EST, as Lead Community Manager Jessica Folsom and Senior Community Manager Gina Bruno are joined by special guest (and Stream Team member) <a href="https://www.twitch.tv/matygon">Matygon</a> to put on their chef hats and prepare some holiday delectables!</p> 
<p>Follow along in what has become an annual tradition as the trio bake some scrumptious snacks from the comfort of their homes while reminiscing on all the exciting changes and updates to occur in <i>ESO</i> during this past year.</p> 
<p>Twitch Drops will be enabled throughout the show (<a href="https://help.elderscrollsonline.com/#en/answer/41809" target="_blank">link your <i>ESO</i> and Twitch accounts here</a>), so be sure to tune in on <a href="https://www.twitch.tv/Bethesda">Twitch.tv/Bethesda</a> with your cookbooks ready this Friday, December 15 at 2PM EST. See you there!</p> 
<p><i>ESO Live is your official Elder Scrolls Online stream, hosted on Twitch.tv/Bethesda by ESO's Community Team.</i></p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>ESO Live</category>
            <category>Community</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/12/f375d331bf824aef30c3d96791c3f49d.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Crown Store Showcase—December 2023]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65065</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65065</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Treat yourself to a holiday delight from among December's new and returning Crown Store items.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/11/b1672459bfe07ca8c6f2544c4f04f551.jpg" /><p><i>Treat yourself to a holiday delight from among December's new and returning Crown Store items.</i></p> 
<p>You can check out all the new and returning items arriving to the Crown Store in December 2023 below. Don't forget, you can head over to the <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/crownstore">Crown Store page</a> right now to view all offers currently available. And be sure to drop by the <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/buycrowns">Buy Crowns page</a> to purchase however many crowns you might need this month! </p><p>Additionally, a variety of Crown Crates are returning this holiday season, including Ragebound and Unfeathered Crown Crates with the renewal of Gifting, alongside the cosmic Celestial Crates. Some items and offers are available for a limited time only, so be sure to read their individual details and don't miss out.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<h2>ESO Plus Deals</h2> 
<p>All ESO Plus™ members have access to a monthly selection of exclusive deals and items. You can find more information about them in <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/54825">this article</a>.</p> 
<p><b>Exclusive Free Items</b></p> 
<p><b>Painting: The Endless Library</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/10/32bc67b4096e7ec4126a630b7ba31203.jpg" />
<p><i>A painting depicting just one of the innumerable studies within the Endless Library of Hermaeus Mora.</i></p> <p>The Painting: The Endless Library will be available in the Crown Store FREE exclusively to ESO Plus Members on all platforms for a limited time, from November 22, 2023, to January 4, 2024, at 10AM EST.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> <h2>Crown Gem and Seals of Endeavor Items</h2> <p><b>Mounts</b></p> <p><b>Frost Draugr Charger</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/11/89d3dd884731a7f445508e2407806c10.jpg" />
<p><i>Now seen well outside Skyrim, these skeletal horses once served among Ysgramor's soldiers and were honored after their deaths—or so says one of the epic ballads found in Solitude's Bards College. Dare you ride a steed of such provenance? Of course!</i></p> 
<p>The Frost Draugr Charger will be available for Crown Gems and Seals of Endeavor on all platforms for a limited time, from December 18, 2023, to January 4, 2024, at 10AM EST.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<h2>Adornments</h2> 
<p><b>Hat</b></p> 
<p><b>Icereach Masks Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/11/f6106e2246e953b77711145d70833ff2.jpg" />
<p><i>Join the witches of Icereach by donning the visages of necromancer Bani and cryomancer Gohlla. Handcrafted during the darkest hours of the night, these masks make manifest the wicked spirits of those two coven leaders.</i></p> 
<p>The Icereach Masks Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from December 4 to December 7, 2023, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Winter Broadbrim Hat Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/11/451aef3e064657ce3941c59b41126c9e.jpg" />
<p><i>Festive bargain bundle including the Winter Corsage, Winter Garland, and Winter Wreath Broadbrim hats.</i></p> 
<p>The Winter Broadbrim Hat Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from December 11 to December 14, 2023, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>New Life Festival Cap</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/11/b630208d0a3e5857efa24e027d2e8a10.jpg" />
<p><i>Celebrate the turning of the year and the return of Magnus the Sun in this festive New Life cap. With a bobbing ball of fur on the end of its tapering blue velvet wimple, everyone will know you're the life of the festival!</i></p> 
<p>The New Life Festival Cap returns to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from December 18, 2023, to January 3, 2023, at 10AM EST.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>New Life Monk's Cap</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/11/d1fadbd6aa95a615d57519910a7d6a29.jpg" />
<p><i>For those who wish to celebrate New Life without tawdry and garish display, we offer this more modest festival hat, well suited to monks, simple merchants, and holy knights vowed to poverty. Because New Life is for everyone!</i></p> 
<p>The New Life Monk's Cap returns to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from December 18, 2023, to January 3, 2024, at 10AM EST.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Crafting</h2> 
<p><b>Motifs</b></p> 
<p><b>Crown Crafting Motifs: Frostcaster</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/11/66ae442f2bd6a0f8bcd704b7ea3fdb10.jpg" />
<p><i>Doctor Alfidia Lupus writes, "The most curious aspect of this Frostcaster clothing was its extensive use of an unfamiliar translucent blue-white material labeled 'Stalhrim,' a sort of crystalline metal unlike anything I've ever seen. It was so strange that I laid hands upon it, rubbing and tapping. It was rigid, faceted yet smooth, and gave off a distinct chill." Use to learn the Stalhrim Frostcaster crafting style.</i></p> 
<p>The Crown Crafting Motifs: Frostcaster will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms starting December 14 to December 21, 2023, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Outfit Styles</b></p> 
<p><b>Stalhrim Armor Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2021/11/e5131b864054f09bf5fb02b2b01f0c5f.jpg" />
<p><i>Gear up with armor that features the enchanted ice from Solstheim called stalhrim. Alter your armor's appearance by using this complete set of Stalhrim Outfit styles.</i></p> 
<p>The Stalhrim Armor Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms starting December 7 to December 14, 2023, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Mother Ciannait Arms Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2021/11/58d90bf72f4b3c894d22dac5152254b7.jpg" />
<p><i>Tildanyorian of the Undaunted, quiet scholar and warrior that he is, notes that Mother Ciannait leads the Icereach Coven with wits and crafty skill. Alter your weapon's appearance to match the Undaunted Mother Ciannait awards by using this complete set of Outfit styles.</i></p> 
<p>The Mother Ciannait Arms Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms starting December 7 to December 14, 2023, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item. The matching mask page will have a small chance to drop from the Icereach Coven from veteran Icereach. The matching shoulder page can be purchased from Urgarlag Chief-bane for 50 Undaunted Keys, or has a chance of dropping from Urgarlag's Mystery Coffer for 1 Key. Having the achievement “Cold-Blooded Killer” increases the drop chance of both items.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Nazaray Arms Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2022/06/1416c2ccc14b2e2800c1f93e7c94a78e.jpg" />
<p><i>Mindil the Untested claims, “I may not know much about the spriggan Nazaray, but I know she's tricky and has a wasp friend. Swat it for me, will you?” Alter your weapon's appearance to match the Undaunted Nazaray awards by using this complete set of Outfit styles.</i></p> 
<p>The Nazaray Arms Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms starting December 21, 2023 at 1PM EST to January 4, 2024, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item. The matching mask page will have a small chance to drop from Captain Numirril from veteran Shipwright's Regret. The matching shoulder page can be purchased from Urgarlag Chief-bane for 50 Undaunted Keys, or has a chance of dropping from Urgarlag's Mystery Coffer for 1 Key. Having the achievement “Shove Off” increases the drop chance of both items.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Wardrobe</h2> 
<p><b>Costumes</b></p> 
<p><b>Falkreath Thane</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/11/72175781a29ee18e463a0ac0ab809eb1.jpg" />
<p><i>This classic Nord kilted jerkin outfit projects the confidence and authority of a Falkreath fighting clan chief—complete with the traditional horned helmet!</i></p> <p>The Falkreath Thane costume will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from December 4, 2023, at 10AM EST, to December 11, 2023, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> <p><b>Brilliance Brocade Robes</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/11/f4d50b73c2341709b542416a1e14b656.jpg" />
<p><i>For the Orc who aspires to impress, this season Borzighu of Coldsnap Clothiers offers rich fabrics in subtle shades, accented with gold and steel to convey an indelible image of wealth and power.</i></p> 
<p>The Brilliance Brocade Robes will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from December 4 to December 7, 2023, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Evening Dress</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/11/e700fa448dc06b2aacb75c715b9b85c5.jpg" />
<p><i>A casual dress for evening wear, suitable for the marketplace, crafting center, or tavern.</i></p> 
<p>The Evening Dress costume will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from December 11 to December 14, 2023, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Nedic Armor Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/11/cd0b0031cd71f50b3a863df4811b8680.jpg" />
<p><i>This costume pack includes three examples of the sturdy tribal armor of the ancient Nedes.</i></p> 
<p>The Nedic Armor Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from December 14 to December 18, 2023, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Priest of the Green</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/11/f0db7be3f3eabd2b3302b2e53378a172.jpg" />
<p><i>In Valenwood they're called Spinners; in High Rock, Vicars of Jephre. Wherever they go, the traveling priests of Y'ffre the Storyteller are respected as holy defenders of nature and the natural world.</i></p> 
<p>The Priest of the Green costume will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from December 18 to December 21, 2023, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Crate</h2> 
<p><b>Ragebound Crate</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/11/324350a8576f82c63915b72c4fdadf67.jpg" />
<p><i>A mystery collection of Reach clan-related items!</i></p> 
<p>Ragebound Crates return to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from December 7 to December 14, 2023, at 10AM EST.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Ragebound Crate Bundle</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/11/bdc5dadfd92e9f92c871642fa15a1faa.jpg" />
<p><i>Get an AMAZING value with this bundle of 25× Ragebound Crates and manifest the twisted hunger of Namira with the Shade polymorph!</i></p> 
<p>Ragebound Crate Bundle returns to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from December 7 to December 14, 2023, at 10AM EST.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Unfeathered Crate</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/11/3669654aaac430f491bd4b27d311eb44.jpg" />
<p><i>A mystery collection of Umaril related items!</i></p> 
<p>Unfeathered Crates return to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from December 14 to December 21, 2023, at 10AM EST.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Unfeathered Crate Bundle</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/11/16ea4b60ca3e3055c704e4fb51532e04.jpg" />
<p><i>Umaril, champion of Meridia, is beloved and hated in equal measure—but you cannot question his sense of dramatic fashion. Don the golden Armor of the Unfeathered polymorph, included with this bundle of 25× Unfeathered Crates.</i></p> 
<p>The Unfeathered Crate Bundle returns to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from December 14 to December 21, 2023, at 10AM EST.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Celestial Crate</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/11/f7c66e944ffc9b34f33655e6eecda26a.jpg" />
<p><i>A mystery collection of Celestial related items!</i></p> 
<p>Celestial Crates return to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from December 21, 2023, 1PM EST to January 4, 2024, at 10AM EST.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<h2>Events </h2> 
<p><b>Currency</b></p> 
<p><b>Event Tickets</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/09/74f679e610302be57199309573dd3a29.jpg" />
<p><i> A ticket used to purchase rare goods from The Impresario, Event Merchant. Curious as to what goods? Well, chat with her to see what she has to offer!</i></p> 
<p>Single Event Tickets will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time during the New Life Festival in-game event. Stay tuned for event details!</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<h2>Furniture </h2> 
<p><b>Furnishing Pack: Forge-Lord's Great Works</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/11/6e94dd19633f87057899d2e0068295ce.jpg" />
<p><i>"In the Deep Halls, Far from Men</i></p> 
<p><i>Forsaken Red Mountain, Twisted Kin</i></p> 
<p><i>Hail the Mind, Hail the Stone</i></p> 
<p><i>Dwarven Pride, Stronger than Bone"</i></p> 
<p><i>—Dwemer Inquiries I-III, Thelwe Ghelein</i></p> 
<p>The Furnishing Pack: Forge-Lord's Great Works will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from December 7 to December 21, 2023, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Furnishing Pack: Dwarven Pipes</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/11/7521e231f73431c690e8d3e707c5b868.jpg" />
<p><i>A selection of Dwarven pipes, ducts, and conduits for adding a Deep Elf touch to your home.</i></p> 
<p>The Furnishing Pack: Dwarven Pipes will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from December 7 to December 21, 2023, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Furnishing Pack: New Life Festival</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/11/7a2e8f8f9618803ff746c874cb3d8405.jpg" />
<p><i>Welcome your friends with these essential New Life decorations, complete with ice sculptures, Bounteous Ladles for the younger guests, a hearth for roasting festive feasts, and even a trio of snowmortals!</i></p> 
<p>The Furnishing Pack: New Life Festival will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from December 11, 2023, to January 3, 2024, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Music Box, A Frost Melt Melody</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/11/0467053bc7dc804c8c1659ae1a650251.jpg" />
<p><i>When activated, plays a music box arrangement of the traditional New Life Festival song, "A Frost Melt Melody."</i></p> 
<p>The Music Box, A Frost Melt Melody will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from December 11, 2023, to January 3, 2024, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Tree, Seasons of Y'ffre</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/11/e401161abded4dad47f70e68dcc3471d.jpg" />
<p><i>Seasonal transition is a part of Y'ffre's plan. After planting this tree in your home, you can show your reverence for the God of Song and Forest by adjusting its state to spring, summer, fall, or winter.</i></p> 
<p>The Tree, Seasons of Y'ffre will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from December 21, 2023, at 1PM EST to January 4, 2024, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Furnishing Pack: Druidic Gatherings</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/11/9368ae913f0f2795ebd511b4d6f843fa.jpg" />
<p><i>Revel in the glory of nature, under the benevolent gaze of the Druid King. Lush foliage, rustic huts, and outdoor furnishings draw your circle close together, turning your home into a place of wild celebration.</i></p> 
<p>The new Furnishing Pack: Druidic Gatherings will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from December 21, 2023, at 1PM EST to January 4, 2024, at 10AM EST.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Music Box, Deeproot Dirge</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/11/cb18a16f2d60aa36d694cd89b3a5db1f.jpg" />
<p><i>When activated, plays a music box arrangement of the meditative "Deeproot" composition.</i></p> 
<p>The Music Box, Deeproot Dirge will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from December 21, 2023, at 1PM EST to January 4, 2024, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Houses</h2> 
<p><b>Stone Eagle Aerie</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/11/e9ec8231153a7311c0ed9409a56021d9.jpg" />
<p><i>From its majestic position above the city of Markarth, the Stone Eagle Aerie features breathtaking views, several water features, and sturdy Dwarven stonework. Rumors claim a hidden exit provides easy access to the Markarth Outlaws Refuge.</i></p> 
<p>The Stone Eagle Aerie returns to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from December 7 to December 21, 2023, at 10AM EST. Furnished and unfurnished versions will be available.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Enchanted Snow Globe Home</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/11/930c1aee9fbe98f6ba3e711716b20177.jpg" />
<p><i>Get small to go large: this miniature Snow Globe Home is tiny on the outside but expansive on the inside, proving shrunken real estate is a big bargain! And to make the interior cozier, the exterior features an eternally-festive gentle snowfall. Magical!</i></p> 
<p>The Enchanted Snow Globe Home returns to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from December 11, 2023, to January 3, 2024, at 10AM EST. Furnished and unfurnished versions will be available.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Gladesong Arboretum</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/11/f290025b98dd13cff2f778bab3d4f18d.jpg" />
<p><i>The soothing sound of a waterfall accompanies the wind as it sings softly through the majestic trees in this druidic settlement. Carved stone shelters provide comfortable living spaces and open onto inspiring vistas.</i></p> 
<p>The new Gladesong Arboretum will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from December 21, 2023, at 1PM EST to January 4, 2024, at 10AM EST. Furnished and unfurnished versions will be available.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Houseguests</h2> 
<p><b>Stibbons</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/11/217fa4b0fa3041cea9a83daca752310b.jpg" />
<p><i>The long-suffering Stibbons, Lady Laurent's servant, needs a break. He chose to seek you out, desperate for the peace your home provides. After adding Stibbons to your home, you can set him on a path, plus you and your visitors can speak with him.</i></p> 
<p>Stibbons will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from December 7 to December 21, 2023, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Houseguests: Hildegard and Kor</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/11/c5eedf45543d2eda9ec75f850f5f1216.jpg" />
<p><i>Share your generous hospitality with this Dark Brotherhood duo to learn more about Hildegard's dual nature and Kor's life experiences.</i></p> 
<p>New Houseguests: Hildegard and Kor will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from December 21, 2023, at 1PM EST to January 4, 2024, at 10AM EST.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<h2>Mounts</h2> 
<p><b>Frost Mare</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/11/b314bc29d013b570a074838f6b374460.jpg" />
<p><i>With its icy gaze and steaming breath, the frigid Frost Mare seems carved from the very glaciers of Skyrim.</i></p> 
<p>The Frost Mare mount will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from December 7 to December 14, 2023, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Dwarven Spider</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/11/a617b3191c592686b7a4c69817ea8dff.jpg" />
<p><i>Of all the Dwemer animunculi, the Dwarven Spider is perhaps the most familiar and iconic. This versatile construct comes in several variations, and it should come as no surprise that one of them is a vamidium, or mechanical mount. Clankin'!</i></p> 
<p>The Dwarven Spider mount will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from December 11 to December 18, 2023, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Solstice Indrik</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/11/d54c6e224a7af18890856a6f9fb1d278.jpg" />
<p><i>Legend says this indrik was born of a child's toy, touched by magic on the year's longest night. Others believe a worthy rider wished it into being by pleading with the moons on a cold Frostfall night. Regardless, riders see the world for the wonder it is.</i></p> 
<p>The new Solstice Indrik Mount will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from December 21, 2023, at 1PM EST to January 4, 2024, at 10AM EST. </p> 
<p><i> </i></p> 
<h2>Pets</h2> 
<p><b>Snow Bear Cub</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/11/1708620ce53a44231692dbdabebd187c.jpg" />
<p><i>The Snow Bear is known for its fierceness, but its cub is as cute as a bug. Maybe even two bugs.</i></p> 
<p>The Snow Bear Cub pet will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from December 4 to December 7, 2023, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Sovngarde Pony Guar</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/11/ac35a7cef46c248023bc17c84a27fd9b.jpg" />
<p><i>"You may laugh at the idea of a pony guar from Sovngarde, but they exist. In fact, one showed up around here, but it chose to follow a worthy traveler. Or perhaps one freer with cuddles than I am."—Clever Woman Moritra</i></p> 
<p>The Sovngarde Pony Guar pet will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from December 14 to December 18, 2023, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Sovngarde Pony</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/11/b88bd187be4dac231aa2ccfd19f311ce.jpg" />
<p><i>"Noble ponies trot forth from Sovngarde, seeking those who have made oaths, knowingly or not. Curiosity prompts them to follow an oathmaker to see how they fulfill their promise. If one follows you, give it an apple. They love them."—Clever Woman Moritra</i></p> 
<p>The Sovngarde Pony pet will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from December 14 to December 18, 2023, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<p> </p> 
<p><b>Sabre Cat Cub</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/11/f684aa7130c16cc39b43f864d63e44e1.jpg" />
<p><i>Sabre Cats are mighty and majestic hunters that rule the northern plains and tundra by sheer strength and savagery—but, Daedra take it, they sure are cute when they're cubs!</i></p> 
<p>The Sabre Cat Cub pet will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from December 18 to December 21, 2023, at 10AM EST. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<p> </p> 
<h2>Customized Actions</h2> 
<p><b>Personal Plant Thief</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/11/eb12ef4b9be92e0a87980ecf0a8341ec.jpg" />
<p><i>In seconds, this well-trained prairie dog can pilfer flora you need for your crafting. Be careful, this charming little rogue might steal your heart!</i></p> 
<p>The new Personal Plant Thief Customized Actions will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from December 21, 2023, at 1PM EST to January 4, 2024, at 10AM EST.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<h2>Personality</h2> 
<p><b>Scholar</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/11/9dd529cdb72da0ef69fc9800204742dc.jpg" />
<p><i>Ever notice how everyone in Tamriel keeps a journal? Now you can show the world that you're making your own scholarly record of your adventures and the deeds of those around you. Perhaps the pen IS mightier than the sword.</i></p> 
<p>The Scholar personality returns to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from December 14 to December 21, 2023, at 10AM EST.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<h2>Emotes</h2> 
<p><b>Warm Hands</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/11/86bd660c269e5ef51b40afd18df9bfb2.jpg" />
<p><i>There's a bitter wind blowing in off the Sea of Ghosts—better warm your hands!</i></p> 
<p>The Warm Hand emote returns to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from December 4 to December 11, 2023, at 10AM EST.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p>Whether you desire a new costume or cozy house, you can close out 2023 in style and comfort with the above items. Don't forget, you can get the crowns you'll need for your holiday shopping by visiting the <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/buycrowns">Buy Crowns page</a>. Have you found the perfect gift? Let us know all about it via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, or <a href="https://www.facebook.com/ElderScrollsOnline">Facebook</a>!</p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Crown Store</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/11/b1672459bfe07ca8c6f2544c4f04f551.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Daily Login Rewards—December 2023]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65063</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65063</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Take a look at some of the free rewards available to you simply by logging in to ESO this December 2023!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/11/b6f7fc3a98afc48d147328fdc5f5e542.jpg" /><p><i>Take a look at some of the free rewards available to you simply by logging in to ESO this December 2023!</i></p> 
<p>Though 2023 may be winding down, the daily rewards are only picking up this coming December. A few examples of the rewards on offer are listed below, including a new pet. You can claim them from the Daily Rewards section of the Crown Store, as described in <a href="https://help.bethesda.net/#en/answer/41950">this help article</a>.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Gold Coast Grand Experience Scroll—Day 1</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/06/1f7bf97587039a52547d3df74a2632bc.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Experience more holiday spirit this year!</i></p> <p>Start the month off strong by improving your experience gains with this Grand Experience Scroll. Level up, gain Champion Points, and improve your Skill Lines with a 150% boost.</p><p><br></p> <p><b>Akaviri Potentate Crates &amp; Preview Crate—Days 2-6</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/08/f855b53f259536ac1befed8d3b261f4b.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Akaviri Potentate Crates</i><br></p> <p>Herald the return of the Second Empire with Akaviri Potentate Crown Crates, first introduced way back in 2020. Get one crate each day from day two until day six.</p><p><br></p><p><b>Crown Lessons: Riding Capacity ×5—Day 7</b><br></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/11/3ccea04ad2ca7e229b5963807211dc85.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>How many presents can you carry?</i></p> 
<p>Fill your saddlebags with loot—or holiday presents—after expanding them using these Riding Lessons. Sleigh not included.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Seals of Endeavor ×250—Day 14</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/10/cbf054f9fa4122ee9be26996607da8d2.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Gift yourself fine Crown Crate goods.</i></p> 
<p>Stock up on Seals of Endeavor for choice Crown Crate items, perhaps even from the new <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/64997">All-Maker Crates</a>. You can also earn Seals from Daily and Weekly Endeavors in-game and use them to buy goods contained in Crown Crates or normally purchased with Crown Gems. Learn more about Seals of Endeavor <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/59925">in this blog</a>.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Anchorborn Pony Pet—Day 21</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/11/496142a84e69b44cabfef723fb1698b1.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center" style="text-align: center;;"><i>Probably not a Daedra. Probably.</i></p> 
<p>Is this part of Molag Bal's plot to dominate Tamriel, or just an unfortunate beast of burden geared up with the recycled debris of collapsed Dark Anchors? Whatever its origins, it's adorable! Log in for 21 days to claim the Anchorborn Pony pet. We're (mostly) sure it won't betray you to the God of Schemes.</p><p><br></p> 
<p>Remember, these aren't all the rewards you can claim when you log in to the game this December 2023. To see the full list, log in on the first day of the month! If one of these rewards speaks to you, be sure to tell us about it on <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (Formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>. Of course, if it's the Anchorborn Pony speaking, you might also want to tell a priest of the Divines!</p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Daily Rewards</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/11/b6f7fc3a98afc48d147328fdc5f5e542.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Drive Back the Adversary with Items from the New All-Maker Crown Crates]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/64997</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/64997</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Pay homage to the deity of the ancient Skaal faith with the items and collectibles found in the new All-Maker Crown Crates.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/11/87655bbb15ec324e4907f6d99ac15c70.jpg" /><p><i>Pay homage to the deity of the ancient Skaal faith with the items and collectibles found in the new All-Maker Crown Crates.</i></p> 
<p><i>***</i></p> 
<p><i>The people of the Skaal bow their head in reverence to the All-Maker. For through the All-Maker all are One. Will you join them in their distant land, to stand against the Adversary? Don their stalhrim armors, take up their rune-carved blades. Uphold the Wind and the Earth and the Sun as you seek harmony without and within. The great river of life flows, traveler. Will you flow with it back to the arms of the All-Maker?</i></p> 
<p>***</p> 
<p>The new All-Maker Crown Crates arrive in the Crown Store this Thursday, November 30 at 10AM EST. Opening these crates might grant you a sign of the All-Maker's favor in the form of new and returning items and collectibles.</p> 
<p>These goods include unique mounts, pets, furnishings, and much more. You can see just some of the items available within All-Maker Crown Crates below.</p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/11/df8c3e1aba326b6185e0ef565f50ac14.jpg" />
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/11/bb332fe703e3577fa721ff531b500764.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Clear Ice Boulder furnishing &amp; Frostfall Recall customized action</i></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/11/c6f525c76d08aaa5f1ad27c0142d9086.jpg" />
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/11/b16277db07418b7556f33c10e47bc809.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Windcaller Garb costume and Orphan of the Stars skin</i></p> 
<p>Those who are fortunate enough to truly catch the All-Maker's eye might find one of the below extremely rare Radiant Apex mounts.</p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/11/6daf71bb01d5bd51d53f94e8f74ca1a0.jpg" />
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/11/0ee3020f5ea5b9b0a2be315ea2aef3dc.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Solstheim Shiver Wolf and Star-Orphan Elk mounts</i></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/11/41e3d4f7bee5bd0ea3897d6bd3527fc0.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Blessed Highmane Lion mount</i></p> 
<p>All-Maker Crown Crates will be available in one-, four-, and 15-crate bundles in addition to a unique 25-crate offering that is available as a one-time purchase only. In addition to the crates, this special bundle also includes the Solstheimstone Incarnate polymorph.</p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/11/566e5cae151cbb0f283b2e03f0652033.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Enjoy a bundle of All-Maker Crown Crates alongside the Solstheimstone Incarnate Polymorph</i></p> 
<p>This polymorph will be unlocked automatically and added to your collectibles when the one-off bundle is first purchased. It is not part of the All-Maker crates themselves.</p> 
<p>Of course, the above are just some of the gifts the All-Maker can bestow upon his children. If you wish to see the full list of items you have a chance to receive when opening an All-Maker Crown Crate, check out <a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/647840/official-discussion-thread-for-all-maker-crown-crates">this thread</a> on our official forums.</p> 
<p>Be warned, when the new crates go live, the currently available Buoyant Armiger Crown Crates will be removed from the Crown Store in turn, so don't forget to pick them up while they're still available!</p> 
<p>All-Maker Crown Crates arrive this Thursday, November 30 at 10AM EST, and can be acquired from the Crown Crate section of the in-game Crown Store. Do you hope to prove yourself to the All-Maker and oppose the Adversary? Let us know about your wintry devotions via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (Formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>. </p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Crown Store</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/11/87655bbb15ec324e4907f6d99ac15c70.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Crown Store Gifting Update – October 2023]]></title>
            <link>https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/644559/crown-store-gifting-update-october-2023</link>
            <guid>https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/644559/crown-store-gifting-update-october-2023</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 20:22:11 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[Following up on Studio Director Matt Firor's message last month about the <a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/643289/update-on-current-and-future-status-of-gifting">current and future status of Crown Store Gifting</a>, we are moving forward with re-enabling this functionality for eligible players at the account level. In this post, we will detail what to expect.<br><br>
In September, we temporarily disabled Crown Store gifting due to a rapidly growing issue of "bad actors" using various fraudulent means to amass crowns without paying for them, then using them in turn to sell Crown Store items to players for real-world cash outside of the game client. That said, we recognize that gifting is a meaningful part of our community, and we are in the process of manually re-enabling Crown Store gifting access for select players who meet our specific criteria. This work will be complete tomorrow, October 11, during the maintenance window from 09:00 AM ET to 12:00 PM ET.<br><br>
Gifting eligibility is determined by an evolving list of factors including but not limited to the account being at least 180 days past its first login and previous engagement with in-game features. You may check if you have access to gifting in-game via the Crown Store as well as via <a href="https://account.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/account/billing/billing-history">your billing history page</a> in the ESO account center. If you have access to Crown Store gifting, you will see "Allow Crown Store Gifting" in your billing history. If you try to send a gift via the in-game Crown Store and do not have access, you will see a "Gifting Locked" pop-up message. Please note that we are exploring better ways to display this information in-game in the future, such as updating the Gifting Tutorial.<br><br>
If you do not have access to Crown Store gifting after it is re-enabled on October 11, 2023, and wish for a review of your account, please visit <a href="https://help.elderscrollsonline.com">https://help.elderscrollsonline.com</a> and submit a Customer Support ticket. Please choose the Billing / Purchase / Code category then Platform &gt; I have a question about a sale / offer &gt; I want to send gift items from this account.<br><br>
We appreciate everyone's understanding and patience while we get this solution up and running. Multiple teams have worked long hours to evaluate the best technical solutions that we could stand up in a reasonably short time, while also prioritizing the Crown Store gifting player experience. We are dedicated to continuing to explore ways to make this better and reduce fraudulent activity in ESO. Thanks again for being a part of our community and for your continued support.]]></content:encoded>
            <category>Forum</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[New Patcher Rollout]]></title>
            <link>https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/642066/new-patcher-rollout</link>
            <guid>https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/642066/new-patcher-rollout</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 20:49:19 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[Hello everyone! After plenty of testing <a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en-gb/discussion/632782/new-eso-launcher-testing-and-launch-plan-pc-and-mac">during the last PTS period</a>, we are pleased to announce the rollout of our new patcher on the live servers for PC/Mac. The rollout of the new patcher will happen in four phases, with new countries being added during each phase. As we give countries access to the new patcher, we will make note of it in the list below by noting next to the country name (has the new patcher.) We will also note what phase we are currently in by specifying whether it has not started, in progress, or complete, next to the phase number. The countries getting the patcher are listed in order below.<br><br>
Thanks for your patience as we roll this out to all countries listed below. A special thanks to everyone who helped test out the launcher during the last PTS and provided feedback.<br><br><b>Phase 1 (Complete) </b>
<ol><li>Netherlands (Has the new patcher)</li>
<li>Sweden (Has the new patcher)</li>
<li>Czech Republic/ Finland (Has the new patcher)</li>
<li>Norway/ Denmark (Has the new patcher)</li>
<li>Hungary/ Switzerland/ Romania (Has the new patcher)</li>
</ol><br><b>Phase 2 (Complete) </b>
<ol><li>Poland (Has the new patcher)</li>
<li>Spain/ Turkey (Has the new patcher)</li>
<li>Italy/ Austria/ Belgium/ Portugal/ Greece/ Ireland (Has the new patcher)</li>
</ol><br><b>Phase 3 (Complete) </b>
<ol><li>United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland/ France (Has the new patcher)</li>
<li>Germany (Has the new patcher)</li>
<li>United States of America (Has the new patcher)</li>
</ol><br><b>Phase 4 (Not Started) </b><br>
This phase will encompass all other countries where ESO is available, that are not listed above.<br><br><b>Known Issues</b>
<ul><li>Some Czech Republic players may not have their country recognized, thus making them unable to upgrade the patch at this time. We are aware of the issue and working toward a solution.</li>
<li>Audio issues with sound volume and sound effects. We have a bug in for this and are working on a fix for the future.</li>
</ul>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>Forum</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>