<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>ESO Announcements</title>
        <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/</link>
        <description>Combined ESO blog and forum post announcements feed</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 09:18:04 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>Magic</generator>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Welcome To Gold Road! Your One Stop Shop For Gold Road Launch Content]]></title>
            <link>https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/659603/welcome-to-gold-road-your-one-stop-shop-for-gold-road-launch-content</link>
            <guid>https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/659603/welcome-to-gold-road-your-one-stop-shop-for-gold-road-launch-content</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 09:18:04 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://us.v-cdn.net/5020507/uploads/editor/mh/sq1zda5ebpdj.jpg"><br>
Hello everyone and welcome to The Elder Scrolls Online: Gold Road Launch Day for PC/Mac, PlayStation, and Xbox! We hope everyone is excited to enter the West Weald for the first time. There are plenty of new content to tackle, like Scribing. And remember, we also have Ithelia's secrets to uncover, a brand new Daedric Prince to discover and learn about! To see everything Gold Road and Update 42 have to offer, <a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/659550/pc-mac-patch-notes-v10-0-5-gold-road-update-42#latest">please check out our PC patch notes</a>, <a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/660750">Playstation Patch Notes</a>, and <a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/660749">Xbox Patch Notes</a>.<br><br>
As with any launch, our goal is to make it as smooth as possible for everyone to hop in and play. However, unintended issues sometimes come up. If you run into any issues, please be sure to post your issues in the <a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/categories/bug-reports">bug reports section</a> of the forum. You can also keep update to date on our responses to bugs and other issues <a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/tracker">here, on the Dev Tracker</a>. We keep this section up to date as we get information to share.<br><br>
We do have an active list of known issues for Gold Road. You can view the list <a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/659638/pc-mac-update-42-known-issues#latest">here</a>.<br><br>
As mentioned earlier, with Gold Road, you will now have access to Scribing! This precursor to spell crafting will give you flexibility in ability customization. We're excited to see what abilities all of you create with Scribing. And as with any new system, there is always room for improvement. So please make sure to sound off on what can be improved here on the forum!<br><br>
As many of you are starting your journey into Gold Road, we have a list of several blog posts you can reference to catch up on any missing information regarding the chapter. We have those listed out below.
<ul><li><a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65899">Scribing 101 Dev Video</a></li>
<li><a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66091">Gold Road Preview- Designing Ithelia and Gold Road</a></li>
<li><a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66085">Gold Road Preview- Lucent Citadel and Mirrormoor Incursions</a></li>
<li><a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66003">Gold Road Preview- West Weald</a></li>
<li><a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66155">June ESO Survival Guide</a></li>
<li><a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66071">Anniversary Spotlight- Earn A Multi-Rider Mount With Scribing</a></li>
<li>Meet the Character- <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65995">Nahlia</a> and <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65981">Tribune Alea</a></li>
</ul><br>
Lastly, if you are looking for a bit of hype or a last nudge to hop into Gold Road, you should check out our the Final Gameplay trailer below. Thanks everyone for taking the time to read this and welcome to Gold Road!<br><span><span data-youtube="youtube-vw8UuwAAd8U?autoplay=1"><span><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vw8UuwAAd8U"><img src="https://img.youtube.com/vi/vw8UuwAAd8U/0.jpg" width="640" height="385" border="0" style="height: 385px; width: 640px">https://youtu.be/vw8UuwAAd8U</a></span><span></span></span></span>,This has been updated for console launch]]></content:encoded>
            <category>Forum</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Elder Scrolls Online: Gold Road & Update 42 Now Live on All Platforms]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66077</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66077</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Uncover the mystery of the Forgotten Prince with The Elder Scrolls Online: Gold Road and Update 42 base-game patch, now live on all platforms!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/ab7441b3abfa4ddc788528fb315ab9e1.jpg" /><p><i>Uncover the mystery of the Forgotten Prince with The Elder Scrolls Online: Gold Road and Update 42 base-game patch, now live on all platforms!</i><br></p> <p><i>The Elder Scrolls Online: Gold Road</i> is now live on PC/Mac, Steam, Epic Game Store, Xbox One, Xbox Series X|S, PlayStation 4, and PlayStation 5. This new Chapter for <i>The Elder Scrolls Online</i> introduces a new zone to explore, West Weald, along with a new system to master called Scribing. It also concludes the story of Ithelia, the Forgotten Prince, which began with 2023's Shadows Over Morrowind saga. </p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/459638ba6ddd36869757f1ff8004d442.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>The Forgotten Prince returns</i></p> 
<p>In addition to the Chapter, this release also includes the U42 base-game patch, introducing a host of bug fixes, balance changes, and other improvements free for all <i>ESO </i>players. You can view the full patch notes for <i>Gold Road</i> and Update 42 <a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/categories/patch-notes">on our official forums</a>. </p> 
<h2>Gold Road Chapter</h2> 
<p>In <i>The Elder Scrolls Online: Gold Road</i> you can venture into the heart of Colovian Imperial culture as you unravel the mystery of the return of a never-before-seen Daedric Prince—Ithelia. While <i>Gold Road</i> continues (and concludes) the Shadow Over Morrowind narrative that began in 2023, you can experience and enjoy the latest Chapter's storyline without having to play any of the game's previous content. </p> 
<p><b>West Weald Zone</b></p> 
<p>Located along Cyrodiil's southwest border and neighboring Valenwood and the Gold Coast, this new Chapter allows you to <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66003">explore West Weald</a>, a wealthy Imperial province thrown into chaos. Home to the proud and cosmopolitan Colovians, West Weald has found itself besieged by mysterious unknown Daedra. Even worse, a large part of the region has seemingly overnight become overgrown by the vast jungles of Valenwood, resulting in the migration of local Wood Elves. </p>
<a href="https://youtube.com/v/znogunEB5V0?autoplay=1&rel=0"><img src="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/znogunEB5V0/maxresdefault.jpg" /></a>
<p>Within this new zone, you can explore the city of Skingrad in addition to both the Gold Road region and emergent Dawnwood, where you'll discover a multitude of new side quests, world bosses, delves, public dungeons, and more. Discover more about the zone in <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66003">this preview blog</a>. </p> 
<p><b>Scribing System</b></p> 
<p>An all-new system introduced with <i>Gold Road</i>, Scribing grants you the ability to craft and <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66057">customize your own handmade abilities</a>. With Scribing, you can select a base Grimoire and tailor it with scripts to create an ability that perfectly fits your playstyle and build. </p>
<a href="https://youtube.com/v/_yWOpQ6_T0M?autoplay=1&rel=0"><img src="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/_yWOpQ6_T0M/maxresdefault.jpg" /></a>
<p>With this new system, you'll discover a robust questline that has you restore an ancient Scholarium while diving deep into the mysteries of magicka in Tamriel. Whether you're looking for greater power, versatility, or roleplaying opportunities, Scribing introduces a powerful new way to tailor your builds and play your way. </p> 
<p><b>Group Activities</b></p> 
<p>In addition to the zone's multiple world bosses, delves, and public dungeons, <i>Gold Road</i> also introduces two new group activities to challenge you and your allies: the Lucent Citadel and Mirrormoor Incursions. </p> 
<p>In the Lucent Citadel Trial, you and your large group (12 players total) must venture into a long-forgotten Daedric vault within the realm of Fargrave, contend with its unique boss encounters, and seek out the mysterious Arcane Knot. </p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/82f94f90370d384feb55d981391e73aa.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Team up to defend West Weald</i></p> 
<p>Mirrormoor Incursions are a new type of world event plaguing West Weald and threatening to overwhelm the region with the minions of Ithelia. You can discover more about both activities in <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66085">this preview blog</a>. </p> 
<p><b>New Rewards</b></p> 
<p>In addition to a new zone to explore, stories to experience, and challenges to overcome, the <i>Gold Road</i> Chapter is full of new Achievements, items, and collectibles for you to loot and earn. </p> 
<p>Specifically, West Weald features 10 powerful item sets to loot and craft in addition to three unique Mythic items to uncover using the Antiquities system. Completing Achievements can also earn you a wide range of collectibles, such as style pages for King Nantharion's Royal Armor or even the Wildburn Lynx mount. </p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/ad5fa21a49f122ad3b119ca16cf333b5.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>New collectibles, styles, and more</i></p> 
<p>Rewards also include fragments for the all-new Tales of Tribute patron and deck, Saint Alessia, in addition to a new type of collectible, called Skill Styles. Skill Styles are cosmetic collectibles that allow you to change the visuals for your existing abilities. With <i>Gold Road</i> and Update 42, there are 22 Skill Styles for you to unlock and apply from various sources, including quest rewards, public dungeons, and other activities. </p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/1d948b29fef327a9c9c14a8ce284f2c1.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Great challenges lead to great rewards!</i></p> 
<p>Finally, <i>Gold Road</i> and Update 42 also introduces the <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66017">Adventurer Across a Decade</a> Achievement, celebrating <i>ESO</i>'s 10-Year Anniversary by granting you the Fractured Glory skin for having completed the game's story content (including <i>Gold Road</i>) throughout its long history. </p> 
<h2>Purchase Details &amp; Requirements</h2> 
<p><i>The Elder Scrolls Online: Gold Road</i> is available <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/joinus">to buy now</a>, with four editions:</p> 
<ul><li><i>The Elder Scrolls Online Deluxe Collection: Gold Road</i> </li><li><i>The Elder Scrolls Online Collection: Gold Road</i> </li><li><i>The Elder Scrolls Online Deluxe Upgrade: Gold Road</i> </li><li><i>The Elder Scrolls Online: Upgrade: Gold Road</i> </li></ul> 
<p>If you are a brand-new or lapsed player, both <i>Collection </i>editions include the base game, the <i>Gold Road</i> Chapter, and ALL previous Chapters. If you already own <i>ESO</i> and its previous Chapters, both <i>Upgrade </i>editions grant access to the <i>Gold Road</i> Chapter. Note that to run <i>Gold Road</i> on PC/Mac, your machine needs to meet the game's requirements here: <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/newplayerguide/minspec">PC</a>, <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/newplayerguide/minspec">Mac</a>.</p> 
<p>In addition to the game, both versions of <i>Gold Road</i> are also available in <i>Deluxe</i> editions, which feature a unique mount, pet, memento, outfit style, and emotes.</p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/01/be77a18cfe66c3cfa77b66b9c1e021ca.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Gold Road Deluxe Edition items</i></p> 
<p>To find out more about <i>Gold Road</i> and its editions, <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65365">check out this blog</a>.</p> 
<h2>Getting Started in Gold Road</h2> 
<p>Ready to venture into West Weald? You can travel to the new zone and begin your adventure in the following ways: </p> 
<p><b>Via Wayshrine</b></p> 
<p>You can teleport directly to the zone by accessing your map, selecting Gold Road, and then selecting the automatically unlocked Skingrad Vineyards Wayshrine.</p> 
<p><b>Via the Gold Road Main Quest</b></p> 
<p>You can have the game lead you to West Weald by picking up the Chapter's first main story quest, “Paths of Chaos.” You can find it by navigating to your Collections and then viewing Stories, selecting Chapter, and then Gold Road. </p> 
<p><b>Via the Tutorial</b></p> 
<p>You can also travel to West Weald by creating a new character and completing the tutorial. At the end of the tutorial experience, you can select the zone as your destination and begin.</p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/178df5daaf8d02cd7580ae91c5a6519b.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center"><i>Adventure awaits in Gold Road</i></p> <p>Note that there are no level or story requirements for the <i>Gold Road </i>Chapter, allowing you to jump right in with any of your characters—existing or brand new! </p> <h2>Update 42 </h2> <p>Launching in tandem with Gold Road is Update 42, a free base-game patch for all <i>ESO</i> players. Update 42 introduces a series of balance changes, fixes, and additions with no purchase required (beyond access to the game itself). </p> <p><b>Improvements to In-game Mail</b></p> <p>With Update 42, we've made a series of improvements to in-game mail, focusing on its interface and notifications. This includes the addition of categories (player mail, system mail, and system alerts), improved sorting, attachment preview, and inventory space display. </p> <p>This update also adds a “Delete After Claim” option (helping you keep inboxes under control), a “Take All” function, and notifications for mail with attachments. In addition, messages received from your Hirelings will now be automatically recorded in the Lore Library under “Hireling Correspondence.”</p> <p>Finally, as part of the team's efforts to improve server performance and stability, Update 42's mail changes also include reduced expiration times based on the mail types. </p> <p><b>Environment Sustainability Features</b></p> <p>With this update, we're joining Team Xbox in reducing our game's environmental impact with the following new features:</p> <ul><li>Reduced GPU use during periods of inactivity for PC/Mac, Xbox Series X|S, and PlayStation 5. </li><ul><li>Reducing resolution and imposing a framerate cap during inactivity. </li></ul><li>Screen dimming during periods of inactivity on PC/Mac. </li><ul><li>Note that this already occurs on consoles.</li></ul><li>Reduced GPU use in Contextual Menus for Xbox Series X|S and PlayStation 5. </li><ul><li>When viewing most menus on consoles, the framerate is capped.</li></ul></ul> <p>For more on Xbox's sustainability efforts, <a href="https://www.xbox.com/en-US/community/sustainability">visit this page</a>.<br></p> <p>For everything changing and coming with Update 42, be sure to check out the <a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/categories/patch-notes">patch notes on the official forums</a>. </p> <h2>Forgotten No More</h2> <p>The Forgotten Prince walks Tamriel, and chaos follows in her wake. Investigate the emergence of Ithelia and confront her scions, explore the Colovian region of West Weald, and unlock and customize new abilities with the Scribing System in <i>The Elder Scrolls Online: Gold Road</i>. Tell us if you're excited to dive deep into this new Chapter via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline;">Facebook</a>. </p> <p><i>The Elder Scrolls Online: Gold Road is now live on PC/Mac, Xbox One, Xbox Series X|S, PlayStation 4, and PlayStation 5.</i><br></p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Gold Road</category>
            <category>Update 42</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/ab7441b3abfa4ddc788528fb315ab9e1.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Celebrate ESO in Style with the Diamond Anniversary Crown Crate]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66083</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66083</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Find the finery and fashion appropriate to the ongoing celebrations with the items and collectibles found in the new Diamond Anniversary Crown Crates.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/06/183d368d4915fea341a39956ae007749.jpg" /><p><i>Find the finery and fashion appropriate to the ongoing celebrations with the items and collectibles found in the new Diamond Anniversary Crown Crates.</i></p> 
<p>***</p> 
<p><i>Ten years. From Dragons in Elsweyr to Vampires in Skyrim, we've slain some of the mightiest foes. We've laughed alongside Razum-dar, gotten our hands bloody with Naryu, and cried with Khamira. Whether you carry the lion banner, swear fealty to the Tribunal, or leap into battle with "For the Queen!" on your lips, we've shared a decade of Elder Scrolls Online adventures together.</i></p> 
<p><i>Take up arms in celebration of our Diamond anniversary. Carry remembrances of the Five Companions into battle, ride atop a fallen titan as you leap into the fray, and commemorate the last decade of adventures with dazzling new treasures to last ten years more. Come along, friend. You're always welcome in Tamriel.</i> </p> 
<p>***
</p><p> The new Diamond Anniversary Crown Crates arrive in the Crown Store this Thursday, June 20, 2024 at 10AM EDT. When opening these crates, you'll have a chance to acquire fine goods suitable to celebrate any special occasion in the form of new and returning items and collectibles.</p> 
<p>These goods include unique mounts, pets, furnishings, and much more. You can see just some of the items available within Diamond Anniversary Crown Crates below.</p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/06/c66151c85b06753cec012f09cf075c29.jpg" />
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/06/25dcd9b6a5d46d8e181f5d2af04b1816.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Prince Irnskar's Gala Regalia and King Emeric's Diamond Regalia costumes</i></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/06/6f4b3625a2dcc4894068c25327716a7b.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Queen Ayrenn's Diamond Gown costume</i></p>
<img src="https://esossl-a.akamaihd.net/uploads/Community/Article/blogimage/Polymorph_MolagBalIllusion.jpg" />
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/06/8ef5d81052ef4ca65b02c772f8f1333d.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Molag Bal Illusion polymorph and Skin of the Anchorite skin</i></p> 
<p>The luckiest revelers may find especially grand rewards in the form of the Radiant Apex Mounts below. One of these mounts, the Shackled Titan, even has a special summoning animation if called when using the Molag Bal Illusion polymorph!</p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/06/e041472b30b1627565c000dff4d360a1.jpg" />
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/06/e5ef26000d1ad6df773029f5c4a137df.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Worm Cultist Senche-raht and Tharn's Lucent Revelry Senche mounts</i></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/06/15c7bea48ad16f96c051c2bd69d620ab.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Shackled Titan mount</i></p> 
<p>Diamond Anniversary Crown Crates will be available in one-, four-, and 15-crate bundles in addition to a unique 25-crate offering, the Diamond Anniversary Crate Bundle, that is available as a one-time purchase only. In addition to the crates, this special bundle also includes the Coldharbour Recall Customized Action.</p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/06/1f52eff6cba31db5cf9cfcc5d0d35a87.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Celebrate with this bundle of Crown Crates!</i></p> 
<p>This customized action will be unlocked automatically and added to your collectibles when the one-off bundle is first purchased. It is not part of the Diamond Anniversary crates themselves.</p> 
<p>Of course, the above is just some of the finery held in waiting for this momentous release. If you wish to see the full list of items you have a chance to receive when opening a Diamond Anniversary Crown Crate, check out <a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/660702">this thread</a> on our official forums.</p> 
<p>Be warned, when the new crates go live, the <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65723">currently available Order of the Lamp Crates</a> will be removed from the Crown Store in turn, so don't forget to pick them up while they're still available!</p> 
<p>Diamond Anniversary Crown Crates arrive this Thursday, June 20 at 10AM EDT, and you can acquire them from the Crown Crate section of the in-game Crown Store. Will you be celebrating in style? Share your festive plans and looks via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>. </p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Crown Store</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/06/183d368d4915fea341a39956ae007749.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Your Labors Are Rewarded during the Zeal of Zenithar In-Game Event]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66255</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66255</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Honor the God of Commerce to receive hard work's rewards during the Zeal of Zenithar in-game event!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/06/86e7550fdc628bef6633f8e5c6ffa840.jpg" /><p><i>Honor the God of Commerce to receive hard work's rewards during the Zeal of Zenithar in-game event!</i></p> 
<h2>Work Hard and Prosper</h2> 
<p>The Zeal of Zenithar in-game event returns on June 20 at 10AM EDT, and it runs until July 2 at 10AM EDT. To get started, pick up the introductory quest "The Unrefusable Offer" from Amminus Varo at the Belkarth festival grounds or acquire the free quest starter from the Crown Store. Having trouble locating Belkarth? Don't worry; just head over to the nearest Impresario tent and take the nearby portal. Upon finishing the intro quest, you unlock the daily quest, "Honest Toil."</p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/06/d71e555cee7f13e569acf66be881b4a9.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Seek Amminus Varo to begin your labors</i></p> 
<p>During the event, the first time you complete the daily quest each day, you receive a Zenithar's Sublime Parcel box as a bonus reward. Each subsequent completion of the “Honest Toil” quest during that same day rewards you with a Zenithar's Delightful Parcel box.</p> 
<p>In addition, you can earn Zenithar's Delightful Parcel boxes by participating in the following activities:</p> 
<ul><li>Completing the introductory quest “The Unrefusable Offer”</li><li>Completing any Master Writ, per discipline, per account, each day</li><ul><li>Subsequent Master Writs of the same discipline won't provide further boxes until the daily reset</li></ul><li>First daily Crafting Writ, per account, completed each day</li><li>Each time you defeat a world boss while grouped with a player who is in at least one of your player guilds</li><li>Each time you complete a world event while grouped with a player who is in at least one of your player guilds</li></ul> 
<p>You also have a <b>chance</b> to earn a Zenithar's Delightful Parcel box when conquering each round of a group-based arena challenge or completing a Cycle in the Infinite Archive while teamed up with a player who is a member of at least one of your guilds. Additionally, the final round's reward chest contains a guaranteed parcel, as will Tho'at Replicanum's reward chest.</p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/06/100c72fa3802f776bd5fc86cedbb2b75.jpg" />
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/06/756dd9d5b008f4e02fb579dbd23532d9.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Trade and toil </i></p> 
<p>If (Divines forefend!) you aren't the sort to practice an honest trade, you may discover parcels scattered across Tamriel by pickpocketing citizens and looting strongboxes or thieves troves. Maybe crime does pay, as long as some other rube is doing the hard work first!</p> 
<p>Within either parcel box (Sublime or Delightful), there is a chance to receive the following rewards:</p> 
<ul><li>A tradeable outfit style page for the <b>new </b>Gold Road Dragoon outfit style armor</li><ul><li>If you've already earned a Gold Road Dragoon style page for the day, you have a chance to instead get a style page for a past Zeal of Zenithar event set such as the High Rock Spellsword outfit style armor, Kwama Miner's Kit armor outfit style, or Ashen Militia weapon outfit style.</li></ul><li>Durable crafting materials, provisioning ingredients, alchemy reagents, runestones, or a motif style item</li><li>Crafting boosters</li><ul><li>Chance to drop a gold-tier booster or a research time scroll</li></ul><li>Furnishing or provisioning recipes</li><li>Repair kits, siege repair kits, or a small chance for an Impresario Group Repair Kit</li><li>Treasure Maps, Survey Reports, Imperial City vault keys, Companion gear, or a random currency pouch.</li><ul><li>The random currency pouch can contain either gold or Tel Var stones; there is an extremely small chance that you discover a jackpot that allots 100,000 of the associated currency! </li><ul><li>The earnings from this pouch, jackpot or otherwise, are unaffected by any form of currency boosts</li></ul></ul></ul>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/06/7418b660301b1349c57d59fc47a7b634.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Honor the Divines as a Gold Road Dragoon</i></p> 
<p>Both boxes can contain any of the above, but the Sublime Parcel boxes provide a higher chance to contain the more valuable rewards.</p> 
<h2>Good Deeds Go Round Tamriel</h2> 
<p>These boxes won't be the only bonus rewards you can enjoy during the Zeal of Zenithar event. Throughout the duration, you'll benefit from the following modified global in-game effects:</p> 
<ul><li>Wayshrine travel costs are reduced by 75%</li><li>Repair costs on vendors are reduced by 50%</li><li>Crafting inspiration gain from all sources is increased by 100%</li><li>Vendor prices across Tamriel are reduced by 10%</li><ul><li>These include:</li><ul><li>Vendors that sell items for gold, AP, or Tel Var stones, including the Golden Vendor</li><li>Houses purchasable for gold</li></ul></ul></ul> 
<h2>Event Tickets &amp; Vendors</h2> 
<p>If you participate in the Zeal of Zenithar event, you also receive three Event Tickets the first time you complete the “Honest Toil” quest each day. By the end of the event, you can collect a whopping 39 tickets!</p> 
<p>Thankfully, the Impresario is well-stocked to help you make good use of your gathered wealth. You'll even have your first opportunity to complete the Master of Schemes personality with the release of its third fragment.</p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/06/24f94af4ee71a97012ab795e468c6054.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Ensure your just rewards with masterful scheming</i></p><p>During the event period, the Impresario stocks:</p> <ul><li>All three Molag Bal Illusion Imp pet fragments</li><ul><li>Anchor Chain Fragment</li><li>Dark Anchor Pinion</li><li>Effigy of the Dominator</li></ul><li>All three Master of Schemes personality fragments</li><ul><li>Cold Iron Gauntlet</li><li>Grim Iron Mask</li><li>(NEW) Tyrant's Soul Gem</li></ul><li><b>NEW</b> bound style pages for the Gold Road Dragoon outfit style armor</li><li>Group Repair Kits</li><li>Companion Guild Commendations</li></ul><p>Additionally, during the event, the Impresario's Assistant Philius Dormier offers the following goodies:</p><ul><li>All three Unstable Morpholith pet fragments</li><ul><li>Deadlands Flint</li><li>Rune-Etched Striker</li><li>Smoldering Bloodgrass Tinder</li></ul><li>All three Deadlands Scorcher skin fragments</li><ul><li>Rune-Scribed Daedra Hide</li><li>Rune-Scribed Daedra Sleeve</li><li>Rune-Scribed Daedra Veil</li></ul><li>All three Soulfire Dragon Illusion pet fragments</li><ul><li>Hallowed Hourglass Basin</li><li>Illuminated Dragon Scroll</li><li>Kvatchian Incense</li></ul><li>All three Scales of Akatosh skin fragments</li><ul><li>Aureate Anointing Oils</li><li>Lustrous Ritual Sand</li><li>Sacred Scale</li></ul></ul><p>Last but certainly not least, the Indrik vendor Nenulaure's shop is stocked with the following items:<br></p><ul><li>Nascent Indrik Feathers</li><li>Onyx Indrik Berries</li><li>Mossheart Indrik Berries</li><li>Ebon-Glow Indrik pet</li><li>Sapling Indrik pet</li></ul>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/06/d38e826229c85db13f9c863ecf150571.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Nenulaure the Indrik Vendor</i></p> 
<h2>May Zenithar Fill Your Coffer</h2> 
<p>With Zenithar watching over you during this event, you can earn incredible rewards for your hard work. Ready to pitch in and see the fruits of honest labor arrive as in-game rewards? Let us know whether you'll be honoring the Trader God via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>. </p> 
<p><i>The Zeal of Zenithar in-game event begins June 20 at 10:00AM EDT, and it runs until Tuesday, July 2 at 10:00AM EDT.</i></p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Events</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/06/86e7550fdc628bef6633f8e5c6ffa840.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Celebrate ESO's 10th Anniversary with Us in Grazzano Visconti, Italy!]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66243</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66243</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Sign up today and join other members of the #ESOFam in Italy for an unforgettable night of mystery and fun!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/06/4cf1fb044f13751a24eef4aaaccc6d0e.jpg" /><p><i>Sign up today and join other members of the #ESOFam in Italy for an unforgettable night of mystery and fun!</i></p> 
<p>The <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/anniversary">worldwide 10-Year Anniversary Celebration</a> continues with even more awesome in-person community events. This time, we're inviting players to gather for an evening of <i>ESO</i>-themed fun in the picturesque Italian village of Grazzano Visconti.</p> 
<p>On September 14, guests will arrive at the Ristorante il Biscione and take part in a live Tamriel adventure experience. This will include several whodunit mystery games, so keep your wits about you—these puzzles are worthy of Investigator Vale! Once the games have been completed, community members will be invited to partake in a banquet with their fellow sleuths.</p> 
<p>Want to sign up? Select the button below and follow the instructions to register. Guest slots are limited, so snag your ticket ASAP!</p><p><i><br></i></p><p>If you have any questions regarding event details, please reach out to us on our Italian social channels via <a href="https://twitter.com/bethesda_it">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/bethesda_it/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline.it/">Facebook</a>.</p><p><i>ESO's</i> 10-Year Anniversary Celebration continues all across the globe, and the party isn't done yet! Keep an eye out for news on future events you won't want to miss. Are you excited to join us and other passionate community members in Italy to commemorate an entire decade of <i>ESO?</i> Let us know via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Community</category>
            <category>10th Anniversary</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/06/4cf1fb044f13751a24eef4aaaccc6d0e.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Anniversary Celebration—Dazzle Your Friends with a Flashy Emote from Alienware]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66221</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66221</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Claim a free in-game emote via this 10-Year Anniversary promotion!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/06/75f87acfd13a9b3038f589a209fef51b.jpg" /><p><i>Claim a free in-game emote via this 10-Year Anniversary promotion!</i></p> 
<p>The ongoing 10-Year Anniversary Celebration continues, and we are thrilled to announce more player rewards—this time in partnership with Alienware™! You can now claim the Pyromancer's Quandary emote for <i>ESO</i> while supplies last.</p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/06/c1f3631b9b3d003cf7deb703be00de71.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>The Pyromancer's Quandary</i></p> 
<p>All you need to do is sign in or create a free account with <a href="https://www.alienwarearena.com/ucf/show/2171337/boards/contest-and-giveaways-global/Giveaway/the-elder-scrolls-online-pyromancers-quandary-emote-key-giveaway">Alienware Arena</a> and click “GET KEY” on <a href="https://www.alienwarearena.com/ucf/show/2171337/boards/contest-and-giveaways-global/Giveaway/the-elder-scrolls-online-pyromancers-quandary-emote-key-giveaway">this page</a>. You can then redeem it on the official <i>ESO</i> website using these steps:</p> 
<p>1. Copy the Reward Code provided in your email from Alienware.</p> 
<p>2. Confirm that you own a copy of <i>The Elder Scrolls Online</i> before redeeming a Reward Code. </p> 
<p>3. Navigate to this URL and sign into your <i>ESO </i>account: <a href="https://account.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/redeem-code">https://account.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/redeem-code</a> </p> 
<p>4. Enter the code and click Redeem Code to submit.</p> 
<p>To sign up or find more information and support, visit Alienware's <a href="http://www.aw.gg/arena">official website</a>.</p> 
<p>Are you excited to show your friends and guildmates your pyromantic potential? Let us know via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>10th Anniversary</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/06/75f87acfd13a9b3038f589a209fef51b.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Try Out ESO Plus for Free to Enjoy Unlimited Crafting Storage, DLC Access, & More]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66079</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66079</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Welcome the arrival of Gold Road with access to DLCs such as Scribes of Fate, Scions of Ithelia, and more with an ESO Plus™ free trial!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/06/40fbc1ad52fcab9c911388a3e617ed90.jpg" /><p><i>Welcome the arrival of Gold Road with access to DLCs such as Scribes of Fate, Scions of Ithelia, and more with an ESO Plus™ free trial!</i><br></p> 
<h2>Enjoy ESO Plus on Us</h2> 
<p>The ESO Plus Free Trial is live from now until Wednesday, June 19, 2024 at 10:00AM EDT. During the trial period, you can enjoy the following ESO Plus benefits with no credit card required and no strings attached:</p> 
<ul><li>Full access to over 20 DLC game packs—new zones, quests, dungeons, and more</li><ul><li>Includes access to the zones from last year's <i>Necrom</i> release (Note that players on Xbox and PlayStation consoles will need to wait until after <i>Gold Road</i> launches on June 18 to access <i>Necrom</i>)</li><li>Includes 28 group dungeons (including the <i>Scions of Ithelia</i> dungeons from earlier this year), systems such as Antiquities and Tales of Tribute, and more!</li></ul><li>A Craft Bag providing unlimited storage for all your crafting materials </li><li>Double Bank space for all characters on your account </li><li>10% increase to experience, gold, and Archival Fortune acquisition, crafting inspiration, and trait research rates </li><li>Double furnishings and collectibles space in player housing </li><li>Exclusive ability to dye costumes </li><li>Double Transmute Crystal storage</li></ul> 
<p>Eager to check out ESO Plus for free? Here's what you need to do:</p> 
<ol><li>Log in to <i>The Elder Scrolls Online</i></li><li>Navigate to the Crown Store</li><li>Select the ESO Plus tab</li><li>Select “Free Trial!”</li></ol> 
<p>Once you've activated your trial, all the benefits listed above are available to you until June 19. Note that this free trial does <b>not</b> grant access to the Companions from the <i>Blackwood</i>, <i>High Isle</i>, or <i>Necrom</i> Chapters.</p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/06/9db07c7eb9e9a2428a3e49640779ef4d.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Explore the Telvanni Peninsula with ESO Plus!</i></p> 
<p>If you'd like to continue to enjoy the benefits of ESO Plus beyond the trial, including monthly crown stipends and exclusive in-game deals, you can get full membership via our ESO Plus page! Want to learn more? Check out our <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/guides/esoplusguide">ESO Plus guide</a>.</p> 
<h2>ESO Plus Is a Plus to Have</h2> 
<p>Boosts to XP and gold gains, additional bag space, DLC access, and more await those with ESO Plus membership, and you can try out these incredible benefits with no credit card required and no strings attached during the free trial period. </p> 
<p>Are you excited to enjoy the benefits of membership at no cost? Let us know via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>. </p> 
<p><i>The ESO Plus Free Trial is now live and will run until Wednesday, June 19, 2024 at 10:00AM EDT.</i></p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>ESO Plus</category>
            <category>Crown Store</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/06/40fbc1ad52fcab9c911388a3e617ed90.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PC/Mac Update 42 Known Issues]]></title>
            <link>https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/659638/pc-mac-update-42-known-issues</link>
            <guid>https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/659638/pc-mac-update-42-known-issues</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 19:27:08 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[Hi everyone,<br><br>
In an effort to collate issues discovered after today's launch of Update 42, below is a list of notable known issues and their current status. We'll make a note in the subject when we make any edits or updates.
<ul><li><b>Cannot travel to Eyevea Wayshrine</b>
<ul><li>STATUS: To be fixed in upcoming incremental</li>
<li>NOTE: Attempting to jump to this Wayshrine will still deduct gold</li>
</ul></li>
<li><b>Resource bars appear to be buffed when buffs are not active</b>
<ul><li>STATUS: To be fixed in upcoming incremental</li>
<li>NOTE: This is just a UI/visual issue</li>
</ul></li>
<li><b>Health bars have a permanent glow</b>
<ul><li>STATUS: To be fixed in upcoming incremental</li>
<li>NOTE: This is just a UI/visual issue</li>
</ul></li>
<li><b>Game can occasionally crash</b> (both in-game or prior to logging in)
<ul><li>STATUS: Investigating</li>
</ul></li>
<li><b>A second Arcane Knot can appear in rare circumstances if the player character holding the Knot dies to damage from the Knot</b>
<ul><li>STATUS: To be fixed in upcoming incremental</li>
</ul></li>
<li><b>Abilities appear to be duplicating on the ability bar after using a Skill Respec Scroll and swapping skills on your ability bar</b>
<ul><li>STATUS: To be fixed in upcoming incremental</li>
<li>NOTE: This is just a visual issue affecting the icon; the correct ability will still be used</li>
</ul></li>
<li><b>Wrathsun Staff and Basalt Blooded Staff visuals are incorrect</b>
<ul><li>STATUS: To be fixed in upcoming incremental</li>
<li>NOTE: This visual issue may be all staves with this specific model - we are investigating.</li>
</ul></li>
<li><b>Incorrect directions out of Scholarium during Scribing tutorial</b>
<ul><li>STATUS: To be fixed in Update 43</li>
<li>After entering the Scholarium during the Scribing tutorial, while on other quests you are being directed to leave the area via a portal that hasn't yet been unlocked</li>
</ul></li>
<li><b>Dragon is occasionally missing during Wing of the Dragon quest</b>
<ul><li>STATUS: To be fixed in upcoming incremental</li>
<li>NOTE: You can still interact with an invisible Dragon, should she not appear</li>
</ul></li>
<li><b>"How To Scribe" Tutorial Book is currently set as an item instead of a Collectible</b>
<ul><li>STATUS: To be fixed in upcoming incremental</li>
</ul></li>
<li><b>One of the components required for the achievement "Gold Sword for Hire" states "Gold Road Sojourner" instead of the intended "Gold Road Professional" </b>
<ul><li>STATUS: To be fixed in upcoming incremental</li>
</ul></li>
</ul>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>Forum</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Crown Store Showcase—June 2024]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66157</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66157</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Find a home on the high seas or claim Undaunted plunder with new Crown Store goods this month!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/962fd2536f72aa7754c0cf804b2ed8c0327363.jpg" /><p><i>Find a home on the high seas or claim Undaunted plunder with new Crown Store goods this month!</i></p> 
<p>Below, you can review all the items available in (and coming to) the in-game Crown Store throughout June 2024. Don't forget to also check out what is currently available on the <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/crownstore">Crown Store page</a>. Fancy any of these goods? Then head over to the <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/buycrowns">Buy Crowns page</a> to secure the crowns you need! Certain items and offers will be available for a limited time only, so be sure to read their details below and don't miss out.</p> 
<h2>ESO Plus Deals</h2> 
<p>All ESO Plus™ members have access to a monthly selection of exclusive deals and items. You can find more information about them in <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/54825">this article</a>.</p> 
<p><b>Exclusive Free Items</b></p> 
<p><b>Statuette: Peryite, Blightlord </b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/18df619754737bd63d7423d96dd38cb2.jpg" />
<p><i>A miniature statue of Peryite, the Daedric Prince of Pestilence.</i></p> 
<p>The Statuette: Peryite, Blightlord will be available in the Crown Store FREE, exclusively to ESO Plus Members on all platforms for a limited time, from June 27, 2024 at 10 AM EDT, to July 29, 2024 at 10 AM EDT.</p> 
<h2>Crafting</h2> 
<p><b>Crown Crafting Motif: Huntsman </b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/3135c66cb2311c4669d91f8496ecf2b5.jpg" />
<p><i>For those who would honor Hircine the Hunter, it is right and proper to adopt the apparel and arms of his Huntsmen, those spear-shakers, fewterers, and whippers-in of the Lord of the Hunting Grounds.—Uraccanach the Witchman</i></p> 
<p>The Crown Crafting Motif: Huntsman will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from June 3, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to June 6, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item. Huntsman Motif chapters, and very rarely the complete book, have a chance to drop from Balorgh in March of Sacrifices.</p> 
<p><b>Crown Crafting Motif: Shardborn</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/5c3802102594f1f2b1a00d6bb6334964.jpg" />
<p><i>Glass-smiths form Shardborn arms and armor using creatia and sand in secretive techniques they hold dear. Use to learn the Shardborn crafting style.</i></p> 
<p>The Crown Crafting Motif: Shardborn will be available in the Crown Store with the launch of <i>Gold Road </i>and Update 42 coming June 3, 2024 for PC/Mac, and on June 18, 2024 for Xbox One, Xbox Series X|S, PlayStation 4, and PlayStation 5. Shardborn Motif chapters, and very rarely the complete book, have a chance to drop from Skingrad Reward Coffers, acquired by completing daily Delve quests from Lieutenant Agrance and daily World Boss quests from Commander Salerius in Skingrad.</p> 
<p><b>Crown Crafting Motif: Wayward Guardian</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/acf0bac005e7a005d50e3c406e6430ee.jpg" />
<p><i>Arana of the Ghostsong Clan notes this about Wayward Guardian gear: "If the deepfolk sought the protection of the Witch, Hunter, and Headsman to create their otherworldly works, let us turn that strength against our equally unnatural foes." Use to learn the Wayward Guardian crafting style.</i></p> 
<p>The Crown Crafting Motif: Wayward Guardian will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from June 6, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to June 10, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item. Wayward Guardian Motif chapters have a chance to drop from a Wayward Guardian's Cache, acquired by completing daily quests from Ardanir in Markarth.</p> 
<p><b>Crown Crafting Motif: Meridian</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/f0ff1fe7aefb6ea0aa7098e315e302f4.jpg" />
<p><i>From ancient times till the present, the Cult of Meridia, no matter how often suppressed, always rebounds and reappears. Mortals who revere her often honor her by adopting an armor style inspired by that of the Aurorans, Meridia's Daedric warriors. Use to learn the Meridian crafting style.</i></p> 
<p>The Crown Crafting Motif: Meridian will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from June 10, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to June 13, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item. Meridian Motif chapters, and very rarely the complete book, have a chance to drop from Symphony of Blades in the Depths of Malatar.</p> 
<p><b>Crown Crafting Motif: Nighthollow</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/5c100012078a73522e996974cc8c3712.jpg" />
<p><i>The panoply of the Nighthollow vampires evokes the sublime terror of their shadowy domain. Mortals who see this fearsome armor rarely keep their blood for long. Use to learn the Nighthollow crafting style.</i></p> 
<p>The Crown Crafting Motif: Nighthollow will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from June 24, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to June 27, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item. Nighthollow Motif chapters, and very rarely the complete book, have a chance to drop from Markarth Reward Coffers, acquired by completing the Harrowstorm daily quest for Nelldena in Markarth.</p> 
<p><b>Outfit Style</b></p> 
<p><b>Symphony of Blades Arms Pack </b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/f46da91768f338906a7b779bb5e75d4b.jpg" />
<p><i>Urgarlag Chief-bane may tell you of the sunken ruins of Malatar, where Meridia's champions—such as the Symphony of Blades—await. Alter your weapon's appearance to match the Undaunted Symphony of Blades awards by using this complete set of Outfit styles.</i></p> 
<p>The Symphony of Blades Arms Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from June 3, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to June 6, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item. The matching mask page will have a small chance to drop from Symphony of Blades from veteran Depths of Malatar. The matching shoulder page can be purchased from Urgarlag Chief-bane for 50 Undaunted keys, or has a chance of dropping from Urgarlag's Mystery Coffer for 1 key. Having the achievement “Throwing Shade” increases the drop chances of both items.</p> 
<p><b>Ilambris Arms Pack </b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/8d2951cd4de9acd16952c4b45f9b8852.jpg" />
<p><i>Undaunted veteran Glirion may warn you of the Ilambris twins, who serve as wardens in the Crypt of Hearts, Alter your weapon's appearance to match the Undaunted Ilambris awards by using this complete set of Outfit styles.</i></p> 
<p>The Ilambris Arms Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from June 10, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to June 13, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item. The matching mask page will have a small chance to drop from the Ilambris twins from veteran Crypt of Hearts I. The matching shoulder page can be purchased from Glirion the Redbeard for 50 Undaunted keys, or has a chance of dropping from Glirion's Mystery Coffer for 1 key. Having the achievement “A Crypt for Two” increases the drop chances of both items.</p> 
<p><b>Pirate Skeleton Arms Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/7d5958e91170bde58894b17c1140e42e.jpg" />
<p><i>Captain Blackheart and his pirate crew may control an idyllic haven in Bangkorai, but Glirion the Redbeard hopes to change that—through you. Alter your weapon's appearance to match the Undaunted Pirate Skeleton awards by using this complete set of Outfit styles.</i></p> 
<p>The Pirate Skeleton Arms Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from June 13, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to June 17, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item. The matching mask page will have a small chance to drop from Captain Blackheart from veteran Blackheart Haven. The matching shoulder page can be purchased from Glirion the Redbeard for 50 Undaunted keys, or has a chance of dropping from Glirion's Mystery Coffer for 1 key. Having the achievement “Thoroughly Plundered” increases the drop chances of both items.</p> 
<p><b>Gold Road Dragoon Arms Pack </b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/c4c396a429f8a5b31b4d703d912630ae.jpg" />
<p><i>Those who patrol and ensure the safety of travelers along the Gold Road use matching weapons that feature the red diamond. Alter your weapon's appearance to match the Gold Road Dragoon Weapons by using this complete set of Gold Road Dragoon Outfit styles.</i></p> 
<p>The new Gold Road Dragoon Arms Pack will be available in the Crown Store during the Zeal of Zenithar event, from June 20, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to July 2, 2024 at 10AM EDT. Matching armor pages will drop from Zenithar's Sublime Parcel, obtainable once per day for the duration of the event. Bound versions of the armor pages can be purchased from the Impresario for 5 Event Tickets each during the event.</p> 
<p><b>Anvil of Zenithar Arms Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/f19e382d667589ec58c1328cb96d66d4.jpg" />
<p><i>The blessings of Zenithar, God of Work and Commerce, light up weapons forged on his sacred anvil. Alter your weapon's appearance by using this complete set of Anvil of Zenithar Outfit styles.</i></p> 
<p>The Anvil of Zenithar Arms Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from June 24, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to June 27, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<h2>Wardrobe</h2> 
<p><b>Rimmen Fountain-Side Loungewear </b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/7dac4e0b5b261e622dc11a509027c500.jpg" />
<p><i>Famed for their clear water, the fountains of Rimmen provide a place for locals to gather and catch up on the news of the day. If you seek a moment of refreshment, wear this elegant yet comfortable garb as you dangle your feet in the cool waters.</i></p> 
<p>The Rimmen Fountain-Side Loungewear costume will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from June 10, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to June 13, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<p><b>Pirate Costume Pack </b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/ccfb9cffc46db9aefd4472dda1f8c755.jpg" />
<p><i>The pirates of the Abecean Sea are among Tamriel's fiercest sea raiders—and they have a style all their own, which you can adopt when you don these jaunty and rakish costumes!</i></p> 
<p>The Pirate Costume Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from June 13, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to June 17, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<p><b>Dremora Deceiver Duster </b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/257a492369cd43a271a4642580ea35fb.jpg" />
<p><i>In the ceaseless wars of Oblivion, there will always be scoundrels. After rooking marks of goods and foes of lives, this rugged, Dremora-style coat lets you slink away, sounding no louder than a whisper.</i></p> 
<p>The Dremora Deceiver Duster will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from June 24, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to June 27, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<h2>Crate</h2> 
<p><b>Dwarven Crate</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/b3901af9f6aeee1238b18428623f6c9c.jpg" />
<p><i>A mystery collection of Dwarven-themed items!</i></p> 
<p>Dwarven Crates return to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from June 6, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to June 20, 2024 at 10AM EDT.</p> 
<h2>DLC</h2> 
<p><b>Necrom Deluxe Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/7f8806ce8ecd8a9fb42c345192e9bef6.jpg" />
<p><i>Includes all the bonus content of the Necrom Deluxe Edition, as well as the Necrom pre-purchase digital items.</i></p> 
<p>The <i>Necrom</i> Deluxe Pack will be available in the Crown Store with the launch of <i>Gold Road </i>and Update 42 coming June 3, 2024 for PC/Mac, and on June 18, 2024 for Xbox One, Xbox Series X|S, PlayStation 4, and PlayStation 5.</p> 
<p> </p> 
<p><b>Necrom</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/d39b1aa78c03198f3c880af648a4425c.jpg" />
<p><i>What truths are best left hidden? Discover Necrom and delve into the forbidden secrets of Apocrypha. From Morrowind's Telvanni Peninsula to Hermaeus Mora's realm, fight to preserve reality.</i></p> 
<p>The<i> Necrom</i> Chapter will be available in the Crown Store with the launch of <i>Gold Road </i>and Update 42 coming June 3, 2024 for PC/Mac, and on June 18, 2024 for Xbox One, Xbox Series X|S, PlayStation 4, and PlayStation 5.</p> 
<p><b>Class: Arcanist</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/29c4ad472ab07eae495f781f8d8eabb6.jpg" />
<p><i>Unlocks the Arcanist class for use in character creation.</i></p> 
<p>The Arcanist class will be available in the Crown Store with the launch of <i>Gold Road </i>and Update 42 coming June 3, 2024 at 2AM EDT for PC/Mac, and on June 18, 2024 at 2AM EDT for Xbox One, Xbox Series X|S, PlayStation 4, and PlayStation 5.</p> 
<h2>Events </h2> 
<p><b>Currency</b></p> 
<p><b>Event Tickets</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2022/01/d80129d699abe5116dbb4fb22c2d4b5b.jpg" />
<p><i>A ticket used to purchase rare goods from The Impresario, Event Merchant. Curious as to what goods? Well, chat with her to see what she has to offer!</i></p> 
<p>Single Event Tickets will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time during the Zeal of Zenithar event, from June 20, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to July 2, 2024 at 10AM EDT. Event Tickets are also giftable to other players from within the Crown Store. </p> 
<h2>Furniture </h2> 
<p><b>Music Box, Subterranean Sonata </b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/1eaaa1e50fb21d85aeb0ee062f7a0a4b.jpg" />
<p><i>When activated, plays a music box arrangement of the otherworldly "Subterranean Sonata" composition.</i></p> 
<p>The Music Box, Subterranean Sonata will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from June 6, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to June 10, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<p><b>Furnishing Pack: Maormer Boarding Party </b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/80c4b944a3325d1014eaafdb1f1b5c69.jpg" />
<p><i>The Sea Elves rule the waves, but you've beaten them just the same. Celebrate your victory in battle by furnishing your home with "liberated" serpentine items, including a raiding party tent and a Maormer ship's prow!</i></p> 
<p>The Furnishing Pack: Maormer Boarding Party will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from June 13, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to June 27, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<p><b>Cadwell's Astounding Portal </b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/e0e2a5599fcb180b6a6d3dd19266b257.jpg" />
<p><i>Ready for a jolly good time with Cadwell? Summon him to your home with this handy portal, and he'll play a tune, juggle fish, indulge in some chit-chat, or more! Alas, Cadwell refuses to do preview performances.</i></p> 
<p>Cadwell's Astounding Portal will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from June 17, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to June 20, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<p><b>Furnishing Pack: Aquatic Splendor </b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/888299ca342eb445c0017d85bdd64ffe.jpg" />
<p><i>Add oceanic depth to your abode with this seaworthy arrangement of home furnishings. An abundance of vibrant coral and kelp, effervescent bubbles and jellyfish, and even a mudcrab sparring partner can turn your home into a deep-sea wonderland.</i></p> 
<p>The Furnishing Pack: Aquatic Splendor will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from June 27, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to July 11, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<h2>Houses</h2> 
<p><b>Merryvine Estate </b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/5b5dc0f34448f91dc068970e14a63f5c.jpg" />
<p><i>Merryvine's wines once rivaled those of the nearby Valente Vineyard, but misfortune sent its former owner fleeing. This sun-kissed estate features fertile grapevines, a house suitable for entertaining, and facilities that would please any vintner.</i></p> 
<p>Merryvine Estate will be available in the Crown Store with the launch of <i>Gold Road </i>and Update 42 coming June 3, 2024 for PC/Mac, and on June 18, 2024 for Xbox One, Xbox Series X|S, PlayStation 4, and PlayStation 5. Furnished and unfurnished versions will be available.</p> 
<p><b>The Fair Winds</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/9d438de952d2bad68d90ae4afd13a29a.jpg" />
<p><i>Enjoy sea-based living on the Fair Winds, a spacious galleon hailing from the Systres Isles. You have a bevy of travel options a mere spin of the ship's wheel away, with ports of call in Vulkhel Guard, Davon's Watch, and Daggerfall. Just watch for ornaugs!</i></p> 
<p>The Fair Winds returns to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from June 13, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to June 27, 2024 at 10AM EDT. Furnished and unfurnished versions will be available.</p> 
<p><b>Seaveil Spire </b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/77bbf65e3862e00d8fb1428d860a6762.jpg" />
<p><i>Early in the First Era, a pious tribe of Nedes followed the Tower's guidance to an undersea anomaly, where they built a submerged sanctuary. Millennia later, the edifice and anomaly remain, providing a secure and wondrous escape from the surface world.</i></p> 
<p>Seaveil Spire returns to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from June 27, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to July 11, 2024 at 10AM EDT. Furnished and unfurnished versions will be available.</p> 
<h2>Houseguests</h2> 
<p><b>Clan Mother Tadali </b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/138836652c3ed9a78b351b15c01d27f3.jpg" />
<p><i>Get ready for a visit from Clan Mother Tadali! She'll share her wisdom with you if you share your sunbeams with her. After adding Tadali to your home, you can set her on a path, plus you and your visitors can speak with her.</i></p> 
<p>Clan Mother Tadali will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from June 13, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to June 17, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<h2>Assistants</h2> 
<p><b>Tzozabrar, Dwarven Deconstructor </b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/f2fbc14f5c9a0d4d20e0d42dd9f4aab9.jpg" />
<p><i>Tzozabrar will intake items you don't need, expelling useful materials no doubt scavenged from a Dwarven construct. Tonal interference makes it unusable in Cyrodiil or Battlegrounds.</i></p> 
<p>The new Tzozabrar, Dwarven Deconstructor assistant will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from June 27, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to July 11, 2024 at 10AM EDT.</p> 
<h2>Mounts</h2> 
<p><b>Meridian Sabre Cat</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/625826055d5689776b043f31a885148b.jpg" />
<p><i>"Some accounts of Meridia's plane of the Colored Rooms describe a menagerie of light-imbued spectral beasts elevated from Nirn and 'purified' by the Lady's holy light."—Sayings of Valasha</i></p> 
<p>The Meridian Sabre Cat mount will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from June 10, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to June 13, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<p><b>Ossified Rime Wolf</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/3c1cb929e8727d1dfd9dbcf524e88f35.jpg" />
<p><i>"Tears of rage and hatred don't go wasted in Skyrim. These rare droplets fall upon the snow, calling a spirit of bone and rime from Aetherius. Within seconds, a frost-spiked wolf forms, snarling and bridled with grim purpose."—Hef, Tale Collector</i></p> 
<p>The Ossified Rime Wolf mount will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from June 13, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to June 17 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<p><b>Stitchedwell Stick Guar </b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/7a43c0497b7510e8f06a6ea721f5011f.jpg" />
<p><i>Soul Shriven knights ride only the most finely stitched steeds. As one old knight proclaimed, "Don't mind the bit of fray at the bottom there. Or the pesky splinters sticking out of the handle. This guar is a jolly smooth ride!"</i></p> 
<p>The Stitchedwell Stick Guar mount will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from June 17, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to June 20, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><b>Baysong Quasigriff</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/cc43407abbdc38a1de4fc07abe481cc1.jpg" />
<p><i>Unlike their mainland cousins, the quasigriffs of the Systres Archipelago have vibrant, sea-tinted feathers. Admittedly, Irastimil Direnni never intended to create such colorful creatures. Noble Bretons adore them and travel about High Isle on their backs.</i></p> 
<p>The Baysong Quasigriff mount will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from June 27, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to July 1, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<h2>Customized Actions</h2> 
<p><b>Dwarven Sphere Chop </b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/52120a1ee22861be73dea6e73db34600.jpg" />
<p><i>Why break a sweat by chopping wood yourself when you can have a Dwarven Sphere do it for you?</i></p> 
<p>The new Dwarven Sphere Chop customized action will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from June 6, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to June 10, 2024 at 10AM EDT. </p> 
<h2>Pets</h2> 
<p><b>Meridian Sabre Cub </b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/0f8e9fadeb76724c34a4b146aa0b66f1.jpg" />
<p><i>"Our Lady of the Infinite Energies, Strict but Fair Arbiter of Inner Luminance, grant unto thy most devoted worshiper a sign of thy radiant favor, mayhap a loveable, glowing Sabre Cat cub."—Sayings of Valasha</i></p> 
<p>The Meridian Sabre Cub pet will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from June 10, 2024 at 10AM EDT, to June 13, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p> 
<h2>Upgrades</h2> 
<p><b>West Weald Skyshards</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/d7c9297e78597f96344505352591dc22.jpg" />
<p><i>Instantly unlocks the remaining Skyshards in West Weald.</i></p> 
<p>The West Weald Skyshards will be available in the Crown Store with the launch of <i>Gold Road </i>and Update 42 coming June 3, 2024 for PC/Mac, and on June 18, 2024 for Xbox One, Xbox Series X|S, PlayStation 4, and PlayStation 5.</p><p><br></p> 
<p>It seems the <i>Gold Road </i>Chapter isn't the only exciting thing coming to <i>ESO</i> this month! Whether you plan to thwart Daedric plots alongside the Leramil the Wise, bust heads with the Undaunted, or simply get away from it all with a high seas cruise, there's something for you in the Crown Store this June. </p> 
<p>Don't forget, if you wish to acquire any of the above items, you will need to stock up on crowns via the <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/crowns">Buy Crowns page</a> first. Do you have your eye on any of these new or returning items? Let us know via <a name="_Hlk159602221"></a><a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>. </p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Crown Store</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/962fd2536f72aa7754c0cf804b2ed8c0327363.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ESO's June 2024 Survival Guide]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66155</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66155</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Get ready for a massive month of adventure, promotions, and more with this complete guide to everything that's happening in ESO this June.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/7dedd5f12b55e5b7727b96b397e21415.jpg" /><p><i>Get ready for a massive month of adventure, promotions, and more with this complete guide to everything that's happening in ESO this June. </i></p> <p>It's no secret that June is a busy month for <i>The Elder Scrolls Online</i>. In addition to the <b><i>Gold Road</i> Chapter launch</b>, you can enjoy a host of events, 10-Year Anniversary promotions, and rewards. This includes another amazing <b>Anniversary Spotlight</b>, a special giveaway from our <b>friends at Alienware</b>, a new <b>ESO Plus</b>™<b> limited-time reward</b>, and the return of the hardworking <b>Zeal of Zenithar in-game event</b>—phew!</p> <p>To help you stay on top of everything that's coming up next month, here's a complete chronological breakdown!</p><p><br></p><p> </p> <p><b>NVIDIA GeForce NOW Promotion (5/30 - 6/30)</b></p> <p>If you're an <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66075">NVIDIA GeForce NOW member</a>, you can claim the Sungold Bay Thoroughbred mount free from their official website as part of the ongoing 10-Year Anniversary Celebration. You have only until June 30, so hop to it!</p><p><br></p><p> </p> <p><b>Daily Login Rewards (6/1 - 6/30)</b></p> <p><i>ESO</i>'s daily login rewards continue to grow with a <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66115">useful selection of June offerings</a>, including gold, Seals of Endeavor, and more. Don't forget, you have to log in to <i>ESO </i>each day to progress.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> <p><b>Gold Road &amp; Update 42 PC/Mac Launch (6/3) </b></p> <p><i>Gold Road </i>arrives for PC/Mac! <i>ESO</i>'s latest Chapter release concludes the mystery of the Forgotten Prince in addition to a new zone (West Weald), a new system (Scribing), and wide range of unique challenges and rewards. Pre-purchase now for additional in-game rewards.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> <p><b>Anniversary Spotlight—Gold Road PC (6/3 – 7/1) + Consoles (6/18 – 7/16)</b></p> <p>Part of our massive 10-Year Anniversary Celebration, <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66071">this new spotlight</a> asks you to delve deep into the <i>Gold Road </i>Chapter's new Scribing system. Complete the Scribing questline, and you can claim a free multi-rider mount from the Crown Store for a limited time—don't wait!</p><p><br></p><p> </p> <p><b>Alienware Arena Giveaway (6/10)</b></p> <p>If you're a member of the Alienware community, you can log into <a href="https://na.alienwarearena.com/">Alienware Arena</a> and claim the Pyromancer's Quandary in-game emote free. This special offer is only available while codes last—so don't miss out!</p><p><br></p><p> </p> <p><b>Capture the Relic Weekend (6/13 – 6/18)</b></p> <p><i>ESO</i>'s PvP Battlegrounds game mode heats up mid-June with a weekend-long Capture the Relic mini-event.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> <p><b>Gold Road &amp; Update 42 Xbox/PlayStation Launch (6/18)</b></p> <p><i>Gold Road</i> goes live on Xbox and PlayStation consoles. <i>ESO</i>'s latest Chapter release concludes the mystery of the Forgotten Prince in addition to a new zone (West Weald), a new system (Scribing), and a multitude of unique challenges and rewards.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> <p><b>Xbox Game Pass Perks #2 (6/19 – 8/18)</b></p> <p>The next wave of Gold Pass Perks lands for <i>ESO</i>'s Xbox players. Keep an eye out for more details on what's available and how you can claim your goodies in the coming weeks.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> <p><b>ESO Plus</b><b> New Mount Giveaway (6/19 - 7/19)</b></p> <p>If you're an ESO Plus member, you'll appreciate the unique giveaway we're offering starting June 19. Look out for more details on this exclusive reward soon!</p><p><br></p><p> </p> <p><b>Zeal of Zenithar Event (6/20 - 7/2)</b></p> <p>The Zeal of Zenithar in-game event returns! Traders, crafters, and workers of Tamriel come together to celebrate all things commerce during this sure-to-be-profitable event. Check the official website for details closer to launch! </p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/b6360a035cdef67521809ceee342e35f.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>June 2024 10-Year Anniversary Roadmap</i></p> 
<p>We weren't kidding when we said June 2024 is going to be a busy month for <i>The Elder Scrolls Online</i>. With the <i>Gold Road </i>Chapter launch, 10-Year Anniversary Celebration fun, and in-game events and giveaways, there has never been a better time to jump into <i>ESO</i>. Are you excited for a great month of adventure? Let us know via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>.</p> 
<p><i>The Elder Scrolls Online: Gold Road arrives for PC/Mac on June 3, 2024, and for Xbox and PlayStation consoles on June 18, 2024. Pre-purchase Gold Road now to receive unique bonus rewards at launch and immediate access to the Welkyndstone Ruins Wolf mount. Don't miss out!</i></p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Community</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/7dedd5f12b55e5b7727b96b397e21415.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Anniversary Celebration—Explore Tamriel with NVIDIA GeForce NOW & Claim a Free Mount]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66075</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66075</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Play The Elder Scrolls Online using]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/443606cec773fd3bc35b299eac441908.jpg" /><p><i>Play The Elder Scrolls Online using </i><a href="https://www.nvidia.com/en-us/geforce-now/"><i>NVIDIA GeForce NOW</i></a><i> and you can explore Tamriel atop a free Sungold Bay Thoroughbred mount.</i></p> <p>As part of the ongoing 10-Year Anniversary Celebration, we are thrilled to announce a new GeForce NOW promotion, allowing <i>ESO</i>'s adventurers to discover Tamriel's Second Era via their device of choice AND do so atop a free mount. </p> <p>GeForce NOW Premium Members can claim their free mount by <a href="https://www.nvidia.com/en-us/geforce-now/rewards/">opting into rewards</a> and checking their email for instructions. Ultimate and Priority members can redeem <b>starting today</b>, while free members can claim it starting May 31. It's available <b>until June 30</b>, first come first served.<br></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/78cfa9010f9594769893b61e738feb10.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Claim this mount with GeForce NOW</i></p> 
<p>If you are a Steam or Epic Games Store player, you can stream <i>ESO</i> to your devices using the GeForce NOW cloud gaming service, which was revealed during <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65839">April's kickoff of the 10-Year Anniversary Celebration.</a> Sign up for NVIDIA's highest performance membership, Ultimate, and you can stream at up to 4K and 120 fps or enjoy the game at ultrawide resolutions on <a href="https://nvidia.custhelp.com/app/answers/detail/a_id/5462">supported devices</a>. To sign up or find more information and support, visit <a href="https://www.nvidia.com/en-us/geforce-now/">their official website</a>.</p> 
<p>Are you planning to venture into West Weald with GeForce NOW? Are you excited to own this dashing, dappled ride? Tell us via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>. </p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>10th Anniversary</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/443606cec773fd3bc35b299eac441908.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Anniversary Spotlight—Earn a Multi-Rider Mount with Scribing!]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66071</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66071</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Unlock a free multi-rider mount by delving deep into the Gold Road Chapter's new Scribing system this month of June!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/94407a059066148c8650612951a42f37.jpg" /><p><i>Unlock a free multi-rider mount by delving deep into the Gold Road Chapter's new Scribing system this month of June!</i></p> 
<h2>Unravel the Mysteries of Magicka</h2> 
<p>With the upcoming launch of <i>The Elder Scrolls Online: Gold Road</i> (arriving June 3 for PC/Mac and June 18 for Xbox and PlayStation consoles), you can explore the origins of magic in Tamriel via the all-new Scribing system. With Scribing, you can <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_yWOpQ6_T0M">create your own handmade abilities</a> with a near-limitless number of options available. </p> 
<p>To celebrate this incredible new feature and Chapter launch, we're happy to announce the Anniversary Spotlight—Gold Road. Running from<b> June 3 until July 1 for PC/Mac </b>and <b>June 18 until July 16 for console players</b>, this new Anniversary Spotlight grants everyone who delves deep into the system <b>a special reward</b>. </p> 
<h2>Unlock a Multi-Rider Mount</h2> 
<p>What special reward? Complete the Scribing meta-achievement “Inheritor of the Scholarium” during the Anniversary Spotlight window and you can claim the coveted Wayrest Vanner Pillion Steed mount from the in-game Crown Store <b>for free</b>. </p> 
<p>To unlock this achievement, you need to complete every quest in the Scribing questline (six in total) and restore the Scholarium. </p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/967e64a3a506864ce4bb9f2fe7603af0.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Travel Tamriel together</i></p> 
<p>While a striking and handsome beast, the Wayrest Vanner Pillion Steed is no normal mount, as it supports two adventurers riding at once! What better way to explore West Weald? </p> 
<p>Note that you need <b>access to the Champion System</b> or have a <b>level 30 character</b> to begin the Scribing quest line. This mount can be claimed only during the promotion window (June 3 until July 1 for PC/Mac and June 18 until July 16 for console players)—get ready to prove your worth to the Luminaries of Magic! </p> 
<h2>Endeavor to Craft New Abilities</h2> 
<p>In addition to the unique achievement reward, after <i>Gold Road</i>'s launch, you'll discover a selection of Scribing-themed Endeavors to complete as well. These new Endeavors task you with using your custom-made abilities in your adventures throughout Tamriel, such as defeating enemies, healing your allies, and more. </p> 
<p>Note that these Endeavors will reward you with the typical number of Seals you might expect from other similar tasks and won't be active until June 18 (when the <i>Gold Road</i> Chapter and Update 42 are live on all platforms). </p> 
<h2>Celebrating ESO &amp; Gold Road</h2> 
<p>With the upcoming launch of the new Chapter, we can't wait to see what kind of unique handcrafted abilities the community comes up with during the Anniversary Spotlight—Gold Road. Don't forget, the only way to get your hands on that multi-rider mount is to complete the Scribing questline. Let us know if you're excited about the new system in <i>Gold Road</i> and how you plan to use it via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>—have fun!
</p><p> <i>The Elder Scrolls Online: Gold Road arrives for PC/Mac on June 3, 2024, and for Xbox and PlayStation consoles on June 18, 2024. Pre-purchase Gold Road now to receive unique bonus rewards at launch and immediate access to the Welkyndstone Ruins Wolf mount. Don't miss out!</i></p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>10th Anniversary</category>
            <category>Update 42</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/94407a059066148c8650612951a42f37.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Daily Login Rewards—June 2024]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66115</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66115</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Take a peek at some of the in-game rewards you can earn simply by logging in to The Elder Scrolls Online this June.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/adbdeae6be8c3716dffaf6726a3b6e26.jpg" /><p><i>Take a peek at some of the in-game rewards you can earn simply by logging in to The Elder Scrolls Online this June.</i></p> 
<p>Whether you and your fellow heroes are exploring West Weald or just beginning your <i>ESO</i> saga, you won't want to miss out on this month's tantalizing login rewards. Curious to learn more about Daily Login Rewards? Check out <a href="https://help.elderscrollsonline.com/#en/answer/41950">this help article</a> to discover all you need to know! </p> 
<p>Now, let's take a peek at some of the highlights you can receive throughout June 2024:</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Seals of Endeavor—Day 7</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/10/cbf054f9fa4122ee9be26996607da8d2.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Your Endeavors Pay Off!</i></p> 
<p>Log in this June and lay claim to a whopping <b>500</b> Seals of Endeavor, helping you obtain that one Crown Crate item you've had your eye on. Learn more about Seals of Endeavor and how to gain them in <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/59925">this help blog</a>.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Instant All Research Scroll x10—Day 14</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2021/11/1b9ed166a516ef5d656a69ce1ce41496.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Learn New Crafting Traits Swiftly</i></p> 
<p>Expedite the process needed to unlock new Blacksmithing, Clothing, Woodworking, and Jewelry crafting traits by one day through this set of ten Instant All Research Scrolls, available on day 14!</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>100,000 Gold—Day 21</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/4fd2fa272aef9a9fb443be645a775da3.png" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Gleaming, Glittering Gold!</i></p> 
<p>If your coin purse is a little light, don't worry. We've prepared a care package of 100,000 Gold for you to snag after your 21<sup>st</sup> login this month. You can use these newly obtained riches to help fund your adventures in Gold Road but try not to spend it all at once!</p><p><br></p> 
<p>This is just a brief preview of the 30 login rewards you can claim each day this month. If you'd like to view the full list, head over to the Daily Rewards section of the in-game Crown Store on June 1 to learn more! Are you excited to enjoy these complimentary login rewards while adventuring in the new <i>Gold Road</i> Chapter? Let us know via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>. </p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Daily Rewards</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/adbdeae6be8c3716dffaf6726a3b6e26.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Community Spotlight—Hearth and Homes]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66109</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66109</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Admire this selection of intricately designed homesteads, produced by creative members of the ESO community.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/617acf8193de6405c67e3b1f0adedbd1.jpg" /><p><i>Admire this selection of intricately designed homesteads, produced by creative members of the ESO community.</i></p> 
<p>To celebrate May's <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65941">Anniversary Spotlight—Hearth and Homes</a>, we offered the Sword-Singer's Redoubt household as a free login reward to all players. Then, we challenged our passionate community of <i>ESO</i> home designers to transform this vacant abode into a fully decorated home. Well, the submissions are in, and we wanted to share just a few of our favorites with you:</p><p><br></p> 
<p><a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/comment/8106431/#Comment_8106431">EmperorRemanIV</a></p> 
<p><i>"The Dragontail Camp, containing its own wayshrine, is the Imperial fortified border between the Daggerfall Covenant and Reman IV's Second Empire of Cyrodiil territory taken from the Tharn's Seventh Legion in the March of Ephesus."</i></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/bc0962d1da9a06cee03e09c4da9613ef.jpg" />
<p><br></p><p><a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/comment/8106593/#Comment_8106593">Googoo</a></p> 
<p><i>"Redguard style bedroom. For those who seek rest after a long day of trading at the market. Or mining in the crystal cave."</i></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/b20b8d785d0e6390a64a7d0b94e1e725.jpg" />
<p><br></p><p><a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/comment/8106749/#Comment_8106749">JohnBlacksad</a></p> 
<p><i>"Aladdin's cave of Wonders. This is a project I wanted to do for YEARS. Thank you for giving it away like this; it ended up being such an unexpected perfect match."</i></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/39461cc503ba9e1d9b00ccd659c15ea2.jpg" />
<p><br></p><p><a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/comment/8107403/#Comment_8107403">EdjeSwift</a></p> 
<p><i>"Because of the split-up nature of the structure, I'm doing various things with it. I'm more of a spartan, yet striking kind of decorator. The Bangkorai doorway is a tribute to the Dark Brotherhood."</i></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/9f1446cf32ab368748dc758783c00e13.jpg" />
<p><br></p><p><a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/comment/8108660/#Comment_8108660">Olen_Mikko</a></p> 
<p><i>"Khajiit takeover in Alik'r"</i></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/aff6de73e04082925bc58cf6cb7f0e66.jpg" />
<p><br></p><p><a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/comment/8110122/#Comment_8110122">MageCatF4F</a></p> 
<p><i>"Redguards love technology. After all, they invented cannons while the rest of Tamriel was muttering evil eye curses. Here a gang of international pirates (Inter-Rat) has contracted Mad Scientist Biro Dar to build them an airship raider, the steam powered "Zubenelgenubi" of 10 guns. Join the crew, climb aboard, and wreak havoc from the sky. EHT needed to fire cannons. An EHT open house named: Zubenelgenubi."</i></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/206fe4e21a0de580b39f8badb709363c.jpg" />
<p><br></p><p><a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/comment/8113043/#Comment_8113043">Wolfcrisp</a></p> 
<p><i>"Redguards are my favorite race, so I made a small Redguard sword academy. This house is open, it's my sword singer aerie in NA, and I'm </i><a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/profile/wolfcrisp"><i>@wolfcrisp</i></a><i>.</i><i>"</i></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/79d2db5e1d88d8af20b0422640ae6dcd.jpg" />
<p><br></p><p><a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/comment/8110832/#Comment_8110832">Grizzbeorn</a></p> 
<p><i>"I've re-conceptualized the Redoubt as kind of a makeshift Dark Brotherhood sanctuary, having Hilde and Kor onsite as its ‘caretakers,' with a secondary, though related, focus as a space where Hilde can find the inner peace she seeks, based on cues from the DB storyline."</i></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/5c61713086f61f11f220725faf23b94f.png" />
<p><br></p><p><a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/comment/8110855/#Comment_8110855">Futerko</a></p> 
<p><i>"Ganesha temple."</i></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/4c18726307309a7dd5dc70430adc922a.jpg" />
<p><br></p><p><a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/comment/8111053/#Comment_8111053">Emilyhyoyeon</a></p> 
<p><i>"The Desert Pass Oasis is a rest stop along a small trade route in Hammerfell, especially known for its refreshing lounge pool and washing pavilions. It's popular among traders and travelers alike with its many cozy gathering tents and quaint amenities. PC EU open for public visit. ign @ emilypumpkin."</i></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/2d5832fe365ea8517565227ad2e21694.jpg" />
<p><br></p><p><a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/comment/8110895/#Comment_8110895">Seecodenotgames</a></p> 
<p><i>"This is my new Redguard themed house: Alik'r Oasis Paradise."</i></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/83f770887d93e0a680cad7377f55a5ee.jpg" />
<p><br></p><p><a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/comment/8112192/#Comment_8112192">Lorros</a></p> 
<p><i>"I decided to take a different approach to the new Sword-Singer's Redoubt home, turning it into a crafting library and bazaar."</i></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/25c669c0ff0c506b7c64804d61ddc153.jpg" />
<p><br></p><p><a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/comment/8113148/#Comment_8113148">TeruKisuke</a></p> 
<p><i>"The build started with an idea for a ‘Pretty Pink Stationery Store.' Then, I built a city around it. TeruKisuke on Xbox NA server."</i></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/25dbdf5bff58f943eb06e471b993cdbf.jpg" />
<p><br></p><p><a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/comment/8110567/#Comment_8110567">SilverBride</a></p> 
<p><i>"My Sword-Singer's Redoubt is a place for travelers to stop and rest on their journeys through Alik'r and Bangkorai. It offers some sitting areas to read and relax, and some food and drink to replenish. There is also a sauna room to soak their weary bones. The underground cave area has some Druidic furnishings and candles that provide a peaceful place to meditate away from the heat of the desert sun."</i></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/09a8df8fb9ba1f1fdd79eb740baba571.jpg" />
<p><br></p><p>A massive “thank you” to the awesome members of the #ESOFam for sharing their <a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/657931/show-us-your-sword-singers-redoubt-housing-creations">renovations</a> on the Sword-Singer's Redoubt! Don't forget, there's still time to claim it for yourself, <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65941">simply by logging in</a>! Have you claimed your free house this month? If so, we'd love to see how you've transformed this desert fortress. Feel free to share your designs with us via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (Formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/ElderScrollsOnline">Facebook</a>. </p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>10th Anniversary</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/617acf8193de6405c67e3b1f0adedbd1.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Time is Running Out! Pre-Purchase Gold Road Now to Receive Exclusive Rewards]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66073</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66073</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Don't miss your chance to pre-purchase The Elder Scrolls Online: Gold Road and gain access to unique in-game items at launch!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/b9e68fa29ddb5e9a9178b5bd557c54b9.jpg" /><p><i>Don't miss your chance to pre-purchase The Elder Scrolls Online: Gold Road and gain access to unique in-game items at launch!</i></p> 
<p>Your adventure across West Weald is just around the corner (June 3 for PC/Mac and June 18 for Xbox and PlayStation consoles), but there is still time to pre-purchase your copy of <i>The Elder Scrolls Online: Gold Road</i>. Even better, by pre-purchasing now, you will immediately receive the <b>Welkyndstone Ruins Wolf mount</b>.</p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/695dd22b343dbff1bcd1cbff8cec0b46.png" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Welkyndstone Ruins Wolf Mount</i></p> 
<p>In addition to receiving this mount, any pre-purchase of <i>Gold Road</i> will grant you the following bonus items at launch:</p> 
<ul><li>Eyebright Raven pet</li><li>Strid River Fisherfolk costume</li><li>×1 Diamond Anniversary Crate</li><li>Gold Road Treasure Maps</li><li>×2 Experience Scrolls (+100% for 1 hour)</li></ul>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/61987905918d3f483aa51b4455721207.jpg" />
<p>These items are only available until the launch of <i>Gold Road</i> in June, so be sure to pick up your copy soon! </p> 
<p>Struggling to decide which version of <i>ESO:</i> <i>Gold Road </i>suits you? We recommend checking out <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65365">this blog</a> for a breakdown of what each edition of the Chapter offers. Once you've carefully considered all your options, you can click the button below to pre-purchase <i>Gold Road.</i></p><p><br></p><p>Are you excited to explore West Weald and confront the agents of the Forgotten Prince? Perhaps you're looking forward to tailoring your very own custom skills via the new <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65899">Scribing system</a>? Let us know which aspects of <i>The Elder Scrolls Online: Gold Road</i> you're most looking forward to<i> </i>via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>!</p><p><i>The Elder Scrolls Online: Gold Road arrives for PC/Mac on June 3, 2024, and for Xbox and PlayStation consoles on June 18, 2024. Pre-purchase Gold Road now to receive unique bonus rewards at launch and immediate access to the Welkyndstone Ruins Wolf mount. Don't miss out!</i> </p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Gold Road</category>
            <category>Update 42</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/b9e68fa29ddb5e9a9178b5bd557c54b9.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enjoy Bonus Gold, XP, & More as the Explorer's Celebration Returns]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66063</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66063</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Explore the far reaches of Tamriel and receive bonus rewards during the Explorer's Celebration!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/e101d13d0410d44eae3082858431c07f.jpg" /><p><i>Explore the far reaches of Tamriel and receive bonus rewards during the Explorer's Celebration!</i></p> 
<p>Starting today, May 23 at 10AM EDT, and running until May 28 at 10AM EDT, the Explorer's Celebration returns, granting you bonus rewards as you explore Tamriel.</p> 
<p>During the bonus period, <i>ESO</i>'s intrepid explorers can enjoy the following:</p> 
<ul><li>Increased drops from harvest nodes (this does not include fishing or creature drops such as leather)</li><li>+100% XP gains from every source</li><ul><li> These bonuses stack with other XP boosts such as scrolls or group multipliers</li></ul><li>+100% gold earned from monster kills, quest rewards, and similar sources</li></ul> 
<p>These bonuses are available in all of <i>ESO</i>'s zones! From the maddening stacks of Apocrypha to the serene isle of Artaeum, you can earn additional rewards no matter where you go!</p> 
<p>Remember, the Explorer's Celebration isn't a quest- or ticket-based event, and no unique achievements or collectibles are available. Additionally, the Impresario's shop will remain closed during this period as the merchant takes a bit of time for herself. The Explorer's Celebration runs for a limited time, so get exploring and have fun!</p> 
<p><i>The Explorer's Celebration starts on May 23 at 10AM EDT, and it runs until Tuesday, May 28 at 10AM EDT.</i></p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Events</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/e101d13d0410d44eae3082858431c07f.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Register Today for the 10-Year Elder Scrolls Online Celebration Event in São Paulo, Brazil!]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66045</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/66045</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Join up with other passionate fans for an evening of fun during Brazil's first ever Elder Scrolls Online in-person community event.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/379ede50239afc3e4021271dafddb3d2.jpg" /><p><i>Join up with other passionate fans for an evening of fun during Brazil's first ever Elder Scrolls Online in-person community event.</i></p> 
<p>The global celebration of <i>ESO</i>'s 10-Year Anniversary continues, this time taking us to São Paulo, Brazil, where we have prepared a party the local #ESOFam won't want to miss! </p> 
<p>On May 27, the Taverna Medieval will be host to the 10-Year Celebration event, Brazil's <b>first ever in-person community gathering</b> that promises a variety of fun, <i>Elder Scrolls</i>-themed activities! </p> 
<p>Attendees can expect an evening of non-stop Tamrielic entertainment, including potion crafting, archery training, rune readings, and more! Feeling peckish? Grab a slice of anniversary cake and enjoy an assortment of medieval bites while mingling with your fellow fans. We've even arranged several game stations with <i>ESO </i>ready to play.</p> 
<p>Eager to sign up? Click the button below and follow the instructions to register for this new in-person event. Note that places are limited, so don't hesitate to show your interest.</p><p><br></p><p>This event is one of many being hosted across the world, so be sure to keep an eye out for further news on upcoming celebrations you won't want to miss. Are you ready to join us in Brazil and continue celebrating <i>ESO</i>'s 10-Year Anniversary alongside your fellow community members? Let us know via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline" target="_blank">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>.</p><p><i>If you have any questions regarding event details, please reach out to us on our Brazilian social channels via <a href="https://twitter.com/BethesdaBrasil" target="_blank" style="">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/bethesdabrasil/" style="">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/BethesdaBrasil/" style="">Facebook</a>.</i></p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Community</category>
            <category>10th Anniversary</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/379ede50239afc3e4021271dafddb3d2.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Listen to The Elder Scrolls Online: Necrom Soundtrack Online Now!]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65643</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65643</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Grab your copy of the ESO: Necrom Official Soundtrack, now available for digital purchase and download!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/02/a97678539c0c7b6e14e2b8d25b4efd28.png" /><p><i>Grab your copy of the ESO: Necrom Official Soundtrack, now available for digital purchase and download!</i></p> 
<p>Immerse yourself in the weird and wonderful worlds of Apocrypha and the Telvanni Peninsula with the melodies featured on <i>The Elder Scrolls Online: Necrom</i> Official Soundtrack. You can get your hands on the collection right now from the following platforms:</p> 
<ul><li><a href="http://itunes.apple.com/album/id1742430033?ls=1&amp;app=itunes">Apple Music</a></li><li><a href="https://open.spotify.com/album/6IbTHbVWC7csK2lACOmgeI">Spotify</a></li><li><a href="https://music.amazon.com/albums/B0D2BDQB29">Amazon Music</a></li></ul> 
<p>Are you going to add the <i>Necrom</i> soundtrack to your music library? Let us know via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/ElderScrollsOnline">Facebook</a>!</p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Music</category>
            <category>Necrom</category>
            <category>Shadow Over Morrowind</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/02/a97678539c0c7b6e14e2b8d25b4efd28.png" length="0" type="image/png"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Anniversary Spotlight—Make A Home Away from Home with These Free Housing Rewards]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65941</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65941</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Homeowners across Tamriel can claim the Sword-Singer's Redoubt House and friendly houseguests for FREE during May's 10-Year Anniversary promotion.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/ec015f0e2283df6f7f37c42795a7225e.jpg" /><p><i>Homeowners across Tamriel can claim the Sword-Singer's Redoubt House and friendly houseguests for FREE during May's 10-Year Anniversary promotion.</i></p> 
<h2>There's No Place Like Home</h2> 
<p>Part of the ongoing 10-Year Anniversary Celebration, the “Anniversary Spotlight—Hearth &amp; Home” kicks off today and continues until Friday, May 31, 2024. If you're a weary adventurer in need of a place to call home, you can pick up the all-new FREE Sword-Singer's Redoubt house and various other goodies during the promotional period. </p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/04/795f50a09dd23756ecd8977fe02c1ad5.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Log in to claim this home</i></p> 
<p>Collecting your complementary household is as simple as claiming the Sword-Singer's Redoubt as part of this month's <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65939">Daily Login Rewards</a>. You'll need to log in during May three times to get it—don't miss out!</p> 
<p>Of course, to transform this desert oasis into your new home, you'll need to decorate! Luckily, starting today, you can pick up various furnishings and houseguests on discount in the in-game Crown Store.</p> 
<h2>Host Friendly Houseguests </h2> 
<p>During the promotion period, you can claim the Necrom Guard Miraso houseguest from the in-game Crown Store <b>free </b>after earning the Party Planner achievement. To unlock this achievement, have three players visit your home simultaneously. Better start sending out those invitations!</p> 
<p>Additionally, you can also claim the Alchemy Houseguest <b>free </b>from the in-game Crown Store after completing the Expert Resin Harvester and Novice Alchemy Furnisher achievements. To earn the Expert Resin Harvester achievement, harvest 25 Alchemical Resin, and to unlock the Novice Alchemy Furnisher, learn any Alchemy formula.</p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/e9120514d38b418764e7b8375ed854b8.jpg" />
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/ded43ab4e89227fc8511ecbc56359bb8.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Unlock these two houseguests free! </i></p> 
<h2>Build Upon Your Endeavors</h2> 
<p>Throughout the Anniversary Spotlight, Daily and Weekly Endeavors will more frequently feature challenges related to housing, with increased rewards received upon completion. These include placing furnishings.</p> 
<h2>Welcome Home!</h2> 
<p>Experience the vast sea of opportunities for customization and decoration that came with owning your own household in Tamriel during the Anniversary Spotlight—Hearth &amp; Home! Don't miss your chance to claim valuable free rewards during this promotion period, taking place between now and May 31. How will you transform the Sword-Singer's Redoubt into your dream home? Share screenshots of the finished product with us via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>. </p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>10th Anniversary</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/ec015f0e2283df6f7f37c42795a7225e.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Crown Store Showcase—May 2024]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65943</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65943</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Check out these ancient artifacts, furry friends, and loads of furnishings that will transform your modest house into a palace, all arriving in the in-game Crown Store this May!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/5cb93b877bc43731b308c9736439a24b.jpg" /><p><i>Check out these ancient artifacts, furry friends, and loads of furnishings that will transform your modest house into a palace, all arriving in the in-game Crown Store this May!</i></p> 
<p>Take a peek at all the items arriving in the in-game Crown Store during May 2024. You can also check out what is currently available on the <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/crownstore">Crown Store page</a>. Do any of these goodies catch your eye? Visit the <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/buycrowns">Buy Crowns page</a> to acquire as many crowns as you need! Certain items and offers will be available for a limited time only, so be sure to read their details below and don't miss out.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>ESO Plus Deals</h2> 
<p>All ESO Plus™ members have access to a monthly selection of exclusive deals and items. You can find more information about them in <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/54825">this article</a>.</p> 
<p><b>Exclusive Free Items</b></p> 
<p><b>Statuette: Orc Warrior</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/e735e15239a9b9102e01a98cd4431e23.jpg" />
<p><i>A miniature statue of an Orc warrior emanating strength.</i></p> 
<p>The Statuette: Orc Warrior will be available in the Crown Store FREE, exclusively to ESO Plus Members on all platforms for a limited time, from May 30 to June 27, 2024, at 10AM EDT.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Painting: Infinite Archive</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/03/0acdcaa2fd0d8b91cdd7d0ed199736bf.jpg" />
<p><i>"Those whom Hermaeus Mora calls to the Infinite Archive may serve him—or may choose to leave. But who, upon understanding the limitless knowledge they may access, dares refuse the Lord of Secrets without feeling bereft forever after?"—Mage Allierwen</i></p> 
<p>The Painting: Infinite Archive will be available in the Crown Store FREE, exclusively to ESO Plus Members on all platforms for a limited time, from April 29 to May 30, 2024, at 10AM EDT.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Crafting</h2> 
<p><b>Crown Crafting Motif: Sunspire Style</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/886df7f89a1ef01f5456a01a23b39759.jpg" />
<p><i>Use to learn the Sunspire crafting style.</i></p> 
<p>The Crown Crafting Motif: Sunspire Style returns to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 2 to May 6, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item. Motif chapters, and very rarely the complete book, have a chance to drop from Nahviintaas in Normal or Veteran Sunspire.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Crown Crafting Motif: Welkynar</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/51218ce4b7609692172285d8d1fa91ec.jpg" />
<p><i>Use to learn the Welkynar crafting style.</i></p> 
<p>The Crown Crafting Motif: Welkynar will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 6 to May 13, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item. Motif chapters can be crafted by collecting Welkynar Bindings from the weekly quest for Cloudrest and ten Welkynar Bindings from defeating the final boss in Cloudrest.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Crown Crafting Motif: Annihilarch's Chosen</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/41419836f0a7eb88de48a4a4859b68ab.jpg" />
<p><i>Use to learn the Annihilarch's Chosen crafting style. </i></p> 
<p>The Crown Crafting Motif: Annihilarch's Chosen will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 20 to May 28, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item. Motif chapters, and very rarely the complete book, have a chance to drop from the reward chest after defeating Deadlands Oblivion Portals.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Outfit Styles</b></p> 
<p><b>Molag Kena Arms Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/4902e98ee01f99e0094c9881726beaf9.jpg" />
<p><i>Alter your weapon's appearance to match the Undaunted Molag Kena awards by using this complete set of Outfit styles.</i></p> 
<p>The Molag Kena Arms Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 6 to May 13, 2024 at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item. The matching mask page will have a small chance to drop from Molag Kena from veteran White-Gold Tower. The matching shoulder page can be purchased from Urgarlag Chief-bane for 50 Undaunted Keys, or has a chance of dropping from Urgarlag's Mystery Coffer for 1 Key. Having the achievement “Ire of the Storm” increases the drop chances of both items.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Elder Scrolls Artifact: Sinweaver</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/2f2945532e96261e5c7f112bd5030d82.jpg" />
<p><i>Alter your two-handed sword's Outfit style with a replica of the Sinweaver Elder Scrolls Artifact, the legendary Elven claymore.</i></p> 
<p>The Elder Scrolls Artifact: Sinweaver will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 9 to May 16, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Selene Arms Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/d4b329ea500ec0668a1c499de865e314.jpg" />
<p><i>Alter your weapon's appearance to match the Undaunted Selene awards by using this complete set of Outfit styles.</i></p> 
<p>The Selene Arms Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 13 to May 20, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item. The matching mask page will have a small chance to drop from Selene from veteran Selene's Web. The matching shoulder page can be purchased from Glirion the Redbeard for 50 Undaunted Keys, or has a chance of dropping from Glirion's Mystery Coffer for 1 Key. Having the achievement “All Wrapped Up” increases the drop chances of both items.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Baron Zaudrus Arms Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/0d1e5b40aeb4a6dd8cb9e6bdba9f0ec2.jpg" />
<p><i>Alter your weapon's appearance to match the Undaunted Baron Zaudrus awards by using this complete set of Outfit styles.</i></p> 
<p>The Baron Zaudrus Arms Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 20 to May 28, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item. The matching mask page will have a small chance to drop from Baron Zaudrus from veteran Cauldron. The matching shoulder page can be purchased from Urgarlag Chief-bane for 50 Undaunted Keys, or has a chance of dropping from Urgarlag's Mystery Coffer for 1 Key. Having the achievement “Schemes Disrupted” increases the drop chances of both items.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Truth and Logic</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/07/945554111d463332a7a7cf4d87cb51e5.jpg" />
<p><i>Alter your weapon's appearance to match the Truth and Logic Weapons by using this complete set of Outfit styles.</i></p> 
<p>The Truth and Logic Outfit Style will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 28 to June 3, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Elder Scrolls Artifact: Spear of Bitter Mercy</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/9112db2481493934bc9b1fa09e52fe19.jpg" />
<p><i>Alter your staff's Outfit style with a replica of the Spear of Bitter Mercy Elder Scrolls Artifact, the signature weapon of the Daedric Prince Hircine.</i></p> 
<p>The Elder Scrolls Artifact: Spear of Bitter Mercy will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 30 to June 6, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<h2>Wardrobe</h2> 
<p><b>Costumes</b></p> 
<p><b>Nordic Knot Doublet and Breeches</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/5f3ccb9d5ab8a848bafef2fdbf140851.jpg" />
<p><i>"Nordic Knot designs symbolize the heritage of the people of Skyrim," says designer Jork of Windhelm. "This upscale ensemble pays tribute to that tradition, and looks good even on those not lucky enough to be Nords."</i></p> 
<p>The Nordic Knot Doublet and Breeches costume returns to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 13 to May 16, 2024, at 10AM EDT.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Shrike's Nocturnal Frock</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/cb99621e7a9c0b80dd1791294b54bad9.jpg" />
<p><i>Do you like to keep to the shadows, yet long for a striking look of your own? Any admirer of the Prince of Night and Darkness will appreciate this eye-catching costume.</i></p> 
<p>The Shrike's Nocturnal Frock costume will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 30 to June 6, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Telvanni Master Wizard</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/37d2cbd6372ebb33ee8d2968c1504c36.jpg" />
<p><i>Lesser mages are often surprised to find that the usual apparel of a Telvanni Master Wizard is more stately than ostentatious. The truth is, Wizard Lords such as Divayth Fyr have no need of gaudy display. Their power lies elsewhere.</i></p> 
<p>The Telvanni Master Wizard costume will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 20 to May 28, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<h2>Crate</h2> 
<p><b>Scalecaller Crate</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/fc1586244a8880a334ad7711df3737ce.jpg" />
<p><i>A mystery collection of Scalecaller-related items!</i></p> 
<p>Scalecaller Crates return to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 9 to May 23, 2024, at 10AM EDT.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Xanmeer Crate</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/f9baab7dc0449c7fba0cc17601fbbd0d.jpg" />
<p><i>A mystery collection of Murkmire related items!</i></p> 
<p>Xanmeer Crates return to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 23 to June 6, 2024, at 10AM EDT. Additionally, ESO Plus Members will receive a discount when purchasing the Xanmeer 15 Crate Bundle.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Furniture </h2> 
<p><b>Bust: Abnur Tharn</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/0a01525b1de77e006becfabdc0f8e6ff.jpg" />
<p><i>Experience the wisdom of Abnur Tharn within your very own home with this talking bust! Display this noble piece of statuary in a place of prominence so that you and every houseguest may listen intently to the former Grand Chancellor.</i></p> 
<p>The Bust: Abnur Tharn will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 2 to May 9, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Statue, Pride of Alkosh Hero</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/10fea1b6858009cc2f574ef223c959bb.jpg" />
<p><i>The Pride of Alkosh Hero brandishes an hourglass lantern while in a victory stance over a vanquished Dragon. The lantern shines forth with a warm glow, a bright beacon, or not at all; owner's choice!</i></p> 
<p>The Statue, Pride of Alkosh Hero will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 2 to May 9, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Furnishing Pack: Moon-Bishop's Sanctuary</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/8b14546e6e4c1739b3cabb3781d34d13.jpg" />
<p><i>Display your reverence for the Moons with this assortment of clerical Elsweyr furnishings. Luxurious tapestries, tasteful furniture, and even a target dro-m'Athra will make your home the envy of Khajiiti adepts everywhere.</i></p> 
<p>The Furnishing Pack: Moon-Bishop's Sanctuary will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 2 to May 9, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Furnishing Pack: Shadow and Stone</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/e0448cd99574ef2a96a502ddee4f6986.jpg" />
<p><i>By my hand blood enters the Marsh. By my deed the Marsh is fed and grows fertile. By my silent watch the Hist may thrive. Honor my doings, O Sithis, for my brethren show me but fear. Guard me not, O Sithis, for only my own strength honors you.</i></p> 
<p>The Furnishing Pack: Shadow and Stone will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 2 to May 9, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Furnishing Pack: Molag Bal</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/57b87346a4c139fd93317ab74e102a02.jpg" />
<p><i>Furnishings related to the Daedric Prince Molag Bal and Coldharbour.</i></p> 
<p>The Furnishing Pack: Molag Bal will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 9 to May 16, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Music Box, Diamond Melody</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/c246eac055cf547898977422d96d1087.jpg" />
<p><i>When activated, plays a music box composition of the traditional imperial song "Chim-el Adabal."</i></p> 
<p>The Music Box, Diamond Melody will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 9 to May 16, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Craglorn Multicultural Kitchen Pack</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/cad04660576670638afc1599a8d23bab.jpg" />
<p><i>A selection of mainly Ra Gada-inspired cross-cultural kitchen furnishings, ideal for Earthtear Cavern.</i></p> 
<p>The Craglorn Multicultural Kitchen Pack will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 9 to May 16, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Music Box, Songbird's Paradise</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/38cfdbbd622b6069ad08d2a5375fc9f5.jpg" />
<p><i>When activated, plays a music box arrangement of the uplifting "Songbird's Paradise" composition.</i></p> 
<p>The Music Box, Songbird's Paradise will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 16 to May 20, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Target Deadlands Harvester, Trial</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/3da4830f008a0b889872e0990b1a1d4d.jpg" />
<p><i>This is a large house item. This may be attacked and, when destroyed, will regenerate. This creature is equivalent to a veteran trial boss. Its abilities include granting a resource-restoring synergy opportunity, performance buffs, and self debuffs.</i></p> 
<p>The Target Deadlands Harvester, Trial will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 16 to May 23, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Furnishing Pack: Fargrave Bazaar</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/7c9007743da2f8a0444acddd043f94cd.jpg" />
<p><i>Bring Fargrave's Bazaar to your own abode with this collection of curious commodities. Floating books, suspicious specimens, drifting globules, and more await your mercantile merriment.</i></p> 
<p>The Furnishing Pack: Fargrave Bazaar will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 16 to May 23, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Furnishing Pack: Lord Vivec</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/d422359349635e3041d3552f5f082ff5.jpg" />
<p><i>Furnishings inspired by Lord Vivec, the Tribunal Temple, and Morrowind.</i></p> 
<p>The Furnishing Pack: Lord Vivec will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 16 to May 23, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Music Box, Fargrave Daydreams</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/68446297f808e44dde8f63b42154f28c.jpg" />
<p><i>When activated, this artistic rendering of the Celestial Palanquin plays a music box arrangement of the ominous "Fargrave Daydreams" composition.</i></p> 
<p>The Music Box, Fargrave Daydreams will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 23 to May 28, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Furnishing Pack: Tyrants of the Merethic Era</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/314edd4a992b7511ae062d3d21e03487.jpg" />
<p><i>These relics date back to the height of the Dragon Cult's power, long before the bloody revolution of the Dragon War. Though this particular Dragon's name is long forgotten, its story is still told by the ancient friezes found in its barrow.</i></p> 
<p>The Furnishing Pack: Tyrants of the Merethic Era will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 30 to June 6, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Music Box, Enigmas of the Elder Way</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/ddb493e96f6c92a22eca987db6a1b93a.jpg" />
<p><i>When activated, plays a music box arrangement of the mesmerizing "Enigmas of the Elder Way" composition.</i></p> 
<p>The Music Box, Enigmas of the Elder Way will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 30 to June 6, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Houses</h2> 
<p><b>Elinhir Private Arena</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/2eeaeb88ab0d6c9d2887febcfee3ee8c.jpg" />
<p><i>Pit Fighting promoter Crottus "Thumbs-Down" Lycus built this private arena atop the haunted ruins of Molavar because the land was cheap, and what could go wrong? He vanished mysteriously some time ago, and now his unique Arena Home is back on the market.</i></p> 
<p>The Elinhir Private Arena will return to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 16 to May 23, 2024, at 10AM EDT. Furnished and unfurnished versions will be available.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Houseguests</h2> 
<p><b>Caska</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/4a9d8d9634f3369a7349538bd5f3d9b1.jpg" />
<p><i>Caska the Senche-raht serves as the first mate on The Perfect Pounce, and she loves time off to pursue other interests, perhaps in your house! After adding Caska to your home, you can set her on a path, plus you and your visitors can speak with her.</i></p> 
<p>Caska will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 2 to May 9, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Hezehk</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/6a8b38d70b6c98b8b72f59b5b375ae88.jpg" />
<p><i>Fresh from Madam Whim's in Fargrave, this irrepressible Skaafin immediately imparts a surprisingly upbeat atmosphere to your abode. After adding Hezehk to your home, you can set him on a path, plus you and your visitors can speak with him.</i></p> 
<p>Hezehk will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 9 to May 16, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Sereyne</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/f3b691f6fbfbd499763cf3b1a8c769f7.jpg" />
<p><i>An outlaw with a talent for magic but a thirst for alcohol, Sereyne wants a cozy place to drink her troubles away. Perhaps you can provide? After adding Sereyne to your home, you can set her on a path, plus you and your visitors can speak with her.</i></p> 
<p>Sereyne will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 16 to May 23, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p> <b>Scruut</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/9a2ec54e60ae1c6b7aaf345beb59d3b9.jpg" />
<p><i>Divergences in fate's threads draw Scruut's attention. Yet, this mighty Watchling seeks your company until the Great Eye summons her. Coincidence? After adding Scruut to your home, you can set her on a path, plus you and your visitors can speak with her.</i></p> 
<p>The new Scruut houseguest will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 23 to May 30, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Arox the Mutilator</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/f64aaa9a27c2088ecda6d14e5dc46c08.jpg" />
<p><i>Kneel before the mighty Arox and he might just offer to crush your enemies for you! But, as a daedrat. Not his former much bigger self. After adding Arox to your home, you can set him on a path, plus you and your visitors can speak with him.</i></p> 
<p>Arox the Mutilator will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 30 to June 6, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Assistants</h2> 
<p><b>Xyn, Planar Purveyor</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/12dd55fdb222cd7b5d9b3fc0fe4cd9f2.jpg" />
<p><i>Xyn travels the Daedric realms looking for profitable opportunities. They'll happily take your goods (or those of your groupmates) in exchange for common mortal coinage.</i></p> 
<p>The new Xyn, Planar Purveyor will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 9 to May 16, 2024, at 10AM EDT.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Mounts</h2> 
<p><b>Dro-m'Athra Senche</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/bc3079fc4577c0014455caadac57136f.jpg" />
<p><i>The Senche-shaped dro-m'Athra are known to the Twilight Cantors as the sar-m'Athra, but everyone else just calls these eerie and uncanny mounts the Dro-m'Athra Senche.</i></p> 
<p>The Dro-m'Athra Senche mount returns to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 2 to May 6, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Spotted Duneracer Senche-raht</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/42eadc7022d663a151527a346ef162ec.jpg" />
<p><i>Years of winning racing competitions finally bored Hazazkheran, so he ran messages for the queen for a time. Alas, even that grew predictable. Now he wants to poke his whiskers into all the hidden corners of the world, perhaps with you.</i></p> 
<p>The Spotted Duneracer Senche-raht mount returns to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 6 to May 13, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Painted Wolf</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/aa393845450a0b38cf4066c46ad7de7c.jpg" />
<p><i>In the rugged badlands of central Hammerfell, even camels struggle to maneuver across the broken terrain. But wolves can go where even camels cannot, so the roving Redguards of the canyon lands have bred the local Painted Wolves into sure-footed mounts.</i></p> 
<p>The Painted Wolf mount will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 9 to May 13, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Riften Coalhorn Ram</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/5de2876c7731ea22af8c76645d96f2db.jpg" />
<p><i>None dare stare Riften's native ram in the eyes, it sees threats in many things, and only its owner can meet its gaze without needing to brace for an immediate headbutt. In short, would-be Riften Coalhorn Ram thieves are frequently airborne.</i></p> 
<p>The Riften Coalhorn Ram will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 28 to June 3, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Banded Guar Charger</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/9796950d1d85bf38d06322803f79e5b4.jpg" />
<p><i>A breed of guar bred for cavalry use, able to carry an armored warrior into battle.</i></p> 
<p>The Banded Guar Charger will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 30 to June 6, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<h2>Customized Action</h2> 
<p><b>Stonelore Split</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/b7bc6fc7b2b63976d5e55cfb21eb3820.jpg" />
<p><i>Trees grant gifts that linger after their passing. Druids recognize this gift as what it is, a blessing from Y'ffre. </i></p> 
<p>The Stonelore Split customized action will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 16 to May 20, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Malacath's Harvest</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/6b5f52a4c708a8abd963c2575e9f40be.jpg" />
<p><i>"Never underestimate any foe. And that includes the wilds of Wrothgar. Even the plants put up a fight here, which is why I use my ancestor's sharpest dagger and pray to Malacath with each sweep.” Ghaz of Orsinium.</i></p> 
<p>The new Malacath's Harvest customized action will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 30 to June 6, 2024, at 10AM EDT.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<h2>Pets</h2> 
<p><b>Dro-m'Athra Senche Cub</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/e501fd5cccbdf250f22e1e281f1c142f.jpg" />
<p><i>Combine Adorable with Abominable, and what do you get? The dro-m'Athra Senche Cub, the cutest thing ever to come out of the Dark Behind the World. Dance, kitten, dance!</i></p> 
<p>The Dro-m'Athra Senche Cub pet will return to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 2 to May 6, 2024, at 10AM EDT.</p><p><br></p><p> </p> 
<p><b>Dragontail Goat</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/3be02d6b67500e79088f7b5076b62475.jpg" />
<p><i>The brown Goats of the Dragontail Mountains are stronger than they look. There's a saying in Hammerfell: "Hits as hard as a Dragontail ram!"</i></p> 
<p>The Dragontail Goat pet will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 6 to May 13, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Vale Fawn</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/ce0467873f7b94be1ecb99b858666c68.jpg" />
<p><i>Though this adorable fawn's kin shimmer with hues different than its own, the first color ever seen was the pearly white glow on this one. Give it enough care and you can help it overcome its shyness, allowing it to cavort at your side.</i></p> 
<p>The Vale Fawn pet will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 13 to May 20, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Infernal Sep Adder</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/10e6028adc61b413856db7e89b952e0f.jpg" />
<p><i>Though it may look like it just crawled from the depths of the Deadlands, the Infernal Sep Adder is actually native to the higher altitudes of Hammerfell. As pets, they are not affectionate. Great conversation starters, though.</i></p> 
<p>The Infernal Sep Adder pet returns to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 20 to May 23, 2024, at 10AM EDT.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Ja'khajiit Khamira</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/35b8995e456060c6207d4fa7d28cf6e2.jpg" />
<p><i>Ready for action? Like Khamira herself, this kitten certainly is! With a roll and a hiss, Ja'khajiit Khamira enters your life, ready to face danger at your side.</i></p> 
<p>The Ja'khajiit Khamira pet will be available in the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 23 to May 28, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Anthorbred Avalanche Dog</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2021/11/f929b66cca21c527e1cc97aaa4540f73.jpg" />
<p><i>With this loyal dog at your side, you have a companion who can help you make it through even the most treacherous of avalanches in Pale Pass and other mountainous areas; even if it has to pull you out from under a pile of fallen snow and detritus.</i></p> 
<p>The Anthorbred Avalanche Dog pet returns to the Crown Store on all platforms for a limited time, from May 28 to May 30, 2024, at 10AM EDT. ESO Plus Members will receive a discount on this item.</p><p><br></p> 
<p>If you've been searching for some new furnishings or houseguests to populate your household, be sure to check out the in-game Crown Store this May! Want to pick up any of the items featured in this showcase? Don't forget to head over to the <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/crowns">Buy Crowns page</a> and stock up on crowns beforehand. Which housing accessories highlighted here are you looking to add to your homestead? Let us know via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline" target="_blank">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>. </p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Crown Store</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/05/5cb93b877bc43731b308c9736439a24b.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Daily Login Rewards—May 2024]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65939</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65939</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Keep cozy with a comfortable pile of rewards available just by logging in this May 2024.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/04/6eb60a409b1b03733f4ffdb84a1634e0.jpg" /><p><i>Keep cozy with a comfortable pile of rewards available just by logging in this May 2024.</i></p> 
<p>There are some huge login rewards coming to <i>The Elder Scrolls Online </i>you can claim in the month of May, including an entire house! Check out what exactly you can get below. Curious about Daily Login Rewards? Learn more by reading <a href="https://help.elderscrollsonline.com/#en/answer/41950">this help article</a>.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Sword-Singer's Redoubt—Day 3</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/04/795f50a09dd23756ecd8977fe02c1ad5.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Stay cool in the desert sun</i></p> 
<p>Make Hammerfell your home and get comfortable in this brand-new in-game house situated on the border of the Alik'r Desert and Bangkorai. Enjoy crystal caverns, oasis waters, and wide spans of sand and stone as part of the design of this remarkable reward.</p> 
<p>You'll receive the unfurnished house on just your third day of logins this month, starting things off with something spectacular. Speaking of spectacular, this house could be hinting at something special! You'll have to wait and see…</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Scalecaller Crown Crates—Days 4-8</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/04/07da169625f5e7a3e7bfcce2a2ef2af9.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Plunder Scalecaller's hoard</i></p> 
<p>Claim one crate a day for five days to collect five Scalecaller Crown Crates in total. You'll unlock creepy collectibles themed around Scalecaller Peak and Fang Lair, many of which are available for preview <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/26329">in this blog</a>.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Seals of Endeavor—Day 10</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2023/10/cbf054f9fa4122ee9be26996607da8d2.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Endeavor to get something nice</i></p> 
<p>More Seals of Endeavor make their way to you this month, helping you unlock the Crown Crate item of your dreams. Log in to claim a hefty purse of 500 Seals as your tenth daily reward this month. You can learn more about Seals of Endeavor <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/59925">in this blog</a>.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Bruma Spotted Pig pet—Day 14</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/04/f9a2004afe730908225e09db408854cb.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Too cute—don't even think about bacon!</i></p> 
<p>Don't you dare mention pork pies around this friendly fellow. He's far too charming to eat, but definitely a good option for head pats.</p><p><br></p> 
<p><b>Xanmeer Crown Crates—Days 16-20</b></p>
<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/04/82e49ed369e9d008d5f33215e09040c3.jpg" />
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>Treasures reclaimed from the mire</i></p> 
<p>More Crown Crates? That's right, there's another set of five crates that will be claimable over five more days. Acquiring all of them requires logging in at least twenty days in total, which seems like no time at all according to the Argonians of Black Marsh. You can preview a selection of the items available in the Xanmeer Crown Crates <a href="https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/55357">in this blog</a>.</p><p><br></p> 
<p>As fabulous as these rewards are, they are far from the only items on offer. To see everything, start your logins on May 1 and take a look at the full list! We think you'll find this month quite welcoming, so come right into Tamriel and make yourself at home.</p> 
<p>Which of the upcoming rewards are you most excited for? Let us know via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/elderscrollsonline">Facebook</a>. </p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Daily Rewards</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/04/6eb60a409b1b03733f4ffdb84a1634e0.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Gold Road Chapter & Update 42 Now Live on the PC/Mac Public Test Server!]]></title>
            <link>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65909</link>
            <guid>https://www.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/news/post/65909</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Wander paths untraveled by testing the new Gold Road Chapter and Update 42 base-game patch on the PC/Mac Public Test Server!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/04/b3ce5e4d284add2fef4a606f415460ad351985.jpg" /><p><i>Wander paths untraveled by testing the new Gold Road Chapter and Update 42 base-game patch on the PC/Mac Public Test Server!</i></p> 
<p>It's that time again—time to get an early look at <i>ESO</i>'s upcoming content and make the game better while you do so! The Public Test Server (PTS) has been updated to include the content from the <i>Gold Road</i> Chapter, including the new Scribing system, as well as the Update 42 base-game patch. To access the PTS environment, go to the Settings menu within the PC/Mac <i>ESO</i> launcher by toggling the “Show Public Test Environment” option. You can then download and access the test environment. Don't forget to leave feedback and report any bugs you come across by typing “/feedback” or “/bug” in chat.</p> 
<p>The PTS is open to any PC/Mac players, regardless of whether they own <i>ESO</i> or have pre-purchased <i>Gold Road</i>, so if you'd like to get your first look at the upcoming Chapter and more, be sure to jump in! </p> 
<p>For everything you need to know about <i>Gold Road</i>, Update 42, and this particular test, visit the <a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/656454/">PTS Patch Notes</a> on the official <i>ESO </i>forums.</p> 
<p>Are you excited for your first in-game look at West Weald and the all-new Daedric Prince? Let us know via <a href="https://twitter.com/TESOnline">X (formerly Twitter)</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elderscrollsonline/">Instagram</a>, or <a href="https://www.facebook.com/ElderScrollsOnline">Facebook</a>!</p> 
<p><i>The Elder Scrolls Online: Gold Road and Update 42 arrive June 3 on PC/Mac, and June 18 for Xbox and PlayStation consoles.</i></p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>News</category>
            <category>Community</category>
            <category>Update 42</category>
            <category>Gold Road</category>
            <enclosure url="https://esosslfiles-a.akamaihd.net/ape/uploads/2024/04/b3ce5e4d284add2fef4a606f415460ad351985.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Crown Store Gifting Update – October 2023]]></title>
            <link>https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/644559/crown-store-gifting-update-october-2023</link>
            <guid>https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/644559/crown-store-gifting-update-october-2023</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 20:22:11 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[Following up on Studio Director Matt Firor's message last month about the <a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/643289/update-on-current-and-future-status-of-gifting">current and future status of Crown Store Gifting</a>, we are moving forward with re-enabling this functionality for eligible players at the account level. In this post, we will detail what to expect.<br><br>
In September, we temporarily disabled Crown Store gifting due to a rapidly growing issue of "bad actors" using various fraudulent means to amass crowns without paying for them, then using them in turn to sell Crown Store items to players for real-world cash outside of the game client. That said, we recognize that gifting is a meaningful part of our community, and we are in the process of manually re-enabling Crown Store gifting access for select players who meet our specific criteria. This work will be complete tomorrow, October 11, during the maintenance window from 09:00 AM ET to 12:00 PM ET.<br><br>
Gifting eligibility is determined by an evolving list of factors including but not limited to the account being at least 180 days past its first login and previous engagement with in-game features. You may check if you have access to gifting in-game via the Crown Store as well as via <a href="https://account.elderscrollsonline.com/en-us/account/billing/billing-history">your billing history page</a> in the ESO account center. If you have access to Crown Store gifting, you will see "Allow Crown Store Gifting" in your billing history. If you try to send a gift via the in-game Crown Store and do not have access, you will see a "Gifting Locked" pop-up message. Please note that we are exploring better ways to display this information in-game in the future, such as updating the Gifting Tutorial.<br><br>
If you do not have access to Crown Store gifting after it is re-enabled on October 11, 2023, and wish for a review of your account, please visit <a href="https://help.elderscrollsonline.com">https://help.elderscrollsonline.com</a> and submit a Customer Support ticket. Please choose the Billing / Purchase / Code category then Platform &gt; I have a question about a sale / offer &gt; I want to send gift items from this account.<br><br>
We appreciate everyone's understanding and patience while we get this solution up and running. Multiple teams have worked long hours to evaluate the best technical solutions that we could stand up in a reasonably short time, while also prioritizing the Crown Store gifting player experience. We are dedicated to continuing to explore ways to make this better and reduce fraudulent activity in ESO. Thanks again for being a part of our community and for your continued support.]]></content:encoded>
            <category>Forum</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[New Patcher Rollout]]></title>
            <link>https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/642066/new-patcher-rollout</link>
            <guid>https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en/discussion/642066/new-patcher-rollout</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 20:49:19 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[Hello everyone! After plenty of testing <a href="https://forums.elderscrollsonline.com/en-gb/discussion/632782/new-eso-launcher-testing-and-launch-plan-pc-and-mac">during the last PTS period</a>, we are pleased to announce the rollout of our new patcher on the live servers for PC/Mac. The rollout of the new patcher will happen in four phases, with new countries being added during each phase. As we give countries access to the new patcher, we will make note of it in the list below by noting next to the country name (has the new patcher.) We will also note what phase we are currently in by specifying whether it has not started, in progress, or complete, next to the phase number. The countries getting the patcher are listed in order below.<br><br>
Thanks for your patience as we roll this out to all countries listed below. A special thanks to everyone who helped test out the launcher during the last PTS and provided feedback.<br><br>
Edit for 3/4/2024: All phases have now been complete.<br><br><b>Phase 1 (Complete) </b>
<ol><li>Netherlands (Has the new patcher)</li>
<li>Sweden (Has the new patcher)</li>
<li>Czech Republic/ Finland (Has the new patcher)</li>
<li>Norway/ Denmark (Has the new patcher)</li>
<li>Hungary/ Switzerland/ Romania (Has the new patcher)</li>
</ol><br><b>Phase 2 (Complete) </b>
<ol><li>Poland (Has the new patcher)</li>
<li>Spain/ Turkey (Has the new patcher)</li>
<li>Italy/ Austria/ Belgium/ Portugal/ Greece/ Ireland (Has the new patcher)</li>
</ol><br><b>Phase 3 (Complete) </b>
<ol><li>United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland/ France (Has the new patcher)</li>
<li>Germany (Has the new patcher)</li>
<li>United States of America (Has the new patcher)</li>
</ol><br><b>Phase 4 (Complete) </b><br>
This phase will encompass all other countries where ESO is available, that are not listed above. (All countries where ESO is available now have access to the launcher.)<br><br><b>Known Issues</b>
<ul><li>Some Czech Republic players may not have their country recognized, thus making them unable to upgrade the patch at this time. We are aware of the issue and working toward a solution.</li>
<li>Audio issues with sound volume and sound effects. We have a bug in for this and are working on a fix for the future.</li>
</ul>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>Forum</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>